"After reaching the shore"
"I love the sea."
"After the hair greys"
"I understand the world."
"Yesterday's joys come together"
"Today, at this moment,"
they find meaning."
"Today's joys will come together"
"To find their
meaning tomorrow."
"To live my life
that I never lived."
"Unable to bear this, upwards I go"
"To kindle my never ending passion."
"Here and now, I am coming out of it"
"Here and now,
I immerse into the depths"
"I look at myself
as someone else."
"Not with any reason,
just naturally."
"With clarity, like
that of a sunray!"
"I dont belong to these depths,
but I dwell in them."
"As a mirror I am born"
"I become everything I see."
"The joy of a kitten's
caress on my feet"
"Is a life enough for me."
"I want to stroke, everything I
come across, beautifully!"
"I will always be myself."
"Every day I will
live to the fullest"
"Will object, a life
of conventions."
"I will live a life
of supreme essence!!!"
"I will become as
pure as possible."
"With the wind flies the Hawk."
"Beautifully, without a path."
"It being its own reality."
"Like the rock that goes to
the depth of the waters"
"With a renouncing of sound"
"I drown in the sights I see."
"Like the bird that rides
on the bull's hump"
"I will live upon the Earth."
"I would join hands,
and walk along with the Earth."
"Some kind of ecstasy is flowing"
"That provides depth!!!"
"This moment envelops like a mother"
"Singing a lullaby"
"After reaching the shore"
"I love the sea."
"After the hair greys"
"I understand the world."
"Yesterday's joys come together"
"Today, at this moment
they find meaning."
"Today's joys will
come together"
"To find their meaning tomorrow."
(Priest's chants)
Come.
Come, all of you.
Good morning
Greetings.
Greetings sir.
What's the time?
8:59 am.
9 to 6, in 36 frames, we are going to
click photographs in your digital camera.
No preview.
No deleting, if you find a mistake.
We need to know
what's your mistake.
9 to 6, no one should to talk to each
other, no chatting, no whatsapping.
Okay, sir
Every frame that you capture
should be one that you admired...
and not what you took
to impress others.
- Hey ! call out!
- Focus!
I got it sir, I got it.
Sir...
Good
Only photography, possess
the quality to freeze time.
Prabha, in that photo of
mine which you clicked...
whenever I see it,
I will be 37 only.
So make it count
Leave the moment
Sir, one selfie with you
A selfie with me itself is it?
Hey! Don't overlap.
Does anyone know how to drive?
I have not had enough sleep.
Sir, I know
I can drive.
Are you sure?
Okay be ready tomorrow morning.
Okay, sir
Hey!
I will wake up in the
middle and check
If you cross 100km, you had it!
- Okay, sir.
- Got it?
Listen! If you feel sleepy, do tell.
Don't just go bang it. Okay!
Thanks
Thanjavur sir.
You were fast asleep sir.
That's why I did
not wake you up.
Some problem in Kollidam bridge.
That's why we have to go through
Thanjavur and then Trichy.
Google maps are on.
Go straight.
Google says left.
Don't listen to that.
Listen to me.
Go straight.
Okay, sir
Roll the window down.
Now just smell the air outside.
So, how is it,
the air of my native?
This is your native sir?
This is where I was
born and brought up.
My native!
See that's the old bus stand.
After my parents got married, this is
where, they first came and got down.
Look there.
That's the government hospital.
That's where I was born.
Look there, can you see that?
That's Oriental towers.
The first shopping
complex in our town.
Here on the right side.
Raju's bakery.
Even after you have eaten well,
your mouth will water
Egg puff!!!
Can you see a hospital there?
Next to that, was
where my house used to be.
I myself, am not able
to recognize the place.
Should I stop here, sir?
No...no, If someone sees me,
I will have to talk.
Do you know what that is?
- The Big Temple.
- Yes, who built it?
Raja Raja Cholan.
Hey, that...
What happened sir?
Can you go in full speed, and stop
in front of him and scare him?
Now watch.
Go
Go...go
Enough...enough.
Good morning, officer
K.Ramachandran.
Hey! Little one!!!
It's you is it!
No wonder!
I was thinking, who has so much guts
to come and run the car over me.
Are you fine?
What is this,
you started off well no
Why you suddenly
giving me respect?
You better go back to
calling me like old times!
You still haven't stopped charming
people with your laughter!
Come let's go drink tea.
How come your here?
Because...
I am going on asking you,
and your looking elsewhere.
Uncle! Shall I just go and
take a look around school?
Oh! no! that's very difficult!
That's not possible.
First you have to get the
principal's permission.
Then you have to get the
signature of your parents.
Are you serious?
Hey! What is this unusual question?
This is your school.
Go and see it.
K.Ramachandran.
That's me!
When did you come?
Just now.
Just take that stone little one.
I just, got carried away
by the old memories.
I took out,
without breaking it.
Thank you
You remember,
your friend, who stuck to you.
From philomina nagar
- Are you still in touch with him?
- No
Because of work
There's just no time.
This is a photograph
of the school , is it?
Hello!
I am All Saint's School,
watchman speaking.
Oh! Protector!
How are you?
Murali here
Murali, how are you?
I am your protector only speaking!
I am fine
We were just talking about you.
Ram just dialed your
number.
What about you?
Am fine darling.
How are you?
Everything will happen only
according to one's fate .
Just concentrate on your work.
Little one, Murali wants
to talk to you.
Hey! Savage!
What are you doing there?
Actually, I don't know.
What sort of answer is this.
How's school?
Dude...!
Is it still the same or
have they rebuilt it?
Dude! It's just like before.
Same building, same table,
same chair, same protector!
Hey! Let's do a video call!
What rubbish!
what's keeping you so busy?
Come here and see it.
Hey! call please!
Dude! This is a feeling.
Come and see it live!
Isn't it around 10 to 15
years since we passed out?
- Excuse me!
- School is exactly the
What you saying 10 to 15 years?
Fat hopes, one whack,
I will give you.
You and me completed
school in'96
Now it's 2016.
Do you know subtraction,
or should I do it?
Hey! Twenty years,
has gone by is it?
Holy smokes!
Didn't even realize it.
Yes, dude! We have grown older.
Now why you reminding me about that.
At least who have seen
a lot of places
I haven't stepped
outside Tamil Nadu.
Okay, let that be, we have a
lot left to experience, dude!
I will prepare the list,
when are you coming to Chennai?
Okay listen to me carefully.
I am coming from Thanjavur.
After I reach, I will
come and see you.
I have to write it in water,
your empty promises.
Okay, what's with the
sudden visit to Thanjavur?
I will come and tell
you about that.
Do you have any of
our friends numbers?
I want to call and talk to them.
Hey! Crazy brother!
It will take ages, to get
everyone's numbers and talk to them
Then?
Why you worried, we have the
useless, school whatsapp group!
Who do you think is
the admin for that?
Who else! It's you dude.
Even in school you were the one.
Now, no one can beat you to it.
- Hey! say that when you among people.
- Okay dude.
Now I will add you to the group.
Thanks, dude.
Welcome back to school
Mr. K.Ramachandran.
May I come in, please?
Hi, you late comer.
Hi, friends
Dude!!!
Hi, Ram
Hello! Photographer
The Lion has entered the arena!
Oh! look who has joined!
Hey Savage, where were
you all these days?
No matter what, a hero is
a hero, a comedian is a comedian!
No one bothered
when I was added to the group.
You're not on any social network
How come you came onto the group?
I had gone to our
school this morning
After I saw our classroom and our playground
I just felt like talking to all of you.
Now I feel like
seeing all of you.
Hey! Ram! Even feel
like seeing you.
The groom himself has spoken.
We are definitely meeting.
As a Ram say
we all should meet our sometimes
Hey! now you want to see all of us
Is it not?
Here, take a look !
Hey Ram
Post a current photo of yours
Let's see how you look.
Hey! handsome!
Cannot recognize you at all.
As though we are all
growing younger
That's why he wants
to see everyone.
Admin is typing
Then definitely there will
be some important message.
I'm waiting
We are the'96'batch
It's been 20 years
since we passed out
I feel it would be great
if we have a reunion.
Everyone will get an opportunity
to see each other as well.
Super idea
I vote
Awesome dude!
After all I am the class leader!!!
Superb idea!
Oh! now I have to say something!
Hey Murali!
You're too cool!
Hey!
Since all of us are online,
let's fix the place also now!
Thanjavur?
Then why not at Thiruvarur
Nonsense
Are we conducting
a classical music concert!
Look, just a few of you are in Thanjavur
Most of us are in Chennai
The rest have ran away
to US, UK, Australia
Then is Chennai, fine?
Super
Chennai is fine.
That will be easy for everyone.
Then, when?
That's what matters
Carefully plan that.
Half the people will promise
to come, later on ditch us.
Definitely keep it
during a weekend.
We can also try during the holidays.
What's the date today?
Jan 7th.
Two months from today
is our reunion!!!
That would be March 7th!
In Chennai!
All of you better be there.
Double okay
Those who don't come
will die puking blood
You rocked it dude!
Ram we should thank
you for this!
Long live K. Ramachandran.
So, cool, everything
got fixed so fast!
Hey! someone tell my wife.
If I ask, she won't let me come.
Can we bring the kids?
It would be very difficult
to leave them and come.
Please come us family
This is the first time you guys have done
something meaningful after starting the group
'Two months later'
I don't think
I can make it
I really miss you
Hi, what's app dude
how are you doing?
Hello my friends,
I know you will be annoyed
if I speak in English like this.
That's Vinoth.
Hi!
- Hi!
How are you?
- It's been a long time.
- I'm fine.
How are you?
Idiot.
I told you, take the left at the
temple and then the second right,...
you have done the opposite.
Hey! I don't know all that
Come back to the temple,
I can only direct from there.
Hang up! hang up!
Dude!!!!!
Are you fine?
Come! Come!
Hey! why hasn't he come yet?
Trusting he would come,
I have ordered extra food.
I had called him thrice.
The third time I called him, he
said he will come and hit me...
if I call him again and hung up.
In spite of that I
called him again
Wonder what he is going
to come and do to me.
Hey is this Gulab Jamun?
No, red bricks,
you want to eat?
He has posted a poetry
about that girl on Facebook!
- Is that so?
- What had he posted?
Geetha
Tell me...tell me
Hey! hold his hand.
Geetha, give me the key to
open the door to your heart?
Hey!
Dude!!!
Wait...wait
Hey carry him!
Hey! leave me
I've grown old!
"If my friend asks for my life,
I will say take it!!"
Hey! with whose
permission did you kiss me?
Okay
Now go meet your darling sister,
before she gets wild.
I can sense someone boiling
Yeah right
You promised to come and see
me the next day itself!
My dear niece, your uncle has come!
Niece?
What if this one's also a boy?
Won't you accept it?
No way! I want a girl.
I have named her Iniyaval.
It's a done deal.
Okay, my darling!
Even she agrees!
Okay it's going to be a girl.
Now you eat the sweet.
Hi Sathish, how are you?
Now come and talk properly
After you are married and have kids.
When I used to come then and talk,
all of you, would ignore me.
Sir, you don't worry
she is very good girl
She's a very helpful girl.
During exams, she used to
help us copy.
Is it not guys?
Yes! Yes!
- Do you know where Saravanan is now?
- Where?
What kind of photographs are these?
Can hardly see the faces,
in the dim light.
Horrible!
And you call yourself a photographer!
Hey! has everyone come?
We have to order food.
Four of them are yet to come.
Three of them
have been given directions.
Then, what about the fourth?
Huh?
Who is the fourth?
Why you blinking?
Huh!
Hello!
Come on say it!
Why is he acting so weird?
Janu!
"The fragrance of a flower
is that a melody?"
"What blossoms in a young woman's heart
is that a rhythm?"
"Heart's desires are like
the varieties in flowers."
"A bird's song and it's vibes"
"Is the dawn's welcome."
'For us Janu always meant singing,'
'But for her, singing was everything!'
'She used to either sing
or talk about that song.'
'Like the pitch, rhythm, tempo, etc'
'We never understood anything.'
Hey! wait even I am coming.
'Apparently, when Janu was in
her mother's womb itself'
'They had decided to name the
baby, after famous singers,'
'SP. Balasubramaniam if a
boy and S.Janaki if a girl.'
'Such was their family's affinity
towards music.'
'Wonder, what it was about that day,
they named her Janaki Devi'
'She never sang any other
songs, other than that of S.Janaki.'
'Except one!!!'
In all directions,
echoed the tamilian pride!!!
Hail!!! The Tamilian!!!
'Sometimes while listening
to certain songs on the radio'
'It sounded like Janu's
songs being sung.'
'Her voice her face is what,
used to come to my mind.'
'So it wasn't just her singing'
'I was fond of Janu, herself!'
'Even she knew that.'
'That was the only reason why
my attendance was a 90%'
'She was the reason.'
'We have literally been studying
together from our kindergarten days.'
'From then till today, I always
listen to whatever she says!'
'Even she used to ask only me,
if she wanted anything.'
'There were days I used
to be sad,...'
'mulling over my poor marks
and other things.'
'No one else would have noticed,
but Janu would come to me,'
'and just ask, what happened?'
'That was enough!'
'That one word had
the power of ten elephants.'
'It set my heartbeat racing!!!'
'Spirited enough to go bash up
a bunch of harmless guys.'
'I really can't explain
what Janu meant to me'
'The only thing I would pray for,
when I go to the temple is'
'God!'
'Always keep Janu
within my eyesight!'
- Hemalatha
- Present Miss
- Jumshek
Janaki
Janaki Devi
Absent Miss
- Jai Ganesh
- Present Miss
- Murali
- S.Nityanadanam
- Present Miss
- Nanda Gopal
- Raj Mohan
- Present Miss
- K.Ramachandran
- Sathish
- Present Miss
- V.Selvam
- Subashini
- Present Miss
Today we are going to
see about cell biology
Cell means small
It can basically,
functionally, biologically
Also known as,
living organisms
Why, you are looking so grumpy?
Mr.
Hello, Mr...
I am asking you only.
Janu has not come.
Don't know why.
'FRIDAY'
- Hemalatha
- Present Miss
- Jumshek
Janaki Devi
S.Janaki Devi
What happen to her?
I don't know, Miss
Sit
- Murali
- Present Miss
- Nityanadanam
- Nanda Gopal
- Present Miss
K.Ramachandran
Present Miss
Shall I put Physically present?
Always day dreaming
Sit
- Sathish
- Present Miss
- V.Selvam
- Subashini
- Present Miss
What did I do?
Call her.
Hey! hey
Today we are going to see
respiratory system
Respiratory system is...
Hey! call Subha.
(Indistinct chatter)
Your brother is calling you.
What?
Where is Janu?
I don't know.
I will kick you.
Kick me? You think my hands
will be plucking flowers is it?
You're the one who is always
with her, don't you know?!
I don't know.
How will only I know?!
Even I am always
with you, is it not?
I don't even know
where her house is.
Okay, you pay attention to the class.
If she catches us,
she will yell!
OH! MY! GOD!
He knows where Janu's house is.
It is somewhere close by,
near Kaveri super market.
It seems there will be a name
board 'Sukumar', outside her house.
Somewhere here only
Brother! Shall we leave now?
It's getting dark
If we get later than this,
mom will kill me.
Anyway she will definitely
come to school on Monday.
What happened?
Hmm
Why so late?
Special class.
"Oh! Darling"
"I will never let you go!"
"Whatever happens I won't
let my shyness go."
"It can rain nonstop."
'SATURDAY'
'SUNDAY'
I told you
It was enough.
'MONDAY'
Hey!!!
Go inside
You rascal!
Hey! Janu has come.
'I was seeing Janu after 4 to 5 days
and she was sick too.'
'If I was the same person
as I used to be'
'I would have run up to her and would
have enquired about her health.'
What happened Janu?
'That day I just couldn't move'
'Something stopped me!'
Now you alright?
'Everyone was enquiring about
her health, except me.'
All of you go your place
'I wanted to run towards her,
hold her hand and ask,'
'why did you not come
all these days,'
'and how I suffered in your absence.'
'But I somehow couldn't.'
You are having high fever.
Why did you come to school?
'Miss, I am better now.'
You should have taken rest at home.
- Subha take care of her.
- Yes Miss
All of you take you class work
'At that time I did not know how
to explain what that meant.'
'But as far I could understand,'
'that was the first love
of our class!!!'
'I could not figure out
what was happening within me.'
'But I was over flowing
with happiness inside me.'
'My heart was jumping with joy!!!'
'It made me twist my
invisible moustache.'
'After that I could never
converse normally with, Janu.'
'I felt shy and awkward.'
'The minute I saw her,
I began to hide.'
'I couldn't stop myself from
telling Subha about this.'
'Then onwards it was all about,
just eye contact.'
'I thought no one would find out.'
'But somehow Sathish found out.'
Hey ! from when is this going on?
'If Sathish has come to know
Murali will also get to know it.'
You guys have hidden it from me.
What?
With your thoughts elsewhere,
don't neglect your studies.
You should study well, okay?
Do you want to ask me anything?
Are you scared?
Okay, shall I leave now.
What happened?
Did he say something?
- Did you say something?
- No.
Why are all of you
making so much of noise?
Janu, you come here.
Ask her to sing
'By the banks of the river Yamuna'.
Janu.
He is requesting you to sing
'By the banks of the river Yamuna'.
"I am a small girl, I am a flower."
"I am a lotus,
I am a new honey bowl."
"I am jaggery, I am a silver chariot."
"I am a calf,
I am the fresh rainy season."
Hey! I told her. She's
doing this on purpose.
He's asking you to sing
'By the banks of the river Yamuna'.
Sister, he has taken my geometry box and
wants you to sing some song.
I don't understand what is
so special about that song.
He's asking you so many times
to sing that song,
what are you going to lose?
Janu, a fan request?
By the banks of the river Yamuna
from the film 'Thalapathy'.
Please sing, the song
Mr Messenger
Please go tell Mr Fan, that
even on 'All India Radio',
songs are played,
only when directly requested by the fan.
Okay!
Murali!
Is it okay?
Now watch the fun!
"The eyes that spill
poetry, shut !"
"The feet sing a colourful song!"
"In Lord Kannan's chariot with desire!"
"Yearning drowns in blissful toddy!"
"In love"
"Inside the love nest"
"the love bird caresses!"
'After that,
I tried so many different methods,'
'asking her,
but she never sang that song.'
'Stubborn donkey!'
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Have some chocolates.
Did you go to the temple?
Yes, I went in the morning itself.
Where is your brother?
Wait! wait!
Where did you buy your dress?
Maharaja stores?
No, from Kurunji stores.
Dad's choice.
Okay
Now turn.
Have a chocolate.
Take another one.
No, it's okay.
You have grown like a buffalo
How will one be enough for you?
Take another one.
Hey! don't let him go.
He will hit me!!!
Thank you.
Thank you, is that it?
What is the occasion today?
Won't you wish me?
Happy...happy
Happy what?
Happy Diwali is it?
Happy birthday
Thanks
Why you sweating so much?
What did anyone do to you now?
Leave me.
Hey! my brother's a sportsman,
that's why he's sweating.
Is it not?
What happened?
Hey! why is your heart
beating so fast?
What happened?
Just keep your hands
and check for yourself.
Hey! brother!
Hold him! hold him!
You go get water.
Hey! get up!
'Subha couldn't understand, why I was so
fascinated by Janu, that I fainted.'
Shame on you, to faint
in front of a girl.
Disgraceful!
Get up!
'Janu couldn't understand,
what she had done,'
'for someone, to be so
madly in love with her!!!'
'But, I K.Ramachandran
of the 10th standard,'
'had no such confusion, even
in that exhausted state.'
'Like a straight line
drawn with a scale,'
'my focus was only on Janu.'
'If I get married to Janu, you
know what her name will be?'
'Janaki. Ramachandran.'
Janu
'Everything was moving
along smoothly.'
- Miss...Please...don't do this.
- Come here.
Please don't do this...
How dare you copy!
Sorry, Miss
Mr. Ramachandran, so our
holidays start from tomorrow.
I wonder, how you're going to
stay without seeing me for two months.
- Hey Janu ! come fast!
- What is this Subha...
Still addressing her by her name
You have all the rights to address her
as your sister-in-law!!!
Okay! I know what is what.
Now you come and take your cycle out.
Come fast.
Okay then, I will leave now.
Don't forget me.
Happy holidays
How do you know she's coming?
I have been incessantly messaging and
calling her for the past one week.
Not a single reply from her.
I got annoyed and
stopped calling her.
Then?
Suddenly she texted this
morning, saying, she's coming.
- You didn't even tell me this
- Hey...
It's not like I did
not want to tell you
She's got to come all
the way from Singapore.
Thought I'd just wait
till she reaches here.
Come here.
Look at him,
still behaving like a 10th standard kid.
Only thing missing is the school uniform.
Come here, or else I
will break your hand.
Dude, like you're a saint.
Hey! Janu has come.
Hey Janu, how are you?
Here take this and share
it with everyone.
Yeah, say thank you
Thank you
Hey! Subha has come, go see her.
What dude?
Sorry got a little delayed.
Thank God!
You at least came now.
This itself is a relief.
Come.
Finally I've come,
you happy now.
How are you?
I am fine.
- How are you?
- Come, sit.
I am fine.
How many months now?
7 months.
This is my second one.
I never expected so
many of them to come.
All your doing is it?
Everyone did their bit.
Don't even ask.
Even I never expected.
I thought they would just nod in
agreement, and then ditch us.
Thank God, I had organized
some extra food.
Everyone has come.
He has had so many
ice creams from the time we came.
Hey! just ask him how many...
Go
I never thought you would come.
Hey! buffalo!
Hey! why you behaving like a kid?
Standing here with a balloon.
Come.
You go.
You come.
Janu has come.
You come now.
You go.
Go.
- Hey! shut up and come.
- Hey! you go.
Hey! I have grown older!
And you're hitting me like,
you used to in school.
Leave now or...just leave.
Get lost, you savage!
Get lost!
Last summer we were in Singapore,
my husband and son.
If I had known you were there, I would
have definitely come and met you.
Do you have a photograph
of your daughter?
Show me...
Hey! where is he?
If I call him, he's hitting me,
you go call him, yourself.
Hey! what is this..
What happened?
Hmm...
Ram has come.
He is hiding over there.
Hey, Janu
- Hi
How are you?
- I am fine.
- How are you?
- Hi, Janu
You didn't respond to my greeting
Sorry...sorry
How was the Vaitheeswaran temple?
It was nice.
Good morning, Miss
- Aasai Thambi
- Present Miss
- Anbu Selvan
- Anu Radha
- Present Miss
- Aravindan
- Arun Kumar
- Present Miss
- Bhavani
- Bala Murugan
- Present Miss
- Devanadan
- Janaki Devi
- Present Miss
- Jai Ganesh
- Karuppaswamy
- Present Miss
- Murali
- Nandhani
- Present Miss
- Priyadharshini
- Raj Mohan
- Present Miss
- Rajesh Kanna
- Sathish
- Present Miss
- Selvam
- Shyam Sunder
- Present Miss
- Sowmiya
- Subashini
- Present Miss
- Udhaya Shankar
Miss, you never called out
K.Ramachandran's name.
His name is not in the register.
Maybe he is in some other department.
Check it during the interval.
He's not here also.
I thought he would
be in your class.
K.Ramachandran
He has taken his
Transfer Certificate.
Did you not know?
Why would he have taken the
Transfer Certificate?
Hey! you call him your
brother, don't you know?
I promise I don't know anything.
I came back from Kumbakonam
only this morning.
Why, without telling us?
Just can't understand
Hey! nothing to worry!
Let's go to his house in the evening,
Then everything will be clear.
Brother!
What you doing there? It's locked.
Ram?
What?
Krishnamoorthy uncle!
Isn't there anyone in the house?
Krishnamoorthy is it?
How do I tell you that!
Apparently his dad was
in a lot of debt and...
wasn't able to return the money.
So they had to sell the house.
It was built by his grandfather.
So, they did not
want anyone to know.
That's why, they packed their bags
over night and left to Chennai.
No one knows anything else.
Really sad, even he and his mother came
to know about it only that night.
"Why..."
"Did he leave without
saying anything?"
"Why..."
"Did he not close
yesterday's chapter?"
"In the Grey skies..."
"I search for my clouds."
"The time is like a riddle,"
"My path is filled with tears."
"Far away it has gone..."
"The music of love."
"Every tear that drops,"
"Is my prayer in search."
"He left the town I heard"
"My eyes looked here and there."
"He left my very roots I realized"
"That truth caused mayhem within!"
"The music was over."
"Where is your silence?"
"The burden of tears are becoming
my eternal companion."
"Tomorrow seems to burn."
"Where is my morning?"
"Wings are filled with rocks."
"Till I die on the ground."
Ram
Hi
You recognize me?
Janu.
How are you Ram?
I am fine.
How are you?
This is unbelievable, right?
That we would meet like this.
It's been 20 years.
No actually 22 years.
I can't recognize you at all.
When we saw each other
the last time,
you did not even
have a moustache.
What are you doing now Ram?
Travel...
Travel photographer
- What happen?
- I am ok.
You keep quiet.
Hey! I left the kid
with you for 5 minutes,
and look what you did.
Thanks
You want anything else?
You sit down.
- First you drink the water.
- Ok I will drink.
You're ok?
She's come after so many years
and this is what you do!
I slipped and fell.
Did he say anything to you
or the minute he saw you...
Sorry
She has come all the
way from Singapore.
Can't you enquire about her?
Instead of behaving like a kid.
She's married and has a daughter.
Did you ask her about all that?
You're a real moron!
Have you all eaten?
Why have you not eaten?
Normally I don't eat
anything on flights.
Is it?
Hey nutcase! Go run and
touch that tree and get back.
- Go!
- Why?
Okay.
Hello! Is it Dubai?
If you come back fast, run again.
Okay
Hey! What is this?
This is not right
am warning you
My dear sister in law,
is this a bribe for me or is it for...
My man's sister, take a walk slowly and
go touch that tree and come back.
Go.
Thank you
- You, not eating?
- No, you eat.
Phone
Hey! Answer the call.
Sir, yes, tell me sir.
Hey! What is this?
They seem to be heading somewhere else.
Yes sir.
Even I noticed sir.
Looks like they have picked up,
from where they left, at school.
Yes sir, even I feel the same sir.
Hope it doesn't
cause any problem.
We come imagining one thing
and something else happens.
Nothing like that will happen sir.
You don't worry.
You haven't eaten.
Finish this.
Thanks
- Hey!
- Hmm...
What is happening there!
How would I know?
Nothing wrong will happen, no?
- I am not thinking about that.
- Then?
If something, happens
between these two here,
and her husband back in
Singapore get's to know...
If both of us being
the organizers, get caught
Then it will be a real
celebration for us!
You shut up!
I thank all of you,
who have come.
I have something to say,
to those who have not come,
you have missed a
beautiful opportunity in life.
We don't know when and where, something
like this will happen again.
Finally on behalf of 'The All
Saint's School', batch of'96,
I invite our class favourite, Janu,
on to the stage to say a few words.
Our golden girl!
Our kind hearted lioness!
Our Singapore, Princess!
Thanjavur's dancing doll!
We are all slaves to your songs!
Your walk is like a
chariot in procession!
When you talk it's poetry!
Janu, you speak my darling!
Hey! You keep quiet!
I'm so happy
I feel I have
become half my age.
I came thinking everything
and everyone would have changed.
But nothing has changed.
I feel like wearing my
blue and white uniform,
and go to school with
all of you again.
Thanks
Hey Janu!
Sing a song
before you leave.
I just had an ice cream.
That's okay.
Just sing, no one's giving you a prize.
Hey Murali!
Ask her to sing
'By the Banks of the river Yamuna...'
How can I?
Please...Please...
Ask her to sing,
'By the Banks of the river Yamuna'
"Without anyone saying anything
Flowers still emit fragrance."
"Without any bond
Two hearts are speaking."
"Without anyone saying anything
The bird's song oozes honey."
"Without anything
The heart tastes, as sweet as ever!"
"The water cascades through
And the world moves similarly."
"Everything runs by
Similarly time passes by."
"What doesn't stay still
Are the colours of the mind!"
One
Two
Three
Hey! Anyone's got a handkerchief?
Here it
Okay, ready
Hey! look here.
Did you see our protector?
Hey! I am asking you,
did you see our protector?
When are you coming back
again from Singapore?
It will take some time.
- Have you been there?
- No I haven't.
I like your hair
I like yours too
You know, with what great difficulty,
I got permission for this place?
It's really expensive!
These Chinese bulbs are expensive
too, you get them only in China.
These caterers...
My head is aching.
Get me a coffee on the way.
Shall we leave,
the car has come.
Let's go.
How long you staying in India?
Not staying, tomorrow early
morning is my flight.
What's the hurry?
In the last minute I did
not even get a ticket.
Only got a connecting flight.
Have to go to Trichy and board.
You could have planned
to stay for 4 or 5 days.
Even I feel the same now.
Then what, stay and go.
I have left my daughter and come.
She won't be without me.
- What's her name?
- Meera.
Here take a look.
Hey! show me.
She looks very cute.
It was taken there is it?
Should visit these places
at least once before I die.
Here.
Hey Janu! he's checking out your
daughter, in front of you.
Does she look like me,
during our school days?
Everyone says that.
This is why brother,
you should get married
at the right time.
That's why you're still
looking at school kids.
He still is not married?
Nope
Who will give their daughter's
hand to a wanderer!
Why you still not married?
That is...
Because...
Dad's looking for a girl for me.
Hey Ram! Take the car out.
We will come.
Okay! Okay!
Finish your coffee.
I'll wait in the car.
Hey! You finished your coffee?
Your headache has gone?
Then get up.
It's getting late. Give that.
Come
I am asking you...
What's his problem?
Hey!
- All of you are with him, is it not?
- Hey! I messed up is it!
I am going on asking all of you.
One by one you guys are just
getting up and leaving.
You're always with
him, is it not?
- Dad...
- What dad?
Sathish, am asking you
Why is he not married yet?
Since you're going with them
You drop her first
and then you get dropped.
What are you seeing there?
Don't think too much.
Go.
'Intermission'
Hey!
Which route are you taking?
Don't you have to drop Janu, first?
No, first I will drop you.
- Hey! That's a very long route.
- No, who told you, that's only shorter.
Yeah right! Adayar is closer
to Valasarawakkam and...
far from St Thomas Mount is it?
Nonsense!
Shall I check Google
maps and tell you.
No use,
the routes he takes never
appear on the maps.
Hey! Were you serious
or were you joking!
I was serious only.
Careful.
Okay, bye
Am warning you, go drop
her right now, and get home!
- Understood?
- Don't have unnecessary thoughts.
Just a few words,
till I drop her, that's it.
Don't you know me.
Get lost!
Look at you and your white teeth.
Stop grinning like an idiot.
Bye
See you
Be careful.
Will let you know once
the baby is born.
Sure, do let me know.
Keep in touch.
Okay.
- Bye, take care
- Bye
Janu...
So you will talk to me, only
if Subha is not around?
Ram.
Why are you
still not married?
What's the hurry! I'll, slowly...
Ram
Am seriously asking you.
Why haven't you married as yet?
Let's say no one came forward.
I am begging you Ram, please tell me.
Even if it's because of me
it's okay,
just tell me.
I need to know.
Tell me, why haven't
you married as yet?
Ram.
Are you going to
tell me now or no?
Janu, we have
reached your hotel.
Ram, are you going
to drop me now?
No...no...
Subha told me to...
Don't you feel like
talking to me at all ?
No... no..nothing like that.
I will pick you up in the morning
and drop you at the airport.
Take my number.
Janu, am not purposely...
"Beautiful memories are becoming bitter."
"Won't my distances ever vanish?"
"Yearnings of my soul
are tearing me apart!"
"Won't the past ever return?"
"Looking and yet not looking"
"Will my heart, forever live like that?"
"The cowardice of words are like..."
"The harp without a melody."
"Beautiful memories are becoming bitter."
"Won't my distances ever vanish?"
"Within the principles of love..."
"The rules are changing..."
"Emotions are taking over!!!"
"My burdens are
disappearing into thin air."
"The destination seems to
have a hundred paths..."
"To become one with you!!!"
"Shall I bask as the
moon of your love?"
"To be cheated in the break of dawn?"
"In this glorious night, come and live..."
"Hoping the dawn that
breaks is ours my love!!!"
What is it, Janu?
Ram...
Have you left?
Tell me Janu, you need anything?
No, where are you?
Janu?
Have you gone too far?...
Have you gone too far, Ram?
I've been standing right
where I left you!!!
Is it wrong, that I
wanted to talk to you?
Sorry
22 years!!!...
Hey!
Thanks
Janu...
Now tell me, where
do you want to go?
- Yes Subha?
- Where are you?
- Near Guindy.
- Have you dropped her?
Yes. Dropped her
and am on my way.
Did she say anything?
Not really, as she was just
enquiring about my parents,
we reached the hotel,
I dropped her and left.
Oh! Okay.
Alright! you don't keep thinking about
anything, go sleep.
I'll call you in the morning.
Hello
Where you?
I... I am in my room.
What time is your flight
tomorrow morning?
5.50 am.
You're going to Trichy and
leaving from there, is it?
Yes, from here to Trichy,
there to Singapore.
Okay, call me after you reach.
- At least text me.
- Okay, sure.
Okay, bye
Now tell me, where shall we go?
Let's go somewhere.
Somewhere...?
I really don't know,
you suggest.
Why you asking me?
How will I know?
Go, anywhere.
In moment of bravado, I asked you out.
Honestly, I've never been anywhere.
You better suggest,
where to go.
Shall we go to a salon?
Salon?
"If you go inside the Nesapakam market,
the road will curve towards the left,"
then it divides into a fork,
take the right there.
Stop intruding,
then how can you hear
what I am saying.
So, after you take the right at the
fork, take the second right,
you will hit a corporation bank.
On the same road,
it's the third house.
If you go ring the bell,
a nice, plump woman, will
come and open the door.
That's the owner's wife.
Yes.
Oh! the water is it?
It will be red in colour.
In Nesapakam, that's how the
colour of the water will be.
If you want crystal clear water,
you have tolook in places like
KK nagar and Valasarawakkam.
- Did you cut your hair anywhere else?
- No!
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
I have an serious issue to deal with now.
- I know him from long back.
- I'll speak later
I know him from long back?
Is that how you would say it!
Shouldn't you say, you know me,
even before your beard blended
with your moustache?
His father used to bring
him here, as a little boy,
and tell me to
cut it really short,
and this one, used to tell
me to keep it long.
When he was new to Madras,
whenever he saw a Thanjavur bus,
he used to come here
and sit with a long face.
Brother!
Crazy boy!
Okay, tell me, how
should I cut his hair?
Like actors, Rajini or Kamal?
Or like Vijay or Ajith or like Surya?
That's why I am asking?
Uncle, cut his hair,
like a 10th standard boy.
I am gone.
Which year?
'94.
Oh! okay!
Oh! '94 is it?
Should I really have to shave my beard?
Where you coming?
It's like a bear, it will
take time to sculpt.
Sit and watch the fun.
- You sit down.
- You turn this side.
You have lost half your weight.
Don't close your eyes.
Okay?
Double okay
Okay you sit.
Let's put two plaits for you.
Oh no! I don't want.
Okay, now leave the shop
I need to close it.
Okay you wait , I'll come now.
- Who did you think she is?
- I am wise enough.
I can understand everything.
- What do you understand?
- I can understand.
That's what, what
do you understand?
Shall we go?
Remove your shirt.
After all you're wearing
a T Shirt inside.
It has sleeves, right?
Then remove it.
No...hmm...
Hey! Just remove it!
See how this looks!
You and your beard and
the worn out shirt!
What?
What Janu?
Hey! hey! hey!
What?!!!
Hey! hey! Janu.
What is it?
Ram
Are you a virgin?
Yuck, is this way to ask, though?
Is it true?
After going to Singapore,
you have become spoilt...
- Let's go now.
- That's alright.
You answer my question.
It's getting late, first
let us leave from here.
- Are you going to tell me or not?
- Hey! hey! hey!
My shirt is getting crushed.
Then answer me.
Thought you can evade all
my questions and escape?
Now what do you want to know?
Whether...
Whatever be it, let's go
talk about it in the car.
Please Janu
Go.
Come, stand here.
Now, tell me.
Okay! Let me spit this out!
First swear on God, and tell the truth.
Janu, one shouldn't swear
about such things.
Liar!
Don't I know about you.
You would have cooked up a story,
by the time you came from there to here.
Swear on me.
Okay, now tell.
Yes! I am a virgin only, Janu.
Holy! Smokes!
You insisted, so I told.
Now just leave it at that.
But why?
Because I have committed to Lord Hanuman.
Now get into the car.
But how...
Now what do you want...
Oh! Now your ego is
getting hurt is it?
Buffalo! Do you know
how old you are?
Please change the topic.
I am feeling very shy.
Okay, leave that.
In all these years, have you
not fallen in love with anyone?
Can't really say that.
I was expecting this.
Finally the truth is coming out.
What?
Girls, will really like guys like you.
How did they miss out?
- Guys, like, me?
- Yes!
What do you mean
by guys, like, me?
Hey! You're this raw, oozing
manhood, kinda guy!
Why? Hasn't anyone told you this?
Okay, enough of smiling,
come to the story.
- There was a girl called Charu.
- Full name?
Charumathi.
She was my junior in college.
Nice girl. Beautiful to look at.
While studying in college, I had
no idea about her feelings.
After college got over,
one day she called on my landline,
and wanted to talk to me.
She said, her parents were
looking out for a groom for her.
I congratulated her on that.
She got angry.
After that she bluntly asked
if I was interested,
so she could talk to her parents.
What did you say?
What to say?
For me to understand what she
was saying itself was...
Okay. What did you say?
What do you expect me to say?
I told her, that am
jobless, penniless, etc.
- Then? Then?
- She was stubborn.
I had no options left.
Finally I told her the truth.
What is that?
I told her about you.
She was silent for a while.
Then she took a deep
breath and left.
After three months, she sent
me her wedding invitation.
Then she called me.
She told, forget what
happened and come for the wedding.
She said she will be
expecting me.
Did you go?
Whatever said and done, I am
someone she liked.
Poor thing.
I did not want to make her feel awkward.
So I did not go.
Back then,
why you left without telling?
Why did you not come to see me again?
Nothing made sense to me.
I couldn't even ask anyone.
Neither could I forget you.
I completely neglected
my studies.
It was a miracle, that
I even passed my 12th.
I got scared my parents
would get me married,
so I completed my degree properly.
Even then, every time I met
any of our school friends...
I used to wait eagerly to see if,
they would say something about you.
If someone like you,
tall and dark passed by,
I would hope, it would be you
and follow them many times,
but in vain.
To add to all this..
my sister eloped
and got married.
Two months after that,
my marriage was fixed.
With the hatred my father was
harboring for my sister.
I could not even, go and
speak to him about anything.
Even if I had spoken,
what could have I told him?
That I was in love with a
guy till the 10th standard,
but I don't know where he is now?
Even on my wedding day...
Something within told me,
you will come for me.
Now if I say all this, it
would sound very dramatic.
Even while I was seated as a bride,
I felt your presence
in the wedding hall.
I thought, just like how
it happens in films.
You would stop the wedding,
and ask for your Janu.
I was hoping you would take me with you.
But, nothing like that happened.
Only my wedding took place.
After that I was heartbroken.
Till date...
whenever heart is heavy...
my only refuge...
is my 10th standard
K.Ramachandran's face.
What happened?
Sir,
it's getting late,
I have to close the gates.
If you take the car out,
I'll close the gates.
Sit down.
Sorry Ram.
These are things I wanted to tell you,
someday when I meet you.
Who else can I share these things with.
That's why I poured
my heart out.
Please don't think I am trying
to make you feel guilty.
Okay?
No...
The fact that I came to your college...
and sent a message, saying that
I wanted to see you,
don't you know any of that?
When did you come?
Don't tell lies, Ram.
I came, Janu.
Don't play the fool, Ram.
Really, did you come?
One minute.
Ask her.
Please could you call Janaki Devi,
second year Bsc computer science.
I need to talk to her.
Is it anything to do with love?
No sister, it's not what you think.
They both have been in
love, ever since school.
There happened to be a
break in the middle...
It's a ladies college, otherwise
we ourselves would have...
We have come all the
way from Madras.
Just inform her, that would do.
Just for this, have come
all the way from Madras?
Yes sister.
We both are classmates.
I feel bad for you guys.
I will help you.
Are you sure there
won't be any trouble?
No nothing will happen sister.
We just want to see her and
talk to her once. That's all.
Please.
What did you say her name was?
S. Janaki.
One minute.
- Do you know her?
- I don't know.
Hey! Just write her
dad's name as well...
Our bad luck,
there could be two Janaki Devis.
You leave.
What did you say your name was?
K. Ramachandran.
Hey! Where are you going?
Janaki Devi?
That's me.
His name...
There is one boy, waiting
outside, to meet you.
What? Are you a
messenger for love?
Are you coming to
college for this?
If you're not interested
in studying, tell me.
I will take you to
the principal and get you,
your Transfer Certificate.
Hey!
Next time you come to me,
carrying such messages...
I will give you one tight slap.
She saw you from there,
and yelled at me badly.
Don't know what the problem is.
Maybe...
If you had spoken to her directly,
things would have
been better, I suppose.
Just do me one more
favour, please.
Just tell her, I will
never trouble her again.
- Let's go.
- Hey!
Why you being hasty?
Let her come out,
we will talk to her directly.
No need.
No, anything could have
happened in these three years.
The least we can do is, to
not trouble her.
Hey, did we come so far,
just for this?
Sorry, I did not
ask you, for your name?
Vasanthi.
Thanks
Get on.
Sir, come this side
- Which room?
- 318, third floor.
Don't come inside.
No...no...no... I won't ...am
standing outside the bedroom.
- Janu are you okay?
- Ram, I did not see you that day.
I...did not see you...
Okay...Okay...
I swear that day, I never saw you.
I never saw you.
Never saw...
- Janaki Devi?
- That's me.
Hmm...his name?
One boy is waiting
outside to see you.
What are you?
A messenger for love?
Are you coming to
college for this?
Once more, you come with
any such messages...
I will give you one tight slap!
If we were not meant
to be together...
then why...
And look at you,
because of me, you're
also in this state...
First of all, how
could I believe,
that you would hate me.
Whatever it was, I should have,
waited and seen you.
I was hasty.
That day, if only that girl had
mentioned your name...
Everything would
have been different!
It's all my fate.
Why should we get to
know the truth now?
What we believed to be the truth,
could have remained the actual truth.
You have also been thinking about me.
I would have never known
that you came to see me.
In this pain, that is soothing.
How come you never said
anything when you were with me,
but out of the blue, decided to
come after three years to say it?
Actually, every day I
used to think of it.
But something will stop me.
That I am not fair skinned like Janu.
I can't sing like Janu.
I used to keep
thinking like that.
That particular day,
I don't know what happened.
I felt like I would die
if I don't tell you.
Some courage within me that
day, like never before.
I travelled, all the way to your college
and was standing there, for you.
I wanted to ask you.
How did you know I was
studying in that college?
What kind of question is this?
Somehow I know.
But how?
After all you were in Madras.
I had different people
for everything.
I used to come to know everything,
that happens to you.
If I felt like seeing you,
I would come to Thanjavur.
I would follow you,
from college back home,
and if I came too close,
I would go hide.
The only thing, that I did not know,
was that you saw someone else and
not me that day and got angry.
Apart from that I know
everything about you.
What do you know?
Let me hear it.
If you say anything wrong...
Your 10th standard marks were 836.
Your 12th standard marks were 990.
Your b'day dress you would
wear it on my b'day!
Your favourite deity is lord Muruga!
You stop singing after I left town.
You wanted to study Tamil Literature,
but your father paid up
for Bsc Computer Science.
You did not eat
for two days because of that.
Your father was never aware of that.
I meant to say, your father
did not know, but I knew.
In 1998 you had typhoid and,
in 2000 you had jaundice.
The timing was so bad, both the,
times was when you had exams.
Remember, when you were in college,
one curly haired loafer was stalking you.
He who was beaten up by someone,
and admitted in hospital,
which also became a police case?
It was me, who had hit him.
I only hit him.
Around that time, apart from me, three
other guys were in love with you.
Then, for your
college annual day,
for the first time you
wore a saree and came.
Dark blue in colour.
You were scared that your
saree may come out and,
at the same time you were blushing,
as though everyone was looking at you.
Do you know how you looked...
Do it once more.
After that I saw you in a
saree only at your wedding.
Deep purple in colour.
Just like you had thought, I had
come for your wedding, Janu!
I was standing in a
corner amidst the crowd.
I just couldn't wait till
the knot was tied.
I ran as far away as possible,
from the wedding hall
and all that noise.
Coffee?
- Come
- Hello, sir
Sorry sir, is it too late?
No, you are right on time.
Leave it.
- Shall I pour, sir?
- No, no, I'll do it.
- Okay sir
- Thanks
Okay Janu, I'll leave.
After you drink, get some sleep.
I'll come at 3.30, you get ready
and come down. Okay.
I want to speak to you about
something, come here.
No...no... whatever it is, you
say it from there.
Nonsense, come and sit down.
It's taken me 22 years to
see this idiotic face.
That too, just for a night.
I should really
thank God for this.
I will do that tomorrow.
Don't tell me to sleep tonight.
I want to be with you.
I want to talk to you.
That's all.
Okay
What?
"Yearnings take shape and touch me..."
"Burning the beauty..."
"Cradling me like a mother!"
"The language of the eyes, follow
a path which leads to the story."
"Yearnings take shape and touch me..."
"Burning the beauty..."
"Cradling me like a mother!"
"The language of the eyes,"
"and the language
of the lips form a never ending story."
"Won't time become a horse at night?"
"Same dream! Same question!"
"Won't the skies caress
and embrace and dance?"
"The same moon, is coming closer."
"Yearnings take shape and touch me..."
"Burning the beauty..."
"Cradling me like a mother!"
"The language of the eyes,"
"and the language of the lips
form a never ending story."
"Am I the fire that gets wet?"
"Are you the raining moon?"
"Will I be extinguished?"
"Am I the waning musical note?"
"Is love just a never ending dream?"
"Is the never ending
journey not enough?"
"Is time a question alone?"
"That is enough."
"My heart melts in longing to come
closer to you."
"Yearnings take shape
and touch me..."
"Burning the beauty..."
"Cradling me like a mother!"
"The language of the eyes,"
"and the language of the lips
form a never ending story."
Oh God!
- What happened?
- My students.
Okay.
So, what?
What?
If they see us together...
Okay, just check if they
are looking this side.
They aren't looking, but
they are leaving now.
But, don't they have to go out this way?
Oh! Yeah!
Okay, I will go and
hide in the bathroom,
will you call me,
after they leave?
Please
Thanks
Sir this is the kitchen.
- Bathroom
- Washroom is there.
Hi, sir
This look, is stunning!
I couldn't recognize
you from there.
I thought it was some young guy.
What are you doing
here at this hour?
Sir it's Abhi's b'day,
so we came to cut cake.
Learn everything properly.
Okay?
Won't your parents, say anything,
you being out at this hour?
All of you have come
alone at this hour?
Go reach home safely.
Sir, is that your wife?
Hey! I never said anything...
I never said anything.
We are Ram sir's students.
I know, he just told me.
Actually, we had no clue
that sir is married.
He never told us.
I never said anything.
Nothing like that.
Because it was a love marriage,
we did not tell anyone.
Love marriage!!! Is it?
Why?
What happened?
We can't believe that he is married even.
And now you're saying
it was a love marriage.
So mean! Why you saying this?
Since, he is so
strict in class.
We can't talk, we can't look at each
other, and we can't even laugh.
Hey! That's enough!
You will go on talking...
Leave...leave...leave now...
- Why you threatening them?
- It's getting late.
Come, all of you come and sit.
Look at him ma'am, even
in front of you...
I will take care of
that, you continue.
- Where did I stop?
- Shouldn't laugh.
Oh yes, we shouldn't laugh...
we shouldn't even wear sleeveless...
Even my father is better than this, ma'am.
Okay, okay...he's like that only.
I will tell him to be more
gentle with girls, okay?
That's alright ma'am, but
how did sir fall in love?
Our love started, way back
from our school days,
from the 10th standard.
School days is it?
Who proposed first, ma'am?
Sir, you're feeling shy?
Ma'am, when did you
accept, the proposal?
The same day, at that
very moment...
at once!!!
What is this ma'am!
For your beauty, you should have
made him, chase you for a week.
That too sir, you could have
kept him waiting for a month.
At that time he meant
everything to me.
Even now!
Please ma'am, tell us
how sir proposed?
We won't ask you anything else,
we will leave.
Birthday wish, please
Tenth standard, went
by very merrily.
I was always smiling.
After that, Ram left to Madras suddenly.
Without even telling me.
All the smiles turned to tears.
Even after I joined college,
I could never forget him.
It used to be very painful.
But something within kept telling me,
my Ram, will come one day.
He will definitely come for me.
Sometimes though nothing
happens around you,
you will still have a gut feeling
that something is going to happen.
That's how I was feeling that day!
Excuse me, just a minute.
2nd year Bsc Computer Science,
S. Janaki Devi,
can you please call her.
I need to talk to her.
Is it about love?
Yes.
Are you sure there
won't be any trouble?
What's your name?
Vasanthi.
Vasanthi, you don't get scared.
Just go tell S. Janaki Devi
of 2nd year Bsc Computer Science,
that K. Ramachandran has come.
Vasanthi, thanks
S.Janaki Devi?
Someone called K.Ramachandran
is waiting for you.
What happened after
that, is something,
which I yearned, that it would happen
in my dreams atleast.
My Ram, had come in search of me.
In one second my
world had changed.
The minute I heard
K.Ramachandran's name,
my entire being shook!
I couldn't even walk,
but, I was running.
"Come to me my entirety!!!"
"You ..."
"Are my seven musical notes..."
"My Five great elements..."
"My heart is brimming!!!"
"Whatever I see..."
"Is love..."
I was seeing him
after three years.
The school boy face had gone.
A Lion of a man, with a beard
and a moustache, was at the gates!!!
For me.
For Janu.
But, I had by hearted
certain questions,
which I desperately wanted to
ask the day I see him.
But...
Janu!
"Love... Love..."
"Is the biggest lonely companion!"
"Come with me...
Come with me..."
"That is more than enough."
"Love... Love..."
"Till the end of life..."
"Lets travel...
Come with me.!!!"
Okay, enough of listening to stories.
It's getting late.
You people should leave.
Leave...leave...leave...
Hey! come here.
Can't you be happy cutting a cake
at 10pm back at home?
Is it a must to come
out and cut at 12pm?
Okay, leave now. Go reach
safely and text me.
- You both look made for each other, sir.
- Shut up! Leave!
Chatter box!
- Hey!
- I will take care. You leave.
You want a special
invitation is it?
Leave!
Good night, Ma'am
Good night, sir
Good night
Leave.
Where next?
If you won't mistake me,
I want to ask you something?
Oooooh! What is it?
Your hotel is far off from here.
Okay.
No, it's alright, let's go.
Stop it, and just say it.
It's just that, the
hotel is far from here,
where as my house is close by.
What did you think about me, Ram?
No...no... sorry...sorry..
I did not mean it
that sense, Janu.
I promise.
That's why I was hesitant
to ask earlier.
Okay let's go to the hotel.
Shall I book a cab?
I promise...
There is this woman who
tries to entice sage Vishwamitra...
What's her name?
Menaka.
Yeah, and with her there
will two more women...
What are their names?
Ramba and Urvashi.
Yeah.
Well, we can entrust you with
those three women,
in those same minimalistic outfits,
for a night!!!
You won't do anything majorly,
in fact, you will take
care of them safely.
That's because I've shaved off
my beard and moustache,
you're feeling that way.
Oh! really... and if
you hadn't shaved?
Even then you will
feel the same.
Okay, let's walk.
How do we go to your house?
Come let's go.
That side. That one.
Hey!
Any girls as neighbours?
Yes there are.
Come in with your right foot.
You're something...
K.Ramachandran's house, is it?
- Oh no! It's become wet.
- That's alright.
The house is nice.
Where is the bathroom?
Go straight and the bedroom is on the left.
You go, I will get a
towel and come.
Janu, shall I leave the soap and
towel here, at a reachable distance?
Why? There is one here.
Oh! no! I have used that one.
Do you have psoriasis
or something?
No...no... nothing like that.
Just dry these.
Ram, I have to
tell you something.
You have to listen.
You shouldn't stay like this.
You should get married.
You should have a
family of your own.
I want see your children.
I want to pet and pamper them.
I want to see if their
eyes have your semblance...
Whether their nose has
your semblance...
I want to see and enjoy all that.
I want to see your wife.
I want to know who your
wife is going to be.
I want to tell her something,
That no women will get
a gem of a guy like you!
So she better take great care of you.
I literally want to warn her.
I definitely will!
You want to eat?
Shall I order something?
Even in the hotel, you
did not eat anything.
Not hungry.
I am hungry.
Is it okay?
It's like my mother's cooking.
Janu, are you happy?
Hmm...
After many years.
Idiot!
I did not mean now.
I was asking, whether you're
generally happy in life?
What is this? You're asking me,
like my mother would.
I just felt like asking.
If you don't want to tell,
don't tell.
It was difficult
in the beginning.
I got caught alone in Singapore.
I won't know what to do,
every day I used to stand
in front of God and cry.
But he's a very nice person.
A very good father
to my daughter.
Without me saying much,
he understands me.
No problem as such.
If you're asking me
if I am happy...
I would say I am peaceful.
But, at this moment
I feel like saying something,
but I won't.
Janu, you don't get up.
Just stay there.
You may stumble upon something.
I will just come now.
"On the banks of the river Yamuna,
as the cool breeze blows..."
"I dance with Lord Kannan..."
"The eyes blossom, looking at the path..."
"Young Radha wilts."
"The night has gone by,
the day has gone by..."
"The King is not with me."
"The young girl's
unblinking eyes..."
"Search, here and there..."
"Lord Kannan is not to be seen
in the cow herding grounds ."
"Falling in love,
is a painful joy."
"Lord Kannan is not to be seen
in the cow herding grounds ."
"Falling in love , is a painful joy."
"Poor Radha!"
What's all this?
Memories!
Wow! That old aroma!
How come you have, kept all
this safely, for so long?
Your's.
Mine?
How did this come to you?
Yeah, it grew legs and came!
I flicked it.
So I can keep it as memory of you.
But how?
You would leave your shawl in class,
when you go for the P.T period.
So, I kept following, planned it...
and one day, flicked it.
This is what I got.
Careful...careful...careful...
Hey!
- Nothing...nothing...nothing...
- Then why you snatching it?
Love letter is it?
No.
Are you kidding me!
Poetry is it?
About me, is it?
Give it to me.
No, Janu...
If you read it,
you will start laughing.
I am feeling shy.
Hey! hey!
Who is going to write
poetry about me?
Only you will write about me.
Okay! You read it yourself.
Read.
Girl, are you a sea full of waves?
My heart yearns, for your next wave!
Does a fish basket and a flower
shop require an advertisement?
Is an attendance register
required to know your arrival?
Apparently we will lose our
eyesight if we see the lightening.
We lose our eyesight
if we see the lightening.
But when I see your eyes
lightning enters me!
If you belong to your mother who
carried you for ten months...
Then you also belong to me, for I have
carried you in my heart for ages!
Ram!
Haven't you slept?
Okay, come up.
Up?
No I always sleep on the floor.
I am comfortable...
Just come up.
Hey!
Tell me your email id...
your height, weight...etc
Why?
- Let's fix a girl, for you today.
- No, don't want.
Why not?
Look here,
after being in love with
a girl like S.Janaki,
I can't marry any other girl.
Why not? I was also in
love with K.Ramachandran,
and did I not marry M.Saravanan.
Everything is possible.
Tell me.
Postbox78@gmail.com
Is it time?
Another 15 minutes to go.
That girl told me something
at the restaurant.
Yes, even I wanted to ask you.
She was whispering
into your ears.
What is it?
She said, sir is a very nice person,
and to take care of him well.
I know very well that
sir's a nice person.
But, she told me to
take care of him well.
I don't know what
to do for that.
Shall we leave?
"The night, like an island..."
"Is circling us..."
"Even the break of dawn
seems like darkness..."
"Memories like fire
are burning inside..."
"The body cries, like it is death!"
"Separation is my bond and I melt in it!"
"I am separating from what
breathes life into me!"
"Like the rivers that
flow from the mountains,"
"You flowed into my heart!"
"In the barren land..."
"You gave birth to a million seas!"
"Let the dream be my only companion!"
"The night, like an island..."
"Is circling us..."
"Even the break of dawn
seems like darkness..."
"This lotus, in spite of being
in the pond , is lonely."
"The sun basks in the warmth
even when it's not day."
"In one path...two souls are
searching for their soul mates..."
"Time is again and again
placing obstacles!"
"Living a life without you,
is that a life at all!"
"Come my life! Life is to live!
you are the life within me...!"
"Shall I come! Shall I come!"
Thank you Ma'am
Hope you have a pleasant stay
"Every single day my
heart comes alive..."
"And dies that very day!"
"Till the end of my life..."
"My heart will celebrate you!"
"Even when trees fall
and nests shatter..."
"Birds still sing
their melody!"
"Even when the night is over
And almost done with..."
"The moon still waits patiently!"
"The rain drops reach the sea!"
"The immortal love will reach Earth!"
"Even when by body is away from you..."
"My love will live with you forever!"
"You take leave..."
What?
Let, me stay with you for
a little more time.
It's already late, Janu.
Please, Ram
Don't look like that.
Okay, hold this.
Where you going?
Okay, wait, will
come and tell you.
I've taken a ticket for myself
on the same flight as yours.
Till you board the flight
I will be with you.
Okay.
If you cry for this...
Wipe your tears.
Walk.
Show me.
Your id?