Drushyam
"The world has changed..
Times have changed.."
"I am with you in
happiness and in sorrow."
"I am with you in happiness and in sorrow."
Ticket! Ticket! Ticket!
"The world has changed.. Times have changed.."
Ticket! Ticket!
Two tickets.
- Don't you have change?
Everybody is carrying
notes of higher denomination.
I'm writing behind the ticket.
Take back the change
while getting off the bus.
Okay? Here you go.
Ticket! Ticket! Have you
taken the ticket? Ticket!
Ticket! Ticket!
Ticket!
Hello.
Yes. I'm still in the bus.
Okay. All right. I'll call
you when I get off the bus.
How far is Rajavaram from here?
It's the next stop.
Are you new to this place?
Yes, I'm a constable.
I got transferred to
Rajavaram Police Station.
Are you a policeman?
Actually, the new police station
was built recently.
That's Rajavaram
Police Station.
Who is it?
I'm the constable who got transferred here.
I'll be reporting from today.
Where did you work before?
- Kothavalasa.
Isn't the
sub-inspector here yet?
He'll come in an hour. Be seated.
- Okay.
Hello.
Rajavaram Police Station.
The sub-inspector
has not come yet, sir.
He has gone for a meeting
with the RDO.
I'll let him know when he comes.
Okay, sir.
Have you come alone?
Don't you have a family?
Isn't he Rambabu?
Yes, yes. That's him.
He looks so innocent.
- He's not that innocent.
All the officers got transferred
because of him.
What about his case?
- It won't be solved that easily.
It's not an ordinary case.
I think Jagdish paid
a hundred bucks extra.
No problem.
I'll add it to my account.
Mr. Rambabu,
today's collection..
Mr. Rambabu!
What is it?
Hey.
- The cars are so fast, sir.
Come on, hit him.
Wow!
- That was amazing, sir.
That was a good chase, wasn't it?
- No. The direction is bad.
He should have taken close shots
of the hero driving the car.
Only then will the audience
be thrilled to watch.
You seem to be really excited,
sir.
Shall I say something serious?
- Yes, tell me.
Why don't you direct a movie, sir?
How about it?
Give me today's collection.
- I have it with me.
Okay.
What is this?
- What to do, sir?
Constable Veerabhadram
made me wait for a month
and didn't pay after that as well.
- What about Ms. Bhagyam's bill?
She watches only one show called 'Abala Avesham'
and so she paid only 20 bucks.
Then give her the cable connection
only during the show time.
No, sir. Let's cut the cable
connection exactly during the show time.
That way she will pay us
but not get to watch the show.
Isn't that a great idea?
- Is it?
It's not that great, sir.
Sir, it's a complaint call.
Let me handle it.
I don't want anybody calling to say
that they don't have a
cable connection, okay?
You don't want the phone
to ring, right? I'll handle it.
So there won't be any cable
connection problems henceforth?
That won't be necessary.
I'll just disconnect the phone.
This is a better solution.
Isn't that a great idea?
Right. Put the phone down.
Come on.
Go now.
Raghu, where have you been?
Sir, I have been out to get milk.
- Okay.
Raghu, one special tea for me.
Sir,
have the police finished eating?
Yes, everybody did,
except that courageous officer.
Are you talking about Veerabhadram?
He's a sly fellow.
They don't know about him
and so they've been waiting
for him since morning.
For what? - They are from
the Lotheru village.
They just have a son who bought seeds by
taking a loan from a finance company.
He paid the interest
in regular installments.
This time, we suffered a
bad year due to heavy rains.
Constable Veerabhadram
took away my son for not paying
the interest since the last two months.
He wants us to pay the principal
amount and the interest together.
What do we do now?
How is Veerabhadram
related to this?
Veerabhadram must have been
bribed by the finance company.
You can go and talk to the
sub-inspector. - No, we can't.
Mr. Veerabhadram said
he would kill our son
if we spoke to
the sub-inspector.
Do something, Rambabu.
It's better that they
drag this case to court.
What's the use of that?
The finance company is getting
all the work done
by Veerabhadram.
There is no evidence to show
that he took away their son.
How can the court take a decision
without any evidence, Rambabu?
Your Honor,
I'm ready to fight this case
on her behalf, if she permits.
I feel that the truth
she is fighting for
has been covered up
by the police
and so I request the court
to issue a search warrant.
Since it's a unique case,
the city's High Court
issued a habeas corpus petition
against G Sathyam.
The court has
ordered the police
to present Sathyam before
the court in 24 hours.
What is a habeas corpus, sir?
I have an idea.
There's a lawyer in Vizag
named Vishwanath.
His assistant is from
this city itself.
I'll talk to him and get
a habeas corpus issued
like it happens in 'Ankuram' film,
and get your son freed.
Will Veerabhadram allow this?
Nobody can do
anything about this.
When a habeas corpus is issued
the police will be forced
to present him before court.
In fact,
that won't be necessary.
It will be enough if we ask
the lawyer to call Veerabhadram
and warn him to release
their son or face
the habeas corpus petition.
Your son will be back home then.
Sir,
Mr. Veerabhadram is approaching.
Veerabhadram is coming.
Rambabu will manage.
Sit inside. - Yes, sir.
- Come on, come on. - Let's go.
Come on, move it.
Come on.
Raghu, bring two plates of 'idly'.
Sir, an old couple was
here. Have you seen them?
Nobody came here.
- Nobody came?
I wonder where they went.
Raghu, bring me two 'dosas'.
- You have to pay for it, sir.
Hey, have I ever paid?
We are not getting paid
because you're not paying us.
Nobody respects the cops
nowadays. Right, sir?
Nothing like that, sir.
The cops are all eating on credit.
Even we need money
to buy the groceries.
Are we the only ones living on credit?
Does Rambabu always pay?
Doesn't he live on credit?
- Of course, I do.
But I clear the
debts every week.
Then I'll clear my debts right away.
How much is it?
It's Rs. 4,500.
- Is that all?
I'll pay right away.
You can deduct the amount I owe you
from the commission that you owe me.
- What commission, sir?
A new police station has been
sanctioned to our district.
It will be built there,
opposite to your hotel.
Once the construction starts
I'll ask all the workers
to eat at your hotel.
What are you laughing at?
This is the only hotel here.
They don't have a choice.
I'll ask them not to eat.
Do you think they'll
go to the city to eat?
I have the capacity
to have another
hotel built here
immediately.
If you listen to Rambabu
and mess with the police
then your business and life will
be ruined like this. Remember that.
Veerabhadram.
- Why are you interfering in our job?
Raghu, one strong tea.
Rambabu, how are you?
I'm fine, sir.
The cops have been gracious.
The citizens don't need gratitude
from the cops, but security.
Sir, there's a new police station
coming up in front of your hotel.
You'll have great business.
We already spoke
about the business
and the commission
that has to be paid.
What commission are
you talking about?
You know about the commission,
don't you?
"The clouds in the sky.."
"Are pouring.."
Yes!
Sir, I designed an advertisement
for 'Guddu Sweet Stall'
and mentioned about the catering.
I want you to see it.
Sir.
- What is it?
Sir, come and see
the advertisement.
Hey, wait.
- What?
Oh, no! This is a tragic song.
Sir, you can watch this Shoban
Babu song tomorrow as well.
Come and see the advertisement,
Mr. Babu.
Okay, I'll come and see it.
- Wipe away your tears. - Okay.
Come, sir. Please come.
- Yes.
How can you be so sentimental?
Wipe away your
tears and see this.
Look at my talent.
How is it?
I think the phone number should
be mentioned in a larger font.
Sir, there is a voice over as well.
People remember what they see,
more than what they hear.
The number has to be larger
for old people to be able to see.
Sir, old people are
never active at weddings.
Why would they call
to order sweets?
Go and answer the phone first.
- It must be a complaint call.
You're always expecting the worst.
We only get complaint calls,
don't we?
My wife might also call.
- Even she calls only to complain.
Shut up and answer the phone.
- All right.
If anybody asks for me, tell
them I'm not here. - Okay, okay.
Hello. Jyothi Cable Network.
How may I help you?
Mr. Rambabu? Okay.
- You talk.
He's not here. Do you want me
to give him a message?
Okay, I'll tell him.
- Who was it?
It was Mr. Sharma.
- Was it a complaint?
It was not a complaint, but a request.
- A request?
He asked me not to cut the cable
connection
while the adult program was going on.
But he can't move
because of leprosy.
Sir, he can still enjoy
adult programs, can't he?
Hey!
- Yes.
Anju. - Yes.
Where's your mother?
- In the kitchen, dad.
Why have you woken up so early?
- I have exams starting today.
Okay, study.
You cook everyday but you still don't learn.
Why don't you
switch off the gas?
That was the second whistle.
There are still many left.
Don't act like you know everything.
- Okay, okay.
Have you kept the water
ready for my bath?
Everything is ready
in the washroom.
Will you come with me?
- Just shut up!
Don't start early
in the morning.
How about this evening then?
- Just go!
That's enough, mom.
You always forget to
switch off the lights.
The electricity
bill is always high.
Isn't our beauty
queen ready yet?
Anu! Anu!
- Coming, mom.
That's good.
- Look how she's trying to flatter dad.
It's not about that. This is her
way of expressing love to him.
Neither do you do it, nor do you
appreciate her doing it.
Was it raining near the cable
office last night? - No, why?
I called many times last night.
Your office telephone gets
disconnected during rains, right?
Dad, why don't you
buy a mobile phone?
There is never a stable network.
What's the use of a mobile phone?
You won't buy even if
there is a stable network.
By the way, you didn't
even ask why I called you up last night.
You would have called to ask me
to buy some groceries on your way home.
Don't taunt me. You just
don't care for any of us.
You just sit at office
and watch movies.
You have a wife and your children
waiting for you at home.
You don't even come home at
night.
You just don't care for us!
Sorry, dear. I do care for you.
Tell me why you called.
Tell me, dear.
We want to go to the city.
- For what? - Shopping.
S-Shopping? - Yes!
I have to buy clothes
for all of us.
What about the clothes
that you bought last year?
I have the clothes that we
bought during our wedding as well.
But I don't think tattered clothes
would look good.
This is why I asked you
to buy some loose clothes.
But you never listen to me.
- Even I asked you
to take me to a good store,
but you didn't listen to that.
You took us to a cheap store which
had a 'Buy One, Get One Free' offer.
I didn't take you to the store.
- It's you who took us to the store, dad.
Okay, we'll buy new clothes. One of my
customers owns a shop nearby. We can go there.
No!
We have to go to Vijayanagaram.
We want to eat 'biryani'
and watch a movie
in an air-conditioned theatre.
Mom, I want an ice-cream as well.
- What?
Yes. Ice-cream. There are a lot of
things that we want to purchase.
Do you have to spend so much now?
- Why are you so upset?
You're never home,
you don't understand our needs.
Even we desire a few things.
Look,
I don't roam around for fun.
It's my profession.
It's your duty to stay at home.
Family must mean the world to a
woman who is a wife and a mother.
She needs to accept it as a
responsibility and not a burden.
It's not enough to be beautiful.
You should also have
an understanding attitude.
You need to learn from Namrata.
- Who is Namrata?
Namrata Shirodkar.
She is Mahesh Babu's wife.
She got married when she was
at the peak of her career.
Though she was 'Miss India' once,
she now manages her family
like a good wife and mother.
You should learn from her.
Do you know what Namrata's
husband, Mahesh Babu, does?
What does he do?
- He earns crores of money.
He provides his wife with all the
facilities like a car, a driver etc.
He also takes them
abroad for shopping.
She's talking as though Mahesh Babu
takes her permission before doing anything.
Mom is telling the truth, dad.
I read it in the weekly magazine, 'Swati'.
Shut up!
Who ordered for that magazine?
Another thing. Do you know
how they went abroad? - How?
In the flight. - That's obvious. You can't
use an auto rickshaw to go abroad.
Your mother might
actually try that.
Dad, when will we travel by a flight?
Let's end this topic here.
Go to school now
and I'll take you shopping later.
Vijayanagaram.
- Okay, fine. Shopping.
Vijayanagaram. Shopping.
Eat now. Else the food will be wasted.
Why are you digging this pit?
- This is to prepare compost.
You should have hired
someone else to do it instead.
Nowadays, workers ask
for a lot of money to work.
Why don't you buy some fertilizers?
Only people like you can think of such things.
- We have to change with the changing times.
You don't know anything about this.
Fertilizers have chemicals which ruin
the crop. This is a safer option.
I thought you watch only movies.
Now I know you watch
agricultural programs as well.
It's not because of television,
but because I'm clever.
I know a lot, and need to learn little.
- Hello! Hello!
That's not the proverb. It is,
'I know a little, and need to learn a lot'.
Even I watch some movies.
I just wanted to help you.
I used my hard earned money
to buy this five acre plot
and worked on it day and night
to transform it from barren land
into this cozy little home for you.
- Come on. Not again.
The children and I have got bored
of listening to this story.
You flatter yourself a lot nowadays.
- It's not flattery.
I might be an orphan but I still have
my self-respect and confidence.
You don't understand that
and hence you taunt me.
You also spend all
my hard-earned money on shopping.
You always make an issue about shopping.
I'm not spending money lavishly.
I only go shopping once or twice a year.
We wouldn't have had clothes if I didn't.
What are you so happy about?
- Come closer.
You said something about not having clothes.
I was imagining that and..
- Shut up! Aren't you ashamed at all?
It was a mistake to even talk to you.
Simhadri. - Yes, sir.
- Why has everybody gathered here?
They're constructing a new police station.
So, I'm checking where to place the antenna.
That will be eight months later.
Get back to work.
Hey, Simhadri. - Sanes Naidu, I'll manage.
I'm going to the office now.
Okay, okay. - All right.
- Who is that?
He is Sanes Naidu.
He's getting married.
I agreed to relay his wedding live
through our cable network.
We don't have the equipment for that.
- Sir, it doesn't matter.
I'll video shoot his wedding
and send the video cassettes.
You can play those cassettes.
People will know that it's not a live stream.
Sir, everybody will
attend his wedding.
Nobody would watch television.
Isn't that a great idea? Appreciate me.
Shut up and get on the bike.
We have a lot of work left. Such an idiot.
The audience gave me more votes because of
the expression I give when I get slapped.
Actor Nagarjuna was hurt
because his expressions were better.
Do you think you're too good?
Dons like you are no match to me.
You're such an idiot!
Why are you slapping me?
You're just acting like a don.
Acting like a don?
- What?
Sir, one strong tea. - Raghu,
bring one strong tea for the contractor.
Rambabu.
He is the contractor who is managing
the construction of the new police station.
You are..
- He is Rambabu.
He provides cable connection
to the residents of this area.
His office is on top of that building.
Rambabu, will you go home for dinner
or stay here?
I already informed Jyothi
that I wouldn't be home for dinner.
I'll sleep in the office tonight.
- Why is that so?
Why do you sleep in the office
when you have a home here?
Rambabu loves movies and he can
watch movies at his office.
Don't you go home at night?
- There's a problem with the cable connection.
People don't pay the bill if they
don't have a cable connection.
So one person has to stay in the office
and take care of the work.
Yes, you're right.
- Okay. See you again.
Sir, I'll come here for dinner.
- Okay.
"I've gone berserk."
"I've gone berserk in your love."
"I long for you all day."
"I feel restless without you."
"My mind is not in place.."
"Without you."
Simhadri.
- Yes.
I'm going home. I have a headache.
- Okay, sir.
He only looks cunning, but is very innocent.
He couldn't guess my true intentions.
Sir, is the bedroom song over?
- What?
He only looks innocent, but is very cunning.
I just have a headache.
Didn't you find any medicine at the office?
- No. Move aside.
What did you watch today?
A bedroom scene or something else?
If you agree, it will be a romantic scene.
- And if I don't?
It will be an assault scene.
Move aside!
There you go.
Hey! Stop it.
You're behaving like a youngster
even at this age. - I'm not old, dear.
I am still a youngster.
- Is it? - Yes!
Shall I ask you something?
- Tell me, dear.
Let's sell the old jeep
and buy a Maruti.
All you women are very clever. You know
our weakness and take advantage of it.
I'm not like everybody else.
I can be in control.
No Maruti!
Don't try to act smart with me.
Okay fine. Let's buy a Maruti.
Come to me now.
- Okay.
Shall I ask you something?
- Tell me, dear.
Let's buy a second hand car.
- No need.
A new one will be very expensive.
- I'll now go out.
Come on, listen to me.
- I don't want to listen.
Okay, let's buy a new car. I watched
a romantic movie.
Try and understand my feelings.
How many times should I ask you
to switch off the lights?
The bill for electricity usage will be high.
I don't want it. - Dad,
did you come home last night?
What? I..
Why? Shouldn't he come home?
We're getting late for school everyday
because of you. Eat quickly.
Why are you scolding me?
Dad never comes home at night.
That's why I asked. Tell me, dad.
Why did you come home last night?
Actually, I came to tell you
that we're buying a new Maruti.
Yes. We're buying a new Maruti.
What? Really, dad?
- Yes, we're buying a Maruti.
Maruti is a bad choice, dad.
- Really?
Anu is a good girl.
Let's buy an Audi.
- Is that more reasonable?
Come on, dad.
It's worth forty lakhs.
- Forty lakhs? Is it made of gold?
That's why you need to read
the newspaper frequently.
I don't read the newspapers only because
I want to avoid reading about such atrocities.
For someone who watches
movies everyday
it's surprising that you
don't know about Audi cars.
I don't pay attention to objects
that are expensive.
That's why I don't know
about Bodi.
It's not 'Bodi', it's 'Audi'.
- Whatever it is.
We're buying a Maruti.
When are we buying it, dad?
Eat quickly.
You're getting late for school.
She'll leave soon. Take bath
and come. I'll serve breakfast.
I don't have the patience
to take bath.
How will you then dig the pit for compost
without patience?
I don't have the stamina to do that.
All my stamina got drained
last night.
What? I mean..
Actually..
I mean, my bike broke down
on the way home last night.
I pushed my bike all the way home
so I'm very tired. Yes.
Mom, I asked you
about the nature camp.
May I please attend the camp?
- I said, no.
Look what mom is saying, dad.
- What's the matter?
All of us are attending
a nature camp
to educate people
not to build commercial complexes
on fertile yield-giving land.
Fifty people were selected
from our state
out of which only two
were from our school.
Why don't you study at home instead
of attending the nature camp?
If you transform all the fields
into commercial complexes
your future generations will have to
live on medicines rather than food.
You may buy anything
with money
but you can never buy food that will
cure you of hunger. Understand one thing.
If the food remains in your body,
you'll become sick.
If children remain in school,
they'll become crazy.
I walk on a unique path.
- Super, dad!
That was amazing.
- Exactly.
Yes, that was amazing. Give her
Rs. 2000 and then she can go.
Rs. 2000? Rs. 2000!
- Dad.
Will this help you in any way?
- Yes.
We'll have to answer questions
about this in the exam.
I'm trying to score the first rank.
- Is the first rank confirmed?
Confirm!
- Okay then.
Haven't you left yet?
- Bye, dad.
You're late for school.
Come on. Go to school.
Have you packed all the books?
Rs. 2000!
How can you talk like that
in front of children?
Anju is a grown-up.
She understands everything.
No, I don't think she understands.
I couldn't understand anything
when I was her age.
You don't understand anything even now.
- What?
"Every day is a celebration"
"if you live it happily."
"Every day will be pleasant"
"if you wake up with a smile."
"And if you value the happiness
that you have."
"Every part of life seems sweet
and enjoyable."
"Every day of life will remain
as a fond memory."
"Every day is a celebration"
"if you live it happily."
"Every day will be pleasant"
"if you wake up with a smile."
"Life will be filled with joy
and happiness."
"It is said that you won't be sad
if you have dreams to fulfill."
"Include some fun in life"
"and accept some problems."
"Fill your life with fun and play."
"Ours is a family of parents and siblings
who live happily."
"Every part of life seems sweet
and enjoyable."
"Every day of life will remain
as a fond memory."
"Every day is a celebration
if you live it happily."
"Every day will be pleasant"
"if you wake up with a smile."
"Every day is spring,
if you bloom with joy."
"The friendship we share"
"is a blessing in disguise."
"The bond we share is not broken so easily."
"You won't have to visit religious places"
"to find some peace of mind."
"Find peace at home with family"
"amongst their pranks and tantrums."
"Every part of life seems sweet
and enjoyable."
"Every day of life will remain
as a fond memory."
"Every day is a celebration"
"if you live it happily."
"Every day will be pleasant"
"if you wake up with a smile."
"And if you value the happiness
that you have."
"Every part of life seems sweet
and enjoyable."
"Every day of life will remain
as a fond memory."
This is not necessary, mother-in-law.
- Why not, Rambabu? It makes us happy.
Rambabu
you understood our problems
and refused to accept dowry from us
during the wedding.
Now I want to give away the coconut farm
as a dowry for my grandchildren's wedding.
Father-in-law, you agreed
to get Jyothi married to me
though you knew I was an orphan.
Today, you're giving me property
without me asking for it.
Thank you very much.
Dowry is not a necessity, father-in-law.
Girls should be educated
and should possess good values.
We have enough.
I'll ask you if I need anything.
I think you're the most
well-mannered person, Rambabu.
Anju, you lost a pawn.
- Hi, uncle! - Hey, Anu.
How are you, sister?
- I'm fine. Where had you been?
We came a long time ago.
- I had gone out.
How are you, brother-in-law?
- It's been a long time, Rajesh.
He is always busy helping people solve
their problems
by fighting for their rights.
What are you fighting for this time?
There's a village named Devarapalli,
25 kilometers from here.
We got the stone grinding project closed
because of the heavy pollution.
I found these fish near the quarry.
They taste amazing.
Rambabu, fish is good for the heart.
- Is it so? - Yes.
My heart is already at risk
because of your shopping antics.
So it's better to eat fish.
Don't laugh. Give me the fish.
Let's go, mother.
Rambabu, coffee.
- Yes.
Rambabu. - Yes.
- Shall I say something? - What?
I don't know if you'll agree or not.
- Tell me. I'll think about it.
Here you go.
- What is it? - Read it.
Family Preaching from the Divine
by Sri Sri Sri Sachidananda Maharishi
on, Saturday, the 2nd of August
from 8:00 a.m. to 6.30 p.m.
We didn't attend it the last year.
His sermons are very valuable.
Shall we all go?
I can't come.
Go with the children if you want to.
This is for all the family members.
We can't go without you. Come with us.
I told you that I can't come.
- Dad, why is it a curfew today?
The curfew is to protest
the rise in fuel prices.
You're not buying the car
because of the rise in fuel prices?
We'll buy the car. Don't you trust me?
Right, Jyothi?
How is the rise in fuel prices
related to buying a new car?
Your dad will definitely buy a new car.
He just won't use it. Isn't it, dear?
Anju, you took money from me
and went to the nature camp.
You didn't tell me anything about it.
It was very effective, dad.
We attended the nature camp in the morning
and danced around the campfire at night.
- Good.
All of us enjoyed a lot.
We even clicked pictures.
That reminds me of something.
One of the girls created a scene
because some rich guy was clicking
pictures of girls on his mobile phone.
Did he click your pictures as well?
- He did.
Why did you get your picture clicked?
You should have refused.
I didn't get my picture clicked.
He clicked pictures without my permission.
Don't you read the newspaper?
Many girls are committing suicide
because of such issues.
Why would anybody commit suicide
for such issues, mom?
Don't we get pictures clicked
during weddings as well?
Those are normal cameras.
The pictures that are clicked
on mobile phones are very indecent.
Mom, the pictures are the same
in cameras or mobile phones.
It's just that they alter the pictures
on the computer. Say something, dad.
Mom thinks she's right. - That's why
she didn't complete her schooling.
Hello, I've studied much more than
you have. Remember that.
That's not the issue.
I passed my class and you failed.
The flooring is completely ruined.
Why did you leave it unattended for so long?
I couldn't find efficient workers
in the village.
I want to rent it out
if you help me improve it.
We're completing the flooring
in the station.
Only the sub-inspector's room is left.
I'll help you once the work there
is finished on Monday.
Okay. - Rambabu, I'll go now.
I have to be on the site.
Wait, I'll come with you.
Mr. Contractor!
Sir, how much do I owe you?
I must have taken
some money from you.
I wanted to repay all that money.
Why are you acting so innocent?
I know who's making you do all this.
Do you think I'll be scared just because
you might complain to the sub-inspector?
Even he has a share
in the money that you paid.
I'm warning you.
If you complain to the sub-inspector again
then I'll make sure
that your career is ruined. Be careful.
Veerabhadram,
we know about the sub-inspector.
We won't believe you if you say
he supports you in your cheap antics.
Why are you interfering?
- Stop me from interfering, if you can.
Come on, come on.
- How dare you!
How dare you talk like that!
- You're messing with the cops.
I don't care if you're a cop.
I've seen enough people like you.
Please calm down, sir. - Get lost.
- Rambabu, be in your limits.
You don't know what I can do.
I'll teach you a lesson someday.
Why are you fighting with him
for my sake, Rambabu?
He doesn't deserve to be a cop.
- Yes, Rambabu.
But still he is a cop.
We have to be careful.
Why, sir? Why should I fear
the cops when I'm not wrong?
I've never committed a crime
and will never do so.
Give it to me, sister. I'll hold it.
Do you want to impress mom?
Hey!
Hi!
Hi, Anju.
Hi.
- Do you stay nearby?
Didn't you recognize me?
Aren't you Varun?
- So you remember me. Thanks.
How come you're here?
- Actually, I came here for you.
Mom, I'm hungry. Give me something to eat.
Where is your sister?
Did you bring the groceries?
Sister is walking slowly.
Here you go.
Where is your sister?
- I don't know.
What do you mean? You said
she was walking slowly.
We came together till Mr. Gopal's
house. I walked faster after that.
Anju!
Where could she have gone?
Mom, the groceries are in the room.
Anju!
- Yes, mom.
When did you come home?
I called you so many times.
Why didn't you respond?
I got so worried.
Maybe she's listening to songs, mom.
Okay, come out soon.
I'll keep the milk ready.
Don't worry, Anju.
Nobody other than me has seen this.
I'll delete it if you don't like.
But you should do as I say.
I'll come to your backyard at 11:00 p.m.
Come there, okay?
- I won't come, Varun. Please.
Hey, why are you crying, Anju?
I haven't come here
to create a problem for you.
I could have uploaded this
on the internet, if I wanted to.
But I won't do it. Because I like you.
So tonight.. - I won't come, Varun.
Please. I won't come.
Okay! It's not my responsibility
if your family has a problem with
this video going viral on the internet.
If you inform at home
or refuse to come tonight..
Hey, no. You won't do that, will you?
Please spare me, Varun. Please.
Varun, please. - Okay.
We'll meet at the backyard tonight then.
See you. Bye!
You're asleep so soon.
You didn't even drink the milk.
I have a headache.
I'll just sleep for some time.
You'll obviously have a headache
if you listen to loud music.
Shall I give you a tablet?
- No, mom. I'll just sleep for a while.
I'll be all right.
Okay, go to sleep.
Why don't you eat something?
It's quite late.
I think it will rain heavily.
I better leave from here.
Else, there will be a lot of complaints.
Sir. Mr. Rambabu.
- What is it?
Shall I go home?
- You always want to go home.
Do you have an umbrella?
- Yes.
Okay, go then.
- All right.
Did you tell your mother?
You have no idea
how problematic I can be.
Varun, please don't trouble me.
- I didn't want to trouble you.
But you cheated me.
- Varun.
Look, we hail from a middle-class family.
We've never hurt you at all.
Why are you troubling us?
I'm sure even you have sisters.
Please don't ruin my daughter's life.
I'm not ruining your daughter's life,
but you are.
Look at this.
I'll upload this clip on the internet
because you interfered in our affairs.
No. Don't do this. Please.
Please don't do this.
We'll be forced to commit suicide.
Please don't.
- Okay, I won't.
I want your daughter to stay
with me for one hour instead.
I won't accept that in any case.
Mom!
Please, Varun. Give it to me.
Varun.
Anju!
Look, please don't do this.
Don't ruin my daughter's life.
I beg you.
She's just a child.
Don't ruin her life. Please don't.
Okay. I won't ruin Anju's life.
I'll delete the video.
Why don't you fulfill my wish instead?
Somebody walked in with dirty feet.
Jyothi! Jyothi!
Jyothi.
Dad! - Dad!
Hey, what happened?
Jyothi.
Tell me what happened.
Why don't you fulfill my wish instead?
Listen. Varun? Varun?
Anju!
- What?
Varun. Varun.
What happened?
- The phone is dead.
How do we inform dad now?
We can't wait till the morning.
Oh no.
Come, Anju.
- Okay.
Mom!
Anju, bring the spade quickly.
- Okay.
Anju, come on. Help me.
Yes. Prabhakar here.
No, no. Nothing like that.
Let's start the board meeting
sharp at 12.
They are very prompt
and punctual unlike us.
I'll see you there. Okay?
See you. Bye.
The number you're calling
is currently switched off.
His phone is always switched off.
Where is Varun, Geetha? His phone
is switched off from yesterday.
Prabha, I've told you so many times.
Why do you keep calling him and disturb him?
He would have switched off his mobile
because of that.
He's not a child anymore.
We need to give him some freedom.
Else, he'll become a rebel.
- Geetha, I agree that you're right.
We should give him some freedom,
but there's a limit to that.
Varun has crossed all limits.
We have given him a car, laptop,
credit card, an internet connection
and everything else,
without him even asking for those.
Is this necessary at this age?
I think we're spoiling him.
Last month, his credit card bill
was Rs. 26,000.
He did some shopping last month.
He showed me the bills.
What's wrong with that?
You believe everything he says
and he takes advantage of that.
Why don't you understand?
Even I saw the bills. The bill was for
six pairs of jeans and two pairs of shoes.
But he had only two pairs of jeans
and one pair of shoes.
It was a fake bill, Geetha.
What did he do with the remaining money?
Geetha, he's doing something
wrong without telling us.
Did you check his room again?
- Yes.
That's why he didn't come home
last night.
Give him some privacy, Prabha.
Don't doubt him unnecessarily.
Children shouldn't expect privacy
from their parents, Geetha.
He would need privacy
if he's doing something in secret.
Why does he..
- Prabha, understand!
I can't convince you.
What do we do now?
I don't know.
I'm really scared.
I wasn't this scared even when I buried him.
I was so brave at that time.
Was it our mistake?
No.
You were right. - Why don't
we tell the cops about this?
He's the son of
the inspector general of police.
The cops won't spare us
if they come to know about this.
Anju's life will be ruined.
How do we get out of this problem?
Don't worry.
We never hurt anybody intentionally.
Though I'm an orphan, I faced all the
difficulties and took care of my family.
I'll protect our family even
if I have to sacrifice my life for it.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Don't lose hope. - Dad!
Dad!
- What is it?
The keys were in the room.
- I think these are his car keys.
So his car must be around.
How do we find his car?
- He has a yellow car, dad.
Let's go check if there is
something else in the room.
Where did the boy fall after he got hit?
- There.
What are you looking for?
- Blood stains.
Because there are no traces of blood,
I think he had an internal bleeding.
Clear out all this.
- Okay. - Come on.
Dad, SIM card.
- Wait.
There has been a constant signal
from the same place.
We'll trace his SIM card
and nab the culprit.
He has changed the number.
- We need his phone number.
Sir, we can track them
through cell phone signals.
Phone signals will be connected
to different towers at different times.
Even if they leave the city, we can
track them using
the tower signals.
We can trace his movement
with the tower locations.
Don't go out or call anybody
till I come back.
Nobody should find out
that you're at home.
Understood?
- Where are you going?
I have to find the car
and move it from there.
Come soon. We can't stay alone.
Don't worry. I'll be home by evening.
What happened?
- Dad, I'm scared that I may get arrested.
I won't let that happen.
No.
I promise you.
If someone had come
for passport enquiry
then he would have reported
that your son was not present at home.
So you need to be careful.
Don't count anymore.
Do you want to send your son abroad
by paying only Rs. 300?
Give me that amount as well
if you want your son to go abroad.
I had to make an offering at the temple.
It's the same if you give me.
Else, I'll report that your son
was not at home.
How much was the auto fare?
Wasn't that Rambabu?
- Maybe, sir.
Did he buy a new car recently?
- I don't know, sir.
We didn't attend it the last year.
His sermons are very valuable.
Shall we all go?
Hey, move the car.
How may I help you, sir?
- I need a mobile phone.
Which company, sir?
- A second hand phone will do.
Second hand phone?
I want a phone with full battery.
- Full battery..
Try this, sir.
How much is this worth?
- Rs. 900, sir.
Will you please insert this SIM card
in that phone? - Sure.
I'm going to Delhi by flight this evening.
The meeting will last
for two days, sir.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, you have a call.
Please put the phone
on silent mode.
The person you're calling seems
unavailable to take calls right now.
Alcohol consumption is injurious to health.
There's a village called Devarapalli,
25 kilometers from here.
We got the stone grinding project closed
because of the heavy pollution.
Smoking is injurious to health.
Wait here. I'll be right back.
- Okay, sir.
You're here.
I thought you wouldn't come
and that I'd have to stay here tonight.
How about today's collection?
The collection is not that good
because of the rains.
I'm going out of station for two days.
You have to manage here. - Okay.
All right.
How come you're going out all of a sudden?
Vijayanagaram. Jyothi always wanted
to attend the preaching program.
We decided to go now.
- Sir, is there some problem?
Why do you ask? - You look worried, sir.
I can see it in your face.
There's no problem now,
but there will be if you mess up here.
Now you're back to normal.
Carry on. I'll manage.
Jyothi.
- It's dad.
Dad!
- What happened? Don't cry.
I'm home now.
- Where had you gone?
We were so scared
because you took so long.
Dad, don't leave us and go.
- No, dear. I won't go.
What did you do about the car?
- I did what had to be done.
Forget about that.
- What did you do with it?
I have to take bath first.
Bring me a towel.
Aren't you at all tense?
- About what?
The guy.. - Which guy?
No guy came here.
We don't know anything.
- But Varun..
Who is Varun?
I've never heard of that name.
We have to stay unknown from now on.
Else we'll get caught because of our fear.
I went to office before coming home.
Simhadri immediately asked me
if there was a problem.
If Simhadri can suspect a problem,
others can as well.
Did he suspect you?
- He did at first, but I managed.
Even you have to behave normally.
Why don't you tell us
what you did with the car?
Look, don't be bothered
about unnecessary things.
Go to sleep now.
We're going out of station in the morning.
Where are we going?
- It's better we stay away for a few days.
Even you'll feel better.
Tell everybody that you went
to attend the preaching.
But that was yesterday.
Here you go.
Did you buy a ticket, ma'am?
Sir, you've come out with your whole family.
Where are you headed to?
Murli, did you buy a new bus?
- It's not new, but a second hand bus, sir.
I bought it at a lower price.
Where shall I give you a ticket to?
Vijayanagaram.
It's for some preaching.
Jyothi wanted to go, so we're all going.
Here. - Come on, Mr. Rambabu.
I can't accept money from you.
Have I ever forced you to buy a ticket?
Come on, sir.
"Every single minute"
"is accounted for."
"Every single minute spent"
"feels like eternity."
"Be it for you"
"or me."
"It's not easy to change
what has already happened."
"It's not possible to guess"
"what might happen next."
"Every single minute"
"is accounted for."
"Be it for you"
"or me."
"It's not possible to guess"
"what might happen next."
"Time leaves behind some wounds."
"Time also heals those wounds."
"Time doesn't care"
"for love, care and despair."
"But we always care"
"for our family and friends."
"Isn't life all about"
"facing time?"
What is this, Jyothi?
I've told you so many times.
Don't you understand?
We're not able to forget it,
how much ever we try.
You have to forget it.
You don't have a choice.
The cops will use our fear
against us, to prove our crime.
I'm doing everything I can
to protect our family.
Please trust me and do as I say.
Another thing. We need to take
bills for everything we buy.
Be it vegetables, groceries, stationary..
Always ask for a bill at the market.
"Every single minute"
"is accounted for."
"feels like eternity."
Connect me to cyber cell.
"Time alters the story of our life."
"Time also brings tears into our eyes."
"Time passes and drags you with it."
"Time changes and expects you
to change as well."
"Even a single moment"
"can torture us for years to come."
Ma'am, we traced Varun's phone.
On August 2, his phone signal was traced from
Vizag, through Kothavalasa
Vijayanagaram, Srikakulam and Bhuvaneshwaram.
His phone was switched off at an industrial
area called Nimpura in Kharagpur.
Okay. As far as I know,
Varun doesn't have friends in Kharagpur.
Maybe he went
to meet his friends in Kolkata.
His phone must have
got switched off in between.
Possible, ma'am. We've already begun
investigation in the Kharagpur area.
Okay.
"Every single minute"
"is accounted for."
"feels like eternity."
"Be it you"
"or me."
"It's not easy to change"
"what has already happened."
"It's not possible to guess"
"what might happen next."
Seenu, come here.
Don't worry, ma'am. We found only the car.
- Who saw the car first?
Some of the boys
who came here for a swim, saw it.
It looks like the car was in the water
for long. - Yes, ma'am.
It must have been more than two weeks.
Did you conduct a search in the water?
- You don't have to worry, sir.
We did a thorough search.
Mr. Anil Kumar, please wrap it up
before the media finds out.
Yes, ma'am.
- Within 24 hours
we'll find out what happened
and who's responsible.
Ma'am, the car route and the cell
phone route are very different.
On the night of August 2, the cell phone
signal was tracked at a tower in S Kota.
The phone was out of coverage
at 9.38 p.m. that night.
At 9.54 a.m. on 3rd of August, the phone was
within coverage area, at Vijayanagaram Tower.
The signal was then traced
through Srikakulam, Bhuvaneshwaram
and the phone was switched off at Kharagpur.
Ma'am, we sent the police forces
to Kolkata and Kharagpur for
preliminary investigation
but there was no information.
Find out the mobile numbers
that Varun called on that day.
Yes, ma'am.
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, we have proof that money
was withdrawn from the bank accounts
you spoke about,
from an ATM near Rajavaram.
How much is the withdrawal?
- Rs. 20,000, sir.
Why would he need so much money?
Sir, I have a doubt.
I feel that the SIM card that was
out of range on August 2
and the SIM that was within range on August 3
are different phones.
The IMEI numbers are different as well.
Maybe he withdrew cash to buy a new mobile.
No. Varun bought
a new mobile quite recently.
Why would he buy another one?
Geetha, our son is in trouble.
Sir.
Simhadri.
- Yes, sir. - What is this?
It's the tax bill.
- Didn't I ask you to pay it?
Actually..
- It's been three weeks.
I don't think it's been that long.
- What do you mean?
August 2 was a Saturday. I told you
after we came back from Vijayanagaram.
Right?
- Yes, sir.
His name is Varun.
He is the Inspector General
Geetha Prabhakar's son.
He's been missing since a few days.
According to his cell phone records, he was
in our village on the second of this month.
This is Varun's car.
AP 31 BN 6215
This car was recovered
from the quarry near Devarapalli.
Seenu, I heard your son was admitted
in the hospital. How is he now?
He's fine, sir.
- He's fine? - Yes.
Give me a hundred bucks then.
- I don't have that amount, sir.
Hey, you must have it.
- Sir. - Such an idiot.
You must have it in one of the pockets.
Check properly.
Sir. - You must have
some money for your kid's medicines.
No, sir.
- Hey, check properly. - Sir.
This is only twenty bucks. Go now.
Mister, give me half a pack of cigarettes.
Don't you want a special tea today?
I don't have time for that.
I have a serious case at hand.
I have to go.
- What is the case about?
Someone drowned a yellow Maruti
in the quarry near Devarapalli.
Devarapalli doesn't come
under your jurisdiction, does it?
We don't have a choice. We've special orders
from the inspector general of police.
They asked us to inquire if the car
was seen in our village
and where.
I'll leave now.
How come you're paying me?
- I had some change, so I just paid off.
Veerabhadram, you're deliberately trying
to frame Rambabu in this case.
I saw Rambabu drive away in that car, sir.
I even tested it.
He was terrified when I spoke
about the car at the hotel.
I can prove it to you. If he's guilty
then he'll look back at us before
he reaches the office. Wait and watch.
Are you done?
Veerabhadram says that he saw
Rambabu drive away in Varun's car.
How are they related?
- Simple, sir.
Rambabu and Veerabhadram
always have arguments.
They even had a tiff over something recently.
Sir, I suspect that Veerabhadram is trying
to frame Rambabu in this case.
- Okay.
Yes, sir. Rambabu is a good person.
Even I know that.
But Veerabhadram is so sure..
Sir. Look at this.
I went to Sathyam's house
for passport verification
at 7.15 a.m. on August 3.
If this is true, then I could
have seen Rambabu there, right?
Come here.
Where were you on August 2?
We went to attend the preaching
at Vijayanagaram.
When did you return home?
- The next day which was a Sunday.
What time did you come home?
We came home in the evening.
Where did you go for the preaching?
- Vijayanagaram.
Where did you go in Vijayanagaram?
- Sai.. - Wait.
It was at the Sai Baba temple.
Was it at the Sai Baba temple?
It was in the main hall of the temple.
What is all this?
Does this mean that the cops
will come here for interrogation?
They'll definitely come.
But I don't know when they'll come.
It's better if they come late.
But don't worry.
They don't know anything about the guy.
They don't have any evidence.
They'll try to come up with some evidence.
They'll scare you, be nice to you
confuse you
and might even beat me and your mom.
They'll go away when they
don't find any evidence.
That's why we have to always
say the same thing.
We have to give the same answer
to the questions that the cops ask us.
You two, your mother and I
have to say the same thing.
Understood?
Dad, will they beat up mom and you?
No.
Don't worry about that.
Consider it the punishment
that I give you when you're naughty.
Dad, I'm very scared.
Why are you scared when I'm here for you?
Go to sleep. Come on.
Rambabu.
- Yes.
How will you prove that you were
not here on Saturday?
Someone must have seen you
at the hotel or the office.
Someone must have definitely seen me.
How will you prove that we were
not here on Saturday?
Jyothi, this incident was something
that we never expected.
We have only two options.
Either we face it bravely
or give up in fear.
We know that we're not wrong
so I can't convince myself to give up.
That's why we have to face it bravely.
Look, Jyothi, we've never been
in such a situation.
We might not get through it.
But I believe that we would.
The children and you won't go to jail.
I promise you.
I don't know if it was Rambabu or not.
- Hey, don't lie.
You said that it was Rambabu, the other day.
You said that it was him and I agreed.
I didn't say so.
Hey, tell me.
- Sir, like Mr. Sathyam said
we thought it was Rambabu.
But I'm not sure.
Okay. Did you see this car?
- I saw a yellow car, sir.
This is a yellow car itself.
- I don't know if it's the same car.
Why are you always in doubt?
Look, you tell me what you saw.
It seemed like the same car,
but I didn't see the number plate.
You're an auto driver, aren't you?
How many yellow cars have you seen?
- I've seen many, sir.
The postmaster's car
is also yellow, sir.
Maybe we saw his car that day.
- Hey, we'll find that out. Shut up.
Veerabhadram, what is this?
- Sorry, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Did you receive a fax?
- We received one from the IG's office.
Sir, Varun went
to the nature camp last month.
Some students from Chaitanya Junior College
also attended that camp.
One of the girls, Anju,
is Rambabu's daughter.
Sir, please trust me now at least.
Rambabu will speak the truth
if we interrogate him properly.
So today,
it's 'Properties of Organic Acid'.
Ma'am.
- Yes.
Anju, you're wanted by the principal.
The cops will recognize our fear.
Our fear will prove to be
an evidence for them.
The cops don't know
what happened at home.
They will question us with
half the knowledge of the case.
Answer them confidently.
You should tell them
that you know Varun
but not that he came home.
May I come in, ma'am?
- Yes, come in.
Anju, he's Inspector Naveen.
He wants to question you about something.
You're Rambabu's elder daughter, aren't you?
- Yes, sir. - Okay.
Do you know him?
Isn't he Varun?
- How do you know him?
I saw him at the nature camp
that I attended last month.
Do you know anything else about him?
I know that his mother is
the inspector general of police.
Did he tell you that? - I heard
some students talk about him in the camp.
Do you know Varun well?
- No, sir.
I don't know much about him.
- Is it so?
Then how did you recognize him so easily?
Everybody who attended
the nature camp knows Varun.
There was a minor problem because of him.
- What problem?
He was clicking girls' pictures
at the camp.
One girl from Hyderabad complained
to the principal about it.
Did you meet Varun after the camp?
- No. What happened, sir?
Is there any problem?
- Yes.
We have information that you met Varun here.
Did Varun tell you so?
- Yes.
He must have lied, sir. - Did Varun come
to your house on the second of this month?
No, sir. He didn't come.
Sir, one minute.
Which day are you talking about?
The second of this month.
It was a Saturday. Do you remember now?
We had gone out of station on that day.
Where had you gone?
- We went to attend a session
on 'Family Preaching from the Divine'.
Who all had gone?
- My mom, dad, sister and I.
When did you return?
- The next evening.
Did you stay in Vijayanagaram for two days?
We were at the temple on Saturday.
We stayed at a lodge, watched a movie
on Sunday morning and returned.
What actually happened, sir?
This guy is missing. We have proof
that he was in this village on the second.
Because she knew the guy, we wanted
to check if they had met on that day.
No, sir. I didn't see Varun after the camp.
- Okay. Thank you.
Welcome, sir.
Now you can go to your class.
- Okay, ma'am.
Aren't you Rambabu's wife?
- Yes, sir.
Rambabu, you never
come home at this time.
The principal called her and told
that you went to meet Anju at school.
She got scared and called me.
I went to the station and they told me
that you were at my house.
That's why I'm home at this time.
What's the matter, sir?
We came to enquire about a case.
- Let's sit down and talk.
Okay.
- Please come.
Rambabu, do you know this guy?
- No, sir.
Do you know him?
No, sir.
Have you seen this car?
What about you?
- No.
Rambabu, let me be clear with you.
It's better if you answer clearly as well.
- Sure, sir.
This guy's name is Varun.
He is the Inspector General
Geetha Prabhakar's son.
He has been missing
from the past three weeks.
Your elder daughter, Anju, met Varun
at the nature camp last month.
We have information that Varun
came to your house in his car.
The police department recovered this car
from the quarry near Devarapalli.
We have two reasons as to why we are here.
One is that your daughter knows Varun
and the other is that Constable Veerabhadram
saw you drive that car.
You didn't see me that day.
I had gone to Sathyam's house
for passport verification.
When we enquired about it, we found out
that only your daughter knows Varun here.
So he must have come to your house.
We were not here on that day.
We went to attend the preaching program
at the Sai Baba temple in Vijayanagaram.
We returned home in the evening,
the next day.
Now they're talking.
What other proof do you want, sir?
Rambabu, do you think this is a joke?
Nobody asked you for the dates.
Why is your wife telling us about
the dates
without being asked for it?
Rambabu, this is a serious case.
How can you laugh like this?
Do you think we're joking here?
- No, no, nothing like that.
Why would I think so?
Look at her. She's still in a shock.
She doesn't even know
what's happening here.
She has been like this
since the principal called.
You know how college authorities are.
They fear that their reputation will be ruined
if the students are accused of crimes.
That's why she got tensed
when the principal called up
and told her everything including the dates.
Veerabhadram said that he saw you drive
that car on the third of this month.
You didn't answer to that.
There's nothing to say, sir.
- What do you mean?
Everybody knows that
Veerabhadram doesn't like me.
He won't trust anything I say.
Okay, forget about that. Tell me the truth.
- I'll tell you, sir.
If he is saying that he saw me,
then he must be lying
or he must have mistaken
someone else for me.
Sir, we were out of station
from 8:00 a.m. on August 2
to 5:00 p.m. on August 3.
We were in Vijayanagaram.
No, sir. I'm sure that I saw him
that day.
Can you tell me what you did
and where you went
in those days?
Sure, sir.
We left from here by bus,
at 5.30 a.m. on August 2.
Was it raining when you returned?
- Yes, sir.
Jyothi and the children even
contracted fever because of that.
The children didn't
attend school for a few days.
Sir, we've known a lot of people
who collect bills for convenience.
This is the first time I've seen someone
collect bus tickets as well.
Do you still trust him?
We are a middle-class family, sir.
We can keep account of the money spent
only by collecting bills.
Okay, okay. Let's go.
What is the area of this land, Rambabu?
- Around five acres, sir.
Oh, okay.
I shouldn't have spoken, right?
- Yes.
They believed when you
showed them the bills, right?
Veerabhadram, after talking to them
I feel you're trying to frame Rambabu.
- Why would I do that, sir?
I'm sure that I saw Rambabu that day, sir.
We'll inform
the inspector general first.
Dad.
- Yes, dear.
Will the cops believe what we told?
I don't know, dear.
Will the cops come again, dad?
They will come, dear.
What is his name?
- Rambabu, ma'am.
Are you sure that he was driving Varun's car?
I didn't see the number
but it was a yellow Maruti.
Did you see Rambabu drive the car?
- I'm sure it was him, sir.
Didn't they say that they were
out of station on those days?
Sir, they're lying.
You said that they showed you
evidence, didn't you?
They showed us hotel bills and bus tickets.
But we haven't verified
if they were original.
If he is telling the truth
then Rambabu's story and evidence is fake.
He has not even completed his schooling.
I'm sure he would have left behind some
evidence which we can use to nab him.
So, I want Rambabu and his
family here tomorrow morning
with all the evidence that they showed.
Sir! - How come
you're here so early in the morning?
The cops have taken away Rambabu.
- Oh, no. Why?
We left by bus at 5.30 a.m.
Why don't you have the bus tickets?
My husband's friend owns the bus.
He refused to accept money from us.
What time did you reach the Sai Baba temple?
I think it was around 8.30 a.m.
The program had already begun.
We arrived at the preaching
a little late.
What time did you reach the temple?
They'll suspect us if we all
tell them the same time.
You children need not
tell them the right time.
I'm not sure about the time
but the program had already begun
when we reached there.
How long did you wait
for the program to start?
The cops might question you in different
ways to force the truth out of you.
But you should not get tensed
and only say what we've agreed upon.
The program had begun
by the time we reached there.
Your dad said that it started
half an hour after you reached.
The cops might confuse you
but stick to what you said before.
Don't change it.
No. The program had begun
by the time we went there.
Hey, what is this?
- We want to talk to Rambabu.
Let us go inside.
- Hey, what is this?
Even we don't know.
They're not allowing us inside.
Please open the gates.
We'll talk to them and come.
We've been told not to allow anybody inside.
Hey, he is Rambabu's father-in-law.
Open the gates!
Sir, it's for your own benefit.
Move back!
Hey, shut up. You don't know what I can do.
Open the gates!
Don't you understand if told once?
- Hey, just open the gates.
Open the gates!
- Hey, move back!
Hey, how dare you?
- Move back!
We had lunch at a hotel after that.
Which hotel?
I don't remember the name.
What did you eat?
- 'Biryani'.
What did your parents eat?
- Even they ate 'biryani'.
Your sister said that you all ate fried rice.
Maybe she forgot. We ate 'biryani'.
I remember very well.
Mr. Naveen, this is..
- Hello.
Who told you?
No, no. They're just rumors.
It's not true.
I'm in a meeting. I'll get back to you.
What?
- It was a reporter from a news channel.
They've received news
that we're interrogating a family
in our son's missing case.
- Just leave it!
So, Mr. Naveen, what
do you think about it?
They're not as easy as I thought.
They're very adamant.
All of them are saying the same thing.
We tried questioning them differently,
but they're confident about their answer.
Specially their younger daughter.
I'm shocked to see that she's so confident.
- That's it!
Don't you think it's strange
that the small kid is so confident?
Even I felt it was strange, ma'am.
What if they're telling the truth?
He could have lied.
- No, no.
I'm sure about one thing.
They know something about Varun.
But, Geetha, they are..
- Lying!
It's a cooked-up story.
They're very shrewd.
But it won't sell here. - Ma'am,
because we're sure that they're lying
let's conduct a lie detector test.
- How did you become a cop?
We can't conduct a lie
detector test on everybody.
We need a court order for that.
Why don't you get a court order issued?
It's not that easy, Prabha.
We have to prove in the court
that they're lying.
But we don't have any evidence
against them.
I know how to make them speak the truth.
I want to meet every person
that they mentioned. - Yes, ma'am.
Not just that.
If Rambabu hadn't gone
to attend the preaching program
he would have stayed here, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
He would have gone to the office, right?
Find out where else Rambabu goes
apart from his office.
He goes to a hotel opposite
the police station, ma'am.
Very good.
Bring his office staff
and the hotel owner here.
Okay, ma'am.
I felt very scared to talk to the cops.
God has really helped us.
I hope everything is over.
- Jyothi. - Yes.
It's not over yet.
The cops will come again.
Will they come again?
- Yes.
Why, brother-in-law?
What's the problem?
Why don't you tell me at least?
Look, Rajesh, every family
will have some personal issues
that they can't tell anybody.
Please don't ask me anything.
But you have to help me.
- What should I do, brother-in-law?
I've known him as a child.
He's very innocent.
He doesn't hurt anybody.
I don't want
his character certificate from you.
Just answer the question.
How many times did Rambabu
come to your hotel on August 2?
He generally comes twice,
for tea and dinner.
Sometimes, he doesn't come for dinner.
It's difficult to guess.
- Sir, just answer the question.
How many times did he come
to the hotel on the second?
Okay, sir. He must have come twice.
Hold on! I was wrong.
Rambabu had gone out of station on that day.
He went to attend some meeting in Vijayanagaram.
Why didn't you tell us before?
I just remembered.
Rambabu told us about the preaching as well.
What did he tell you?
He said that his sermons
were very valuable for life.
He even told us a few stories.
- What stories?
It was a story about the soul of Sai Baba
visiting Ramakrishna Paramahamsa.
When did Rambabu return from Vijayanagaram?
He returned the next day.
- What time?
He didn't come to office that day.
Do you know them?
- Yes, ma'am.
Did they board
your bus recently?
They boarded my bus
a few days ago.
Have they ever travelled
on your bus before that?
Yes, sir. It was on the second of this month.
Where were they headed to?
- They said they were going to Vijayanagaram.
They said they were going
to attend some preaching.
Are you sure that they stayed at your lodge?
Yes, sir.
- Is he a regular customer? - No, sir.
How do you remember them so clearly then?
I want a double room.
- Sir, that will be Rs. 650 plus tax.
I didn't pay the tax
when I came here the last time.
Maybe you didn't ask for the bill.
I don't want the bill.
Rambabu, is this a family lodge?
Let's go to another lodge.
Ma'am, this is a family lodge.
You'll like the room.
They agreed to stay at the lodge
only when I showed them the room.
Do you remember
when they stayed at the lodge?
I don't remember, sir.
Did they tell you why
they had come to Vijayanagaram?
They didn't tell me, sir.
Did you check the register?
- Yes, ma'am.
They maintain two registers.
One of the registers has Rambabu's name.
They checked in on August 2 and
checked out the next day at 9:00 a.m.
Why do you maintain two registers?
Why don't you give her an explanation?
One of the registers is
for people who ask for the bill
and the other is for people
who don't ask for the bill.
Don't you know that's wrong?
How do you remember them even after so long?
How can we forget good customers, ma'am?
Are you the hotel owner?
- Yes, sir. Why?
I've never eaten a tastier 'biryani'.
This is the only hotel that serves
good 'biryani' in Vijayanagaram.
Even your service was good.
The hotel is hygienic as well.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
- Thank you, sir.
We do home delivery as well.
You can leave your number here.
We don't stay at Vijayanagaram.
Sir, the 'biryani' was very tasty.
- Is it so? Thanks, dear.
Did you come to Vijayanagaram for shopping?
No, sir. We came for the preaching
program at the Sai Baba temple.
We'll leave now, sir.
- All right.
It's good that you remember good customers.
But it's strange that you're mentioning
their date of arrival
and their reason of visit.
- What's so strange, sir?
We don't remember customers
who just eat and leave.
But we always remember customers
who talk to us, appreciate us
and pay us in person.
- Okay, okay.
Okay, wait outside.
- All right.
What is this mystery?
If they were
at home on both the days
how could Rambabu
meet all these people?
Even I'm confused, ma'am.
Geetha,
maybe Rambabu is telling the truth.
I doubt that the constable is lying.
No, sir. I'm not lying.
I saw Rambabu drive away in the car.
I'll quit my job if I'm proved wrong.
Did you contact the person
who delivered sermons at Vijayanagaram?
Based on what you're saying
he must have attended the program.
I'm sure about this because
I've never narrated the stories
that I narrated at Vijayanagaram,
before that.
It wouldn't have been possible
for him to have known them otherwise.
Isn't it possible that someone
who attended your program
could have told him?
The preachings that I gave
are not easy to remember.
Four tickets
What about dad and Anu?
- Let's go inside.
This is the digital projector.
I want to build a theatre in my village.
- Sure, sir.
The investment will be much less
because of the digital projector.
Even the maintenance is easy.
That's my wife and my elder daughter.
- Greetings!
Greetings.
- Greetings.
Do you remember the day
they came to your theatre?
They came on August 3.
How are you so sure about the date?
He watched the movie
sitting in the projector room.
He even told me that they had come
to attend some program
and that they had stayed at a hotel.
That's all.
Just get out!
- You may go now.
Geetha
control yourself. Come on.
Prabha, our son..
Nothing will happen to him.
Be brave.
We'll find out where he is.
Don't lose hope.
Geetha, do you think that the investigation
is headed in the right direction?
Yes, I think so.
- We haven't found any evidence.
All the evidence points out
that they're innocent.
See, Prabha
I'm not saying this
based on the evidence we have.
We cops come to know whether
a person is telling the truth
or hiding the truth from us
based on their words or behavior.
We're trained for that.
We might not have any evidence against him
but I know that he's lying.
He's lying, Prabha!
I can feel it. I can feel it.
Maybe a mother who has lost her son
will always think like this.
Geetha.
Thinking otherwise, I've underestimated him.
A person who has not completed schooling
can't be so clever.
Rambabu always wishes good for the people.
I found out everything about Rambabu, ma'am.
He came to this village a long time ago.
He started off with menial jobs
such as working at a video parlor
as an automobile mechanic
and a cable operator.
Rambabu loves movies.
He watches movies of all languages
and watches them many times.
Maybe that's why
he can speak various languages
even though he's a school dropout.
It's a wonder that someone can gain
so much knowledge from movies.
Movies.
It's an important link.
Ticket! Ticket!
Ticket!
Many people travel in your bus every day.
It's not a big deal to remember
one family among them.
But you seem to have a good memory
because you're able to say
where they were headed to and why.
What are you thinking about?
She just asked you a simple question.
You said that they travelled
in your bus on August 3
and that they had come after attending
a program the previous day.
We want to know how you remember something
that happened 25 days ago.
Actually, I don't remember
what they told that day.
You just said that they had attended
a program on August 2.
We spoke about that
when we met the other day.
What do you mean?
- We met a few days ago.
Where did you meet him?
Sir!
- Hi, dear.
You seem to be going somewhere again.
- You are..
Didn't you recognize me?
- Hey, don't you remember?
He's the conductor of the bus we were in
while returning from the preaching.
Yes, now I remember.
You're the conductor of the bus
that we boarded on August 3
after attending the program
on August 2, right?
Yes, sir.
- Sorry, I forgot. - That's okay.
I'll leave now. Let's go.
Goodbye, sir. - Goodbye.
Who.. Oh, it's you!
- Hasn't the show started yet?
No, sir. How come you're alone?
Where is your family?
They haven't come. I've come alone.
- Okay.
On August 2, we came here to attend
the preaching at the Sai Baba temple
and came to watch a movie on August 3.
- Okay!
If I bring my family again and again
they'll spend lavishly
on shopping and eating out.
Murli, you didn't let me pay for the tickets
when we went to attend the preaching
on August 2 as well. Now you have to accept it.
- Come on, sir. Convince him, ma'am.
How will you clear your debts
if you don't take money like this?
Come on, take it.
- You're too much, sir. Here you go.
Please come. You've come after so long.
- It's not that long, sir.
We came to your hotel after we visited
the Sai Baba temple on August 2. - Yes.
We came to the hotel on August 3, right?
- Yes.
I didn't meet him again, ma'am.
No, sir. It's not been that long.
- Of course, it has.
We went to the preaching on August 2.
When was it? It was a Saturday, August 2.
- It was a Saturday, August 2.
When did we return? August 3, understood?
So we returned on Sunday, August 3
and I asked you to pay taxes on Monday,
August 4. Didn't I tell you?
Yes, yes.
- Exactly.
All the devotees were troubled when Sai Baba
lay unconscious for three days.
But Sai Baba had actually visited
Ramakrishna Paramahamsa in his soul form.
Ramakrishna Paramahamsa told Baba
that he was still needed
to bring Hindus and Muslims together.
Rambabu, how do you know all this?
- Didn't I tell you, sir?
We had gone to attend
the preaching in Vijayanagaram
on the second of this month.
It was a Saturday.
Hello.
This is not her number.
Who is it?
- My disciples have made
a recording of my sermons.
What! A recording?
Many people booked for the recording
at the Sai Baba temple.
I spoke to the manager,
but there is no record
of any person named Rambabu
to have booked the recording.
It's possible that Rambabu booked
the recording in another name.
It might be true.
But none of the people
we interrogated told us
that they were in the village
on those two days. So..
We got on the bus at 5.30 a.m. on August 2.
- Rambabu was out of station.
You didn't accept money when we attended
the program in Vijayanagaram.
He said that he came to attend a
program and that he stayed at a hotel.
It was the day I attended the
preaching at the Sai Baba temple.
That's why we came to
watch the movie on August 3.
We came here when we came
to the Sai Baba temple on August 2.
We came to the hotel on August 3, right?
He just recreated that day.
He recreated all the events
that never happened. - What?
Don't you get it?
He recreated it.
They didn't go anywhere on those two days.
But he made everybody believe that they did.
What's the specialty of movies?
Scene!
A person might not remember words
but will always remember what he saw.
They travelled for two days.
That's not a lie.
They really went to Vijayanagaram
and stayed there for two days.
This is why they didn't change
their statement.
Do you think they travelled on those days?
That is what he recreated.
They must have gone to Vijayanagaram
on the fourth or fifth.
- That must be Monday or Tuesday.
Ma'am, their children didn't attend
school from Monday to Wednesday.
We questioned him about it.
He said that they had a fever
because of the rain
and so they hadn't attended school.
He showed medical bills
when we didn't trust him.
Anybody can issue fake
medical bills for a few bucks.
He's taking us for a ride
by showing us fake bills.
But their names in the lodge register
on August 2, the bus and movie tickets
are all real.
How can you say that they're fake?
That's also an important point, ma'am.
We underestimated Rambabu here.
He might not have completed his schooling
but he has had enough experiences in life.
Now I completely understand
the story that he told us.
Rambabu went to Vijayanagaram
on August 3, in Varun's car.
He bought a parcel at a hotel on that day.
Then he bought a mobile phone,
inserted Varun's SIM card in it
and threw the phone on a lorry
which has a national permit.
He then drowned Varun's car
in the water near the quarry.
He then stole
somebody else's 'biryani' bills.
He then went to the cinema hall
and bought four tickets
for the matinee show.
Then he got on a bus and bought
four tickets while coming home.
He went directly to the office
and reminded Simhadri
that he was going
to attend the preaching program.
On August 4, that is the next day,
he got on Murli's bus
and told him that they were headed to the Sai
Baba temple without him even asking about it.
They went to the temple at 9:00 a.m.
and stayed there till the evening.
He found out about the recording
of the preaching at the temple
and booked it under somebody else's name.
Then they came to the lodge,
where he distracted the manager
and entered their details
on the August 2 page of the register.
He must have written somebody
else's name on the August 4 page
in a different handwriting.
He must have eaten at a roadside eatery
and asked someone to pick up a parcel
from the same hotel where he bought
the parcel on August 3.
Once they checked out of the lodge,
they went to the restaurant
ate 'biryani' and built a rapport
with the manager.
He then went to the cinema hall
and met the projector operator.
He then got on the bus and returned home.
He even conversed with the conductor.
Once they returned home
all of them watched the recording
of the preaching.
He got rid of all the bills
that he collected on August 5
and presented us with the bills
that he collected alone on August 3.
He again went to Vijayanagaram
after a few days and met everybody.
He then repeated to everybody
that he had visited Vijayanagaram
on August 2
for them to remember.
That's why everybody was so sure
that it was on August 2.
That's not the date
they saw Rambabu's family
but the date Rambabu put into their memory.
This is how he fooled
the entire police department.
We don't have any evidence
to prove this.
We just have a theory.
Geetha, if you're telling the truth
then where is Varun?
Why did Varun even meet them?
I'll make him answer for that.
Sir, this is really unfair.
- Come on, come on.
Move it! Move it!
Please move aside.
Dad.
- Is that all?
Move, move, move fast.
- Sir, what is this?
Please wait till the lawyer arrives.
- Hey, get lost!
Rajesh, you have to call the media
if the police take us away again.
Where is my son?
I don't know how to convince you, ma'am.
I've already told you that we were
out of station on that day.
Do you think that the cops are fools?
We know about the tour that you went on
to plant fabricated evidences.
Why did Varun come to meet you?
How are you and Varun related?
I didn't meet Varun
after the nature camp, ma'am.
Enough with your lies!
It's better if you speak the truth.
Else, you'll be interrogated
in a different way.
I swear, I don't know anything, ma'am.
Speak up at least.
Don't waste my time.
It's good for everybody
if you speak the truth.
The truth won't change
if you ask repeatedly, ma'am.
We don't know anything else.
Veerabhadram!
- Yes, ma'am.
No! No!
- Don't beat up my dad. Please.
Rambabu. No!
- Mom!
Mom, tell him not to beat up dad.
- Speak up!
Dad!
- No!
Please don't beat him.
Ma'am, please ask him not to beat him.
Dad!
Rambabu! Rambabu!
Just speak up!
Do you think this is a joke?
Do you think we'll believe your stories?
- Don't..
Rambabu!
Mom, ask him not to
beat up dad. Please.
Veerabhadram, that's enough.
Dad!
Where is my son?
- We really don't know.
Don't you understand?
Speak the truth.
We really don't know.
- Speak up!
Hey, speak up! Come on.
Speak up!
How dare you? Speak up.
I won't spare you. Speak up.
Just tell the truth. Speak up!
Speak up!
- Speak up!
Hey, speak the truth.
You won't budge that easily.
Varun's friend, Shrikant is here.
Ask them to stop.
Stop it! That's enough.
Come with me.
Hey, speak up..
- Veerabhadram!
That's enough! Go away.
- Sir, he..
Enough! Go.
Rambabu, just tell what you know
about the inspector general's son.
Why are you getting beaten up?
I have already told you
that I don't know anything.
What's the actual problem?
Why don't you tell us
if you know something?
Why are you getting beaten up?
Do you know this girl?
- No, ma'am.
Look, Shrikant, we know that Varun
and you attended the nature camp.
Varun has been missing from 26 days.
This girl is somehow related
to that.
It's better if you tell us what you know.
I swear, sir. I don't know anything.
You were the last person to call
Varun on the day he went missing.
If you keep lying
then I know how to make you speak the truth.
I swear, ma'am. I'm telling the truth.
He did answer his phone
when I called up
but he didn't tell me where he was going.
Okay. How is this girl related to Varun?
You know the truth. Tell me!
Hey, speak the truth!
- Wait! Wait.
Don't scare him. He'll tell the truth.
Come on, tell us.
Hey. - Yes.
- Share the video with me.
Sorry. Don't ask for this video.
What's the problem?
Share it through Bluetooth.
This is not an ordinary video.
This is a special case.
Ma'am.
- Come in.
There are a lot of people
who have gathered outside.
Even the media has arrived.
We don't know how they found out
about it.
They want to talk to you.
- I won't talk to anybody.
I don't want anybody
to enter the guesthouse.
Naveen. - Ma'am. - Call for extra
police support, if you have to.
Okay, ma'am. - Come on.
I'm scared of how worse
this matter can get, Geetha.
Yes! It's time to end this.
Everybody, go out!
Veerabhadram, you can stay.
I found out about the nature camp video.
What did you do with my son?
I have already told you
that we don't know anything.
I want to know the truth.
- Okay.
Understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
Dad!
How dare you lie to the cops?
No! Let go of him.
- Hey!
Geetha, this is not right.
I won't spare you.
- Mom!
Speak up!
Will you speak up or not?
You'll have to.
Speak up! Come on.
- Mom!
You know the truth.
- No!
Come on, speak up the truth.
There must have been some reason.
Speak up.
Speak up! Come on, speak up.
- Hey!
How dare you beat up a police officer!
Hey! Speak up!
- Dad! - Rambabu!
I won't spare any of you
if you don't speak up the truth.
We don't know anything.
- Don't you know?
Speak up!
Anju!
- Speak up the truth.
If you don't speak the truth
then I'll not spare your parents.
Tell me the truth
if you want your parents to live.
Shall I kill them?
Speak up!
Veerabhadram!
Why are you so stubborn?
Please tell us if you know something.
Where is Anu?
- Anu! Anu! - Wait!
You can't go inside.
- Sir, it's my daughter.
- Anu! Sir.
This guy came to your house, didn't he?
I don't know anything, sir.
I want to go to my parents.
I'll take you to your parents
if you stop crying and speak up.
Come on, tell me.
Tell me!
Speak up the truth
before I get angry.
Else I'll not spare any of you.
Understood?
This is enough, dad.
Let's tell them the truth.
They'll not spare Anu
if we don't speak out the truth.
He is such a monster.
I'm very scared.
I can't see the children suffer.
I'll confess to the crime. That
will help us get rid of the problem.
Hey, did we tolerate all this to confess?
You won't get arrested. I promise you.
I will keep up my promise,
even if I have to sacrifice my life.
But, Anu..
- Jyothi, they won't hurt Anu.
Don't worry about that.
She'll be fine. I believe so.
Hey, speak up!
- I don't know anything, sir.
Take me to my parents.
Geetha, this is too much.
Let's stop this.
This is illegal.
What about Varun then?
Let's conduct an inquiry.
But just stop this.
Spare that child at least.
We've tortured them enough.
Even then they didn't utter a single word.
If they're really not related to this case
we'll have to regret all our life
for torturing them so much.
You believed a constable
and created such a scene.
What if he is lying?
What will we do then?
Veerabhadram!
Don't kill me. I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you everything. I'll tell you.
Dad!
- Hey!
- Anu! - Sir.
Anu!
- Sir.
Where is she taking my daughter to?
They're taking her to the place
where Varun is buried.
Your story has come to an end, Rambabu.
Your family and you
can live happily in jail.
Hey! Bring them to the jeep.
Why are you doing this?
- Hey, move aside.
Move aside! Move aside!
This is my daughter's house.
Let me go inside.
Nobody is allowed near the culprits.
Why are they the culprits?
What have they done?
Wait for some time and you'll know.
Why should we wait?
- What actually happened, sir?
Even we don't know.
That lady who is injured is my daughter.
The person next to her is my son-in-law.
They took them for an inquiry and beat them up.
Why would the cops do this
without any reason?
The inspector general's son is missing.
This is a serious case.
Use this for the breaking news.
Rambabu is a good man.
You can ask anybody here.
That person there is
Constable Veerabhadram.
He wants to frame Rambabu in this case.
My daughter and son-in-law
don't know anything.
They're trying to frame them.
Dad!
- Anu.
I got scared, dad, and told them everything.
Did he hit you?
- Yes, dad.
He even hit such a small child.
You'll be fine now.
Are you angry with me?
No, dad. Was it wrong to confess?
No, dear. It was right on your part.
Rajesh!
- What happened, brother-in-law?
Constable Veerabhadram hit my daughter
though we told them
that we didn't know anything.
Veerabhadram deliberately dragged
my family to the police station.
Hey, Rambabu!
- Wait, Veerabhadram!
He is Veerabhadram.
- Don't you dare.. - Hey!
What will you do?
- That's him. He hit my daughter.
I'll hit her again. What will you do?
Ma'am, we've got to move.
- Geetha, come on.
Come on, dear. Tell them everything.
I'm here. Nobody can hurt you.
Tell them everything.
The court has decided
that Rambabu's family is innocent
in the missing case of the inspector
general's son, Varun.
The court has also suspended
Constable Veerabhadram
for misguiding the authorities.
- Yes!
Some of the cops have been
transferred to other places as well.
Inspector General Geetha Prabhakar
has been sent on leave.
The district court has ordered
the police to take permission
before interrogating
Rambabu's family again.
Rambabu. Rambabu.
Look at this!
Inspector General
Geetha Prabhakar resigns.
She gave up her job because of us.
She might be a police officer,
but she is a mother first.
Were we unfair in taking away her son
from her?
You're thinking in this manner
because you're a good person.
Wouldn't she have protected her son
if something had happened to Anju
because of her son?
She would have definitely saved him.
Besides, who are we to decide
what's right or wrong?
Humans are always self-centered.
That's a human tendency, Jyothi.
So let's not feel bad, and forget about this.
When did you take out the body from there?
Sunday.
The night I drowned the car.
Where is the body now?
No, Jyothi.
Nobody should find out about this.
It shall remain with me
until I die.
That will keep you safe.
Did you think that Anu would
not speak up till the end?
To be honest with you,
everything was unexpected.
You all were more adamant than I had expected.
Poor Anu. She tolerated
everything for so long.
You faced so many problems
because of me, didn't you?
What are you saying?
You did all this to protect us.
Dad!
The cops have come again, dad.
What is it?
Do you want to torture them again?
It's not like that.
- Why have you come then?
We've come here for Rambabu.
What happened, sir?
- It's nothing.
Is there an issue again?
- No, I'll manage. Don't worry.
I'll change my clothes and come.
She is not here today
as a police officer.
She has come here as a mother
who has lost her son.
Varun was our only child.
Maybe that's why we created a huge scene.
But
we never thought that
it would make us feel so guilty.
When we thought about the whole incident
being composed
we understood one thing.
We were wrong
to have not taught
the right values to our son.
We've hurt your family a lot.
We feel sorry.
Please forget about it and forgive us.
We're shifting abroad in a few days.
We're leaving behind everything here.
But there is one thing that's stopping us.
Every time the doorbell or the phone rings
we expect it to be Varun.
We feel heartbroken
every time we know that it's not him.
That's why I'm asking you.
Can we expect Varun
to come back some day?
I get it.
You don't trust us.
We're responsible for that.
Please forgive us
for causing you trouble.
Come on. Let's go.
You are very influential.
You knew you were wrong
and accepted your mistake.
That's a great thing.
I'm not that great.
I'm just a common man.
My family matters the most to me.
There's nothing else
that I value more than that
nor do I want to.
A stranger entered my life.
He tried to ruin the people
who meant the world to me.
He didn't agree though we begged him.
Things took an unexpected turn.
I was forced to get rid of him forever.
On that day, we didn't realize
that another family would also face a loss.
From that day on
we wanted to beg for forgiveness.
We even apologized.
We can't do anything else, sir.
Every man lives to see
his child's future secured.
No father can see his
child's future getting ruined.
Even I couldn't tolerate it.
You were humble enough
to confront us in person.
Please forgive us as well.
Rambabu,
the sub-inspector is calling you.
Sir, I'll keep my bag in the quarters.
- Okay.
Sir, this is Rambabu.
I know him. I've seen him
in the newspapers and on television.
Sign it.
Do you think the cops
won't trouble you anymore?
I'll be here for a few years.
I won't spare you
even if I find a small clue.
You'll be sent to jail directly.
Do you think the cops are fools?
- No, sir.
I never thought so.
I have a lot of respect
for the police department.
Because of people like you
the police station will protect me, sir.
We're completing the flooring
in the station.
Only the sub-inspector's room is left
to be done.
I'll help you once the work there
is finished on Monday.