FIDA
Good morning, America!
[FM radio playing]
"Good Morning! Hello, USA."
"You are known for your swift"
"Let it be a heartfelt journey"
Hey, bro! What's happening?
I am trying to make porridge.
Go ahead.
No! You do it.
Go and wake up Bujji.
Bujji!
Bujji dear...
Hey, idiot!
How many times should I tell you?
Who will go to school?
Bujji! this is the last time.
Who cares!
Lazy bug!
Raju bro, save me!
Raju bro, save me.
"Hey, Mister! Come, Mister! "
"Hey, Mister! Yo, Mister!"
"I got your back now"
"We three Kings to Jubilee Hills"
"Coming down! Can you feel them chills?"
"From Hyderabad to New York City!
We show you how Kings live"
"We bring that Telugu flavor"
"Bring it down. We are known for valor"
"Greetings, Homie!
They call me the Hustler"
"Go ahead! There is no choice"
"Time never waits for us"
"This race can never be avoided"
"Fulfill all your desires today,
one by one"
"Let your enthusiam fly up the roof"
"As you catch the attention of many"
-Hey! What's your plan tonight?
-I've got plans at home.
-Oh, OK.
-Bye.
"Let there be a lot of fun"
-Hey, Ali.
-Hey, Varun. Hi..
Hey, Suz.
Hey! It's high time.
You need to get married.
-I need a friend.
-And you need a wife.
We need a family.
OK.
Oh, yes!
-Yes.
Hey, bro! 2 daughters! Dad is a
farmer and the mother passed away.
She pursued M.A. Psychology
and her name is Renuka.
Her sister is Bhanumati. She is pursuing
second year in B.Sc. Agriculture.
The interesting part is
they don't care about caste.
-Ohh!
-Date of birth is 15th September.
Hey, September 15th.
-That is Mom's birthday.
-Yeah.
Hey, go and meet her immediately.
Don't miss her.
-Yeah. Let's go.
-My sixth sense says that she's the one.
OK. Finish your exams.
No need. You guys leave.
I will come later.
Yes!
We're coming, India. Yay!
Don't pinch your nails! They might
assume you are not confidennt.
Look straight into her eyes. Be confident.
Don't smoke. Girls do not like it.
Don't be so serious. Keep smiling.
These are Bujji's pills. Keep them safe.
Be confident, man. All the best.
Bloody idiot! Are you a snob?
I will smash you. Don't try to act smart.
Hey! You said that you have class
but you still came.
My sister has got an alliance.
My dad messaged me.
I have to check it out, right?
It is a match from America.
Oh, wow! She'll accompany me in America.
You'll stay here anyway. So...
Go away! All of you leave!
Many guys tried to impress you
but you didn't give them a chance.
All you need is a guy from America.
His stature and income
should be better than us.
That's my choice.
Background chorus:
Go... go...
She's my wife.
She passed away
when Bhanu was 10 years old.
Sister, come here.
She's my sister.
-Greetings!
-Hi.
Greetings!
She nurtured my kids.
Ours was an inter-caste marriage.
That is why we perform
such rituals at home.
Sister! Get something to eat.
Hey! Just sit back.
Hey, wait.
We are against dowry, dear.
We are not likely to support dowry.
You don't have to mention that.
It is better to discuss
everything beforehand.
There comes Renu.
She's Renuka. She studied M.A. Psychology
and is a gold medalist.
Do you guys want to talk?
Go inside and talk.
-Excuse me.
-Hey!
I am Bujji.
Even I want to take a look.
Don't you know Telugu?
Yeah, I know a little bit.
Give it here.
Why?
Nails are bad to keep at home.
I will throw it away.
-That's OK. I will throw it away.
-I will throw it. No problem.
-Just give it to me.
-It's OK.
-What's your name?
-Bhanu.
Man! This is funny shit.
I can't believe he is going to marry her.
That's right. This is just crap.
Crap?
It means shit in our language.
Cigarette?
Why?
I saw your profile picture.
I am asking because
I felt you might have that habit.
I can't do it here.
It is better to take a puff and
talk instead of sitting silently.
That's right.
Oh, man! They shut us up.
What do they do?
-Ah! Do they make out?
-What do you mean?
Would they kiss or something?
Shut up, idiot.
Sorry. I get tensed when I am with women.
I just needed the cigarette.
Are you OK with it?
I mean this arranged marriage.
Let me know if you're accepting
because of your dad or any pressure.
I will talk to your father.
I just want to clear this.
There is nothing like that.
I can talk to my dad
if I do not like the match.
You've got a Master degree in Arts, right?
-What are your hobbies?
-I sleep a lot.
You might have assumed that a village girl
will be homely, doing the house chores.
I just want to say that
I am not such a person.
Good! That's a very good hobby.
Interesting!
Whoa! What is this?
Help me out!
Please, help me out.
Hey!
That is just a buffalo.
Oh!
-Where do you get milk from?
-We buy it from the grocery store.
Come.
No! Don't take me there.
Let me go.
My brother will come and make a decision.
What?
Brother?
What's that, sister?
It will be a second
opinion if he sees her.
Second opinion?
What does he think of himself?
Let us reject the match.
We don't need this. Ask them to leave.
Arranged marriage itself is crap.
On top of it, there are conditions.
Sister! Reject him.
Shut up and eat.
They got no one.
That is why he said that.
It is better to think well
before the wedding.
We have to think twice. Not them.
Dad, you tell me. How can he say that?
Is she a thing?
We didn't make a decision yet.
Let's see. Let that guy come.
What are you thinking?
Sister!
You will have a hard time serving those 3.
They live in America.
We don't even know their food habits.
Will it be shown in movies?
He does not have a personal opinion.
Think about it again.
Shall I tell dad?
Shut up and sleep.
Dad asked us to wait until he comes.
There's no touch and feel.
How can you accept it?
Shut up and sleep.
Lizards?
Come. I will show you.
He said they are from a
farmer's family in a village.
Could she be so modern?
Could he be that handsome?
Not at all.
But, he said that her sister will come.
She could be the one.
He's average. Let me give it a try.
Groom's brother.
Yeah. That's me.
Sorry. I didn't recognize you.
It has been many days that I read Telugu.
Moreover, you were holding it upside down.
It was kind of crazy!
I am Varun.
Sorry.
I am not used to the cars in India.
Cars in America are so strong.
So...
-This is India, sir!
-Shall I drive?
Hey, I am Varun. And you?
I am the bride's sister.
Why do you sound so threatening?
Are you angry with me?
Do you have any problem?
Man! Damn roads! They never change.
Hello! These are our roads. We laid them.
We laid them the way we like.
Are you bothered?
No.
Right! Stay calm.
Everyone comments on the country.
Is it just you?
Or is your sister like you as well?
Don't say a thing about my sister.
She is precious.
Why are you laughing, man?
Is alliance a joke to you?
We had to go through many tensions.
Someone will come and
we should adorn ourselves for them.
We go through sleepless nights before
and after the meet.
How many of such alliances did you have?
You talk like an experienced person.
The groom won't simply tell his decision.
He wants his brother to see her.
That's when you come.
Is he crazy or what?
You can scold me but not my brother.
He is precious.
He's tensed.
That is why he needs a second opinion.
I should kill you.
It is my bad luck
to give a ride to such a guy.
I'm not enjoying the ride with you either.
I will get down. Stop the car.
Why did my brother stay at your house?
He should've booked a hotel room.
We offered and he stayed.
We did not plead him.
Let me get down. Please.
Stop the car.
My dad will kill me.
Why?
How can I insult the groom's family?
You came from afar.
I will follow you in an auto.
There's no need to tell him anything.
Please stop the car.
Seriously! Stop the car, OK.
Will you say that you do not like her
with this excuse?
The alliance is not a joke to us.
Hey! She agreed to wait until I came.
Your sister might have liked my brother.
You should respect that at least.
Hey! You know what?
You talk after yelling.
But, think well before you yell.
Try that. OK.
I don't have money.
-What for?
You are trying to preach me, right?
I don't take advice for free.
[chorus humming]
Yes!
No!
Hey, give me the chocolate back.
-No chocolates!
-Guys, listen.
I like Renuka very much.
I think I really like her.
Whoa! Finally!
Whoop!
Awesome, bro.
And you! You just go and say OK. Alright?
Then, why did you tell them that
I should make a decision?
Ouch!
They should know that
we are close to each other. Right?
She's a good person.
I don't know about her.
But, her sister is different.
I think she's kind of crazy, man.
She left me there.
Why are we staying here?
It would be nice to stay at a hotel.
They requested me a lot
and didn't let me go.
Listen! Just go and say OK.
Don't trouble them. OK.
OK, Chief.
Bujji, come.
-Yeah! We're getting our sister-in-law.
-Whoa! We're getting a sister-in-law.
Waiting for my decision is just a game.
You should accept him.
He is always caught up with work.
He doesn't socialize much.
He is a workaholic.
You take care of him and
we will take care of you.
-We do all the work. Right, Bujji?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
You can if you want to or study.
It will be nice there.
He likes you a lot.
He spoke highly of you.
You guys will be good together,
sister-in-law.
Can I call you that?
Yes.
Why don't you say
something about yourself?
There's nothing about me.
I am just an average guy.
He is special.
We're at this stage because of him.
He's our hero.
I didn't understand all of that
but they seem very nice to me, madam.
I doubt it. How can they be so nice?
We cannot trust them.
I have to test them.
-Hey.
How's it going?
Hey, bro! Meet my sister-in-law Renuka.
Sister-in-law! Meet my brother Raju.
Bro.
Bujji, let's go.
For you.
Hey, Bhanu!
What is it, Aunt?
Go fast and get eggs and
chickpea flour. Go.
Hustle up!
Can't you hear me?
Go fast.
Run!
I am going to the market. Will you come?
Will you come along with me to the market?
-Are you asking me to come?
You asked me out of the car yesterday.
But you're inviting me now. Is it okay?
Sir! Don't get any ideas.
I am doing this task for you.
That is why I asked you to come.
You are our guests.
We never know if you'll stay or leave.
All you can eat at this hour is an omelet.
That is why my aunt asked me to get eggs.
But, I got some work.
Come and see around the village.
Alright. Just give me a minute.
Whoa! What's wrong?
-Will you come like this?
-Why not? I am comfortable.
-Do you guys wear underpants around?
-These are shorts. Not underpants.
I dress according to the season.
Anyway! I am comfortable.
-Do you have an issue?
-I don't have any issue.
Girls in the village can't resist
seeing you like that with bare legs.
What do you do? I mean in America.
-I study medicine. I'm gonna be a doctor.
-Oh! Broiler Chicken?
Ah?
Everyone here is either
a doctor or an engineer.
That's it. Everyone will be the
same and think similarly.
Just like broiler chicken.
They study here and go to America.
That's for money!
Do you like money?
Do you get eggs for free?
Ah?
I mean do you get eggs without paying?
Oh! Smart!
Do you watch movies?
-Very few.
What about Power Star's movies?
-I saw -Gabbarsingh' movie.
-Sardar Gabbarsingh' movie?
-No!
The first one had a famous dialogue
'My craziness has a measure!'
You know. That one. Yeah.
That came long back, man.
You are not updated.
Does your brother watch movies?
-Hey! He doesn't watch them at all.
How can you even exist?
Why don't you watch movies?
She is crazy about movies.
No one stops sister-in-law.
She can watch them.
But, why are you feeling bad?
That'll be fun to be a fan of hero
Pawan Kalyan or Mahesh Babu.
It is awesome.
Two lovers watching favorite star's movie.
That's an awesome scene!
She's not lucky! We cannot help it.
This way?
-Do you booze or have girlfriends?
-What? Why do need that?
You sister is getting married to
my brother. You can ask him that.
You should take my interview.
But, it is wrong to think that
boozing or having girlfriends is bad.
Do you have any girlfriends
whom you had fun with?
Huh!
-Say it. Are you feeling shy?
You just don't give up. Do you?
Forget about me.
-Tell me about you. What do you do?
-B.Sc. Agriculture. We provide food.
-He's out! Who should bat next?'
-Hey, cricket!
Hold this. I will go and play.
Hey! How can you leave me halfway?
Are you passing your time with me?
-It has been many days that I played.
You go buy it. I will come after I play.
-Hey! Can I play?
-No! I won't let you.
Hey, please.
-I just started batting. I won't give it.
Hey! I'll give you a chocolate.
[omelette crackles]
Take it. It tastes nice.
-Have this omelet, son.
-Yeah! Thanks.
-Who's that?
-Groom's brother.
Have it now.
He's so handsome. Electrifying!
Be aware! He will leave you halfway.
A kind of broiler chicken!
He's from America.
-He's not the right fit for us.
-There's nothing wrong in staring at him.
My uncle's family stays in Vizag.
They'll come and finish the formalities.
I actually like Renu a lot.
Renu?
I have to leave America in a week.
So, the wedding should be done by then.
-Is it? Shouldn't we like them as well?
If she likes me...
It can happen in a week. I have exams.
-In a week? That's too early.
-We'll get her a visitor's visa.
I'm not sure when I will be free again.
That's the only request from my side.
In a week?
Can I have Gooseberry pickle?
He has very bad timing.
Sister.
Get that.
-Hey, Bhanu!
-Yes, aunt.
Go and get amla pickle from
Lakshmi aunt's house.
-Quick!
-OK.
-Run... go fast.
-Is he crazy? It's puring outside.
Listen! Go carefully.
Sister, where are they?
I went to get it even though it poured.
How can they finish eating?
-I'll get back to him.
-Leave it. He doesn't know about it.
Are you defending him already?
He must think of it. I'll go and ask him.
Bhanu...
Wait! Dad wants to talk to them.
Stay with me. I'm tensed.
It is about the groom.
Hey! What will you say?
Dad likes him. It's already late.
I have to get married anyway.
Don't tell me such cock-and-bull stories.
Please.
Say yes only if you like him.
You have to give medicine to
dad every day. Remember it.
-I'll tell dad...
-Bhanu...
-Dad!
-Bhanu, wait.
-Sister likes him.
-Just wait, Bhanu.
Sister likes him.
What's your din about? Stay calm.
Yes, it is. It is my sister's wedding.
I'll talk about it.
Come here, dear.
Dad likes him. It's already late.
I have to get married anyway.
Renu dear! Don't agree just
because of those reasons.
Think about it.
It will happen only if you want it to.
Dad! I told her the same.
I asked her in a similar manner.
Didn't I? Say it.
What did she say then, dear?
She said Yes. She said that she likes him.
That's enough.
She's my angel. She is so lucky.
I'm so happy, dear.
He's a good guy.
Who'll give me the medicine if you leave?
I'm there for you. Am I not?
You may leave.
It's just me and dad. That's it.
You too.
Stop it.
I'm worried, dad.
I have to leave in a week.
Why should girls leave their house
and everything?
Whoever started it did wrong.
It is cheating... Cheating!
People like you will be happy to leave.
No way. I will not leave.
I won't leave even after marriage.
I didn't even sleep here properly.
I am telling you, dad.
I am just like a son to you. That's it.
Shoo... Go...
Damn!
Hi.
[whistles]
Hey! You said you'd show me the village?
Is that all? Won't you show me?
That's your responsibility. You know.
We are your guests, right?
He has a really bad timing.
It's good that you reminded me.
Mallana temple in our village is famous.
Will you come?
Mallana temple? OK. Cool.
But, you have to get up early at 3 am.
Why?
That's a tradition.
-Can guys living in America do it?
-Yeah... no problem.
-You have to take a cold water shower.
-OK.
-Head bath!
You have to dress up traditionally
like in Tirupati.
-Dress?
-I will give you.
OK.
Take rest. You have to get up at 3, right?
-OK.
Sleep well.
-Good night.
Bloody lizards!
Lizards?
No...I couldn't sleep because of jet lag.
Are you going somewhere, dear?
Why'd you get ready?
Casually. Hello...
Come...
-Whoa! What are you wearing?
-Hey, Bujji.
You look like a clown.
-Just shut up.
-He must be the groom.
-Yes!
Listen! It's already late for marriage.
Don't delay in having kids.
I'm not the one.
[music]
Bhanu?
She's up there.
Hey! Why are you touching me?
You asked me to wake up early
and have a bath, right?
Oh, no! I totally forgot about it.
I didn't wake up.
Let's do it some other day.
-Hey, wait.
-Hey!
What about that traditional attire?
I heard there is no such tradition.
Hey! You look good in it.
You will feel free.
That's not the point.
How can you cheat like that?
Conspiracy!
I couldn't sleep because of the lizards.
-You asked for the pickle.
-Oh, man!
I tried so hard and got it.
Who will eat that now?
Did you keep that in mind?
Shall I tell your aunt?
Will you?
Will you tell my aunt?
I might. Suppose.
Oh, shit!
Did you click my pictures in the morning?
Don't say shit. Say 'bloody' instead.
You will feel good.
-Try it.
-You are crazy.
You look good.
I got many adult-rated pictures.
Care to watch them?
Where? Hey! Bhanu...
When did Indian girls change like this?
Don't generalize.
It is just me. Bhanumati! All in one.
A family with 2 religions and castes.
Hybrid girl!
You and your language of agriculture.
-Is your brother a good man?
-Why?
My sister is so good.
She's not like me.
She doesn't get angry or hurt anyone.
She is very good.
How about your brother?
We know that your sister is precious.
Don't you know how my brother is?
We do. But, there's a little fear.
Fear? Why?
She leaves us behind to come be with you.
Don't worry.
-Promise?
-Promise.
Hey!
When are you taking me to
Mallana temple?
Pray for it and it will come true.
Pray!
He is my brother-in-law's brother.
-It is beautiful.
-This is our village.
Wake up in the morning then I dab...
Thanks.
-I need toilet paper!
-You wait.
Hey, Bujji! Come here.
Toilet paper!
I need toilet paper.
-Here. Take water.
-No!
Bujji, no! Use water.
-Bujji, use water.
-Toilet paper.
-Hey, Bujji! Here...
-No!
Crazy!
There! It's there!
-Lizards won't come now.
-Thank you, Bhanu sis.
How's it?
Water from our well.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Good.
This land is 10 acres on the whole, Sir.
Including the area up there and under...
-What about that?
-Yeah. All of it.
-Greetings, Sir.
-Greetings.
This is the one, Sir.
-OK.
-Who are you? Are you the owner of it?
-No, Sir.
I leased it for farming.
It has been 20 years.
Take this, Sir.
Look at this. This is that bit.
It tastes good.
We get an amazing harvest, sir.
What do you get from it?
He's selling it, right?
I came to you regarding that, Sir.
You might construct a building. So,
I request you to get me a job there.
-Will you do the labor work?
-We don't have another choice, Sir.
It's OK, dad.
Hey!
Did you buy the lands?
We are still looking.
Its the land grandpa does farming in.
You don't think before buying.
You wouldn't stop until fields go barren.
You look amazing. Beautiful.
-Huh?
-Cool.
You might've never seen a
girl who sweats it out.
You must've only seen girls who
are glued to their gadgets.
Bloody! Have you gone crazy? Mad fellow!
Sorry. I wanted to see you. So...
Crazy!
You saw me near the well, right?
Shouldn't I see you?
Why'd you play such tricks?
You could just ask.
Ask for it and you'll get it.
Whoa!
"He's here. He's in no hurry"
"He worked his flattery"
"He won't let you stay calm or steady"
"He threw a smile at you"
"He gave you sleepless nights"
"He keeps hunger away by
disturbing you a lot"
"Renuka dear! Your man is here"
"He asks you out on a dinner date"
"He held your hand making
you go topsy-turvy"
"He's here. He's in no hurry"
"He worked his flattery"
"He won't let you stay calm or steady"
"He threw a smile at you"
"He gave you sleepless nights"
"He keeps hunger away by
disturbing you a lot"
"Renuka dear! Your man is here"
"He is here!"
"Men are tricksters! "
"Men are tricksters,
trying to impress you"
"You shouldn't be easy on them"
"Accept and reject his wishes at times"
"Maintain this and
he will stay with you for life"
"He's here. He's in no hurry"
"He worked his flattery"
"He won't let you stay calm or steady"
"He threw a smile at you"
"He gave you sleepless nights"
"He keeps hunger away by
disturbing you a lot"
"Oh, my! He's so tall! "
"Oh, my! How does one manage to kiss him?"
"He can't be reached unless
a ladder is in hand"
"I know the technique of
holding you by the waist to kiss you"
"Don't you worry"
"He's here. He's in no hurry"
"He worked his flattery"
"He won't let you stay calm or steady"
"He threw a smile at you"
"He gave you sleepless nights"
"He keeps hunger away by
disturbing you a lot"
How much did you study?
Shame on you!
Why'd you have to study so fast?
I just started.
Hey! Did you change already?
I will fail if I do not study.
Hey!
Your dance was too good. Awesome!
What's up with the land?
We bought the land
and gave it on lease to grandpa.
Grandpa is happy. The crop land
is in good hands and we're happy.
Real Estate agents won't
bother you anymore.
You did a good thing.
I didn't expect this from you.
I am impressed.
Ah?
Impressed!
Hey! Do you want me to
help with your exams?
I can read the chapter
and help you out.
Come that way.
Say it again.
You sounded great.
Alright. Give me a couple of minutes.
I will change and come.
Cool room!
Did you click my pictures from here?
Thanks.
So!
Draw these diagrams and graphs.
Yeah. OK.
-Can you do it?
-Yeah.
Will you understand anything
from copying and reading?
-You need to understand the concept.
-Get to it. I know what to do.
Oops!
Wait. I will give you the rubber.
-Give me what?
-A rubber...
Condoms are called rubbers in the US.
Shy, eh!
Is that making you shy?
Condoms are advertised
in India to avoid AIDS.
Millions are spent on
these advertisements.
Oh!
Looks like you are an expert at this.
Man!
Won't you let me be?
Everything seems likes a test.
Nothing like that.
Why do you care about what I think?
Bhanu! No one wants to be the
bad guy in front of girls.
Care for a tea?
Yeah.
Where's the tea powder?
Yeah. It's done.
Thank you.
Do you cook?
Not just cooking.
We take care of everything for Bujji.
Bathing, feeding, diaper changing!
Everything.
Sister-in-law won't have a problem
with that.
Was Bujji a late born child?
Actually...
My mom adopted him.
We wanted to adopt a baby girl.
But, that didn't work out.
My mom passed away
when Bujji was 2 years old.
She loved him like anything.
Does Bujji know?
He knows.
Actually, he talks about it with pride.
He feels we were simply born
where as he was chosen by mom.
I was doubtful about you
guys but it's cleared.
She'll be happy. I can sense that.
You always think in favour of your sister.
Don't you notice us? Is that it?
Does your world revolve around her?
OK. Forget about your sister.
What do you think about me?
Why?
Hey! Just say it.
Oh, my!
I'll fail in my exam. Shall we start?
OK. Let's go.
So, the earthworm helps the farmers
by preventing soil erosion...
...and they help to discern the soil.
I have to give medicine to my dad.
I am leaving.
Hey! We are going to
your collegeat 9, right?
Dad! Get up.
-What is it, dear?
-Pills.
Sorry, dad.
I forgot about it. It is my mistake.
Why are you acting like a kid?
You have an exam tomorrow.
Go and sleep.
Sorry, dad.
I wasn't mindful.
Dad! I am your precious one, right?
You are very precious. You are my life.
I will always be with you.
I won't go anywhere.
We have our land, Mallana temple,
and our village.
Hey, go!
Go. Hey, you!
I am not going anywhere.
Did he come to your room?
Oh, my gosh!
You won't let anyone into
your room, right?
So, do you like him?
It was a weak moment.
He disturbs me a lot.
One reason!
I need just one reason
to get him off my mind.
He's not the right one for me.
I can't leave everything behind for him.
Stay with me.
I will say that we're going
to the exam together.
Ah?
I only asked him to come
along to our college.
I get it! Weak moment, am I right?
No! I see danger. Let's go.
Hey! He's here. Look...
My heart is pounding.
Look... It's okay.
Just take a look.
He came for you. Don't
make yourself look bad.
-Let's go. We might be late for our exam.
-OK. Let's get changed.
Now?
How can we go like this?
Look at your dress.
Guys will tease you if you go like this.
You know Naresh is
always staring at you.
We don't have time. He might come.
Let's go.
Hey, Bhanu!
Bhanu!
Have you seen the question paper, man?'
Have you seen Bhanu?'
-Have you seen her mole?
-No, buddy.
I can't resist touching her.
-Soil strain?
-Yeah. I wrote that one.
Hey.
-Hi.
What are you doing here?
If I don't show up,
you might blame me.
Bye.
Just kidding.
I came because I was bored.
I got the same question I recited to you.
-Is it? Nice.
-Yeah it was good.
-How did you write your exam?
-I did well.
Hey, dude!
What's this? Shall we get out of here?
Do you want to leave? Won't you hit him?
Come. Let me show you my college.
Biryani in our cafeteria tastes great.
Hey, Bhanu! How'd you write your exam?
Yes!
Filthy dogs!
They tease me every day.
Let's go to the cafeteria.
There will be people around.
-Hey, Bhanu! How'd you write your exam?
-I did well.
Did you, rerally?
I want to break their bones.
You eat.
Pray for it and it might happen.
Where's the rest room?
-Go straight and take left.
-OK. I'll just be back.
Hey, your man is electrifying!
Everyone is talking about him.
Shut up.
No way.
He is a coward. Not gutsy at all.
He wanted to leave when
Naresh was teasing me.
I can get him off my mind now.
What do you mean?
Is it because he didn't put up a fight?
Maybe he knows how to handle things.
-Speaking in his defence?
I am trying hard to get him off my mind.
He is stuck in there.
This excuse is enough for me.
I will delete him from my mind.
The game is over.
-Is that your final word?
-Hmm...
Hey!
Hey! What was the need to touch her?
Did you have to
Why do you care about that mole?
Like, seriously?
You better focus on studies.
Hey, wait.
Pick those papers up.
Pick them up.
-Hey! I said, pick them up.
-Hey, pick them up.
It hurts, Sir. Please leave me.
Does it hurt?
Answer this and I will leave you.
Why are earth worms and
farmers good friends?
They help in the
prevention of soil erosion.
They aid in having a
good harvest as well.
Good answer.
Are they spoiling you?
Go and study.
You've got so many moles.
Is that why you're so interested, huh?
He took a chance and got doomed.
He's so strong, girl.
Hey!
You hit them well.
Were their bones broken?
No! It's not that bad.
They're safe.
What do you eat, man?
I have oat meal for breakfast
and then vegetables.
Lots of chicken
or fish in the afternoon...
One reason! God!
Just give me one good reason.
Hey.
Stay with me.
We came together. So,
let's go back together.
I can't resist anymore.
Don't think too much.
I will catch a train.
You won't get this chance again.
Enjoy the moment happily.
Look at your face. It's glowing!
Go.
Hey!
Wait up...
"Hey, man! What have you done, man?"
"There's chaos in my heart"
"Hey, hero!
Stop teasing me, you tough one"
"You make my heart feel tingled"
"Your heart keeps twirling around"
"It feels hurly-burly
no matter what you do"
"Hey, man! What have you done, man?"
"There's chaos in my heart"
"Hey, hero! Stop teasing me, knotty guy"
"You've disturbed all my heart"
"Dew drops groove with you"
"in the form of drizzling rain"
"Heart flows like a cascading stream"
"It reminisces your caressing presence"
"This rain makes me feel swooned"
"I wonder what's happening within"
"You never realize the
anxiety inside of you"
"I'm all wet with the showers of love"
"Hey, man! What's this, man?"
"There's confusion in my heart"
"Hey, hero! Stop teasing me, knotty guy"
"You've disturbed all my heart"
"The mishmash in you is filled
with fortunate twirls"
"You cannot get it no matter
what you do"
Hey, brother-in-law! So good to see you.
How are you?
I missed you a lot.
Who's she?
Who's she? She is my uncle's daughter.
Her name is Sailu.
She is from Hyderabad.
She is going to come to the US.
OK. Bye.
Don't look at them. No... No...
Damn!
Ramireddy! Go to that side.
Why are you late? Make it fast.
Hey, Bhanu! Station master
asked us to come. Shall we go?
We will book the
entire compartment beforehand.
We need time to decorate it.
Oh! OK.
Sister-in-law.
Bujji!
Ta-da! This is for you.
They belong to my mom.
We waited long for this day.
All of it for your sister-in-law?
Won't you save some for your wedding?
See you, sister-in-law.
What is this, sister?
Hari, Isn't it done yet?
-I have no idea how to tie this.
-Uncle! Help him wear it.
Thanks, uncle.
[wedding chants]
Bujji, come.
Wait, sister-in-law! I'll help you.
Oh! Thank you.
Thank you.
Give it here.
Food is served over there.
Yay!
Have more, Ramulamma.
Oh!
Fritters?
-No! I don't want it.
-Have it, brother-in-law. Please serve.
-No, Bhanu. I don't want it.
Have it, brother-in-law.
I am telling you, right?
-Have it.
-Stop overacting.
Why don't you have it for me.
"All the Goddesses look upon you"
"May they guard you with their blessings"
"There shall not be tears
or agony in your eyes"
"All your dreams will come true
with their grace"
I wish your mom was alive to see this.
-Do you want this, sis?
-Yeah.
Bhanu!
We're packing luggage separately
for the first time.
It doesn't feel good.
I don't feel good at all.
Why do you have to go?
Why should girls leave
everything behind and go?
Why don't you ask brother-in-law?
He is a good man.
Try asking him. He might stay back here.
Such things exist only in
dreams, not in reality.
Why don't you try asking him?
Prince Charming comes on a
horse to take his Princess along.
He would't stay back at her palace.
-Shut up.
You try convincing me instead of him.
Isn't it tough for you, sister?
Are you not worried?
How will you endure it?
Trust!
I trust him.
It just happens. We can endure
anything and everything.
Ask him to stay back
with that very belief.
OK. You can ask your Prince
Charming when it's your time.
Will you propose and ask him to stay back?
Is that your plan?
Hmm.
You'll have your conditions, right?
You think it will work out?
He's a doctor in America.
So, think about it.
We shouldn't propose first.
They'll take us for granted.
They'll get dominative.
What if he rejects you?
He cannot reject me.
That's out of question.
Hey, Bhanu! Where is my coffee?
It is on the way.
The station master called up.
He asked us to come.
OK. Cool.
Varun.
-Hi, Bhanu sis...
-Here's your shampoo.
-Thanks.
We shall sit together on the train.
Don't go anywhere.
OK.
I'll be in the second class coach.
I have to ask you something
and it is very important.
OK.
Hey, Bhanu! Come here.
What happened?
Nothing.
Don't forget. My coach is S8.
OK.
Sister!
-What is it?
She's trying to be smart.
She arranged for their
first night on the train.
Aren't you ashamed?
I didn't do it.
It was Varun's idea and I helped him.
There are auspicious
moments for such things.
It can't happen wherever you plan it.
Tell that guy.
Hey! Come here!
You don't have to say it. I will tell him.
You go along with your sister in the car.
They will go by train.
Let's go.
Do you get it?
Hey!
Take care, dear.
OK, then.
OK.
-Yeah.
-Yes!
We planned to perform rituals at
my uncle's house.
Brother-in-law! I will go by train.
-You guys enjoy.
-Hey!
OK. Go.
Why?
She wants to go, right? Let her go.
Bye!
Hey, Bhanu! What are you doing here?
Brother-in-law wants privacy.
He asked me to go by train.
Tell me this. Are they
happy together, dear?
Have some water.
Sister.
-I don't get it.
-Don't think like an oldie, aunt.
They need to have moments together.
I'll be right back.
Bujji.
Goodnight.
Where is Varun?
He's with Sailu.
Sailu! Let me think.
Wait. Let me think.
Don't worry. I will tell you.
Give this to the groom's family.
-OK.
-Lemon rice is so good.
-I will go along.
Veeru! Let me come with you. Wait.
Come.
See.
Dinner, Sir.
No.
You might feel hungry. Have some.
Are you really hungry, brother-in-law?
We don't want anything.
Let's go.
Have a banana.
What is it?
Bujji didn't have anything.
He might have it.
Sailu! India has nothing to
offer the doctors. Just come.
I will take care of the visa
and university applications.
There's nothing here but lizards,
buffaloes and dirty roads.
It is OK for a vacation.
You can pass time in the
fields on a tractor.
You career is at stakes if you stay here.
I will talk to your family.
Trust me. Just come.
Let's plan the wedding later.
-OK?
-OK, brother-in-law.
I trust you.
Love perished even before it bloomed.
I don't have to look
for any more excuses.
What is it, dear?
What are you doing here?
Are you missing your sister?
There's nothing like that, dad.
Nothing like that.
I got you. That is enough for me.
I will stay here with you.
My darling daughter!
You are a sweetheart.
Aren't you dear?
Greetings.
Come, dear.
-Give it to me.
-No!
Go and get it.
Hey, Bhanu.
Sister! He is calling you.
Is everything OK?
You know you're our guests now, right?
Do you want some coffee, tea or anything?
Hey.
[performing rituals]
Hey, what happened?
-I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
-Just a minute.
Sister.
Bhanu! Are you here?
We placed our luggage in the
room upstairs. Keep an eye.
-Lentils broth.
-Fritters.
Shall I serve lentils broth?
Will you have it?
Have it.
-Bhanu! Fritters...
-No! I don't want it.
-Have it. It will be good.
-I don't want it.
This is lemon rice.
You call it yellow rice.
Taste it.
-What happened?
-Serve me a fritter.
That's enough.
See you, dad.
Brother-in-law.
Hey! What's up with this?
Bujji.
Thanks.
-Dad!
-Dear.
-Take care, dad.
-You too take care, dear.
See you, aunt.
-See you, father-in-law.
-Bujji! Bye.
Here. Take your bag.
Where is Bhanu?
Ask her to come.
We're getting late. Let's go.
"She neither lets me think nor calm down"
"She neither stays nor leaves"
"I am bound by captivity"
"I could neither feel anything
nor fall asleep"
"She neither leaves nor reaches out"
"I wonder when I'll be free of worry"
Happy married life, Raja.
-Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
-How was the wedding?
He is Ali. Varun's friend.
-How about your journey?
Hey, kiddo!
"She neither lets me think nor calm down"
"She neither stays nor leaves"
"I am bound by captivity"
"I could neither feel anything
nor fall asleep"
"She neither leaves nor reaches out"
"I wonder when I'll be free of worry"
"My life is slipping out of control"
"This suffering is inevitable"
How was your journey?
Yeah, dad.
-Sister-in-law! Give that to me.
"Heart's racing to be in your presence"
Did you water my plants?
-Sister-in-law! Is it Bhanu?
It's good here.
-Give it to me.
I am watering them.
-How's Sumathi doing?
Sister-in-law.
Hello.
Bhanu!
Bhanu! This is the picture of
Narsing Rao's son.
He saw you at the wedding and liked you.
Her mother wants to know your opinion. It
hasn't been 2 days since ister's wedding.
You are already bothering me.
Send me away. Send me away as well.
"I can neither endure it nor comprehend"
"I can neither stop nor glide toward you"
"It's a feeling never reminisced"
"I can neither be in the
moment nor take a chance"
"I can neither live this
dream nor pacify myself"
Hi...
Next will be your wedding.
"My life is slipping out of control"
"This suffering is inevitable"
"Heart's racing to be in your presence"
"It's a thought that haunts you"
"Your presence caresses me
even in my sleep"
"I get forgetful and look for myself"
"The anxiety in my heart
makes me restless"
"I shall express my feelings
to you someday"
"Your voice calls out like chasing dreams"
"That trance has tangled
me like consciousness"
"The anxiety in my heart
makes me restless"
"I shall express my feelings
to you someday"
"Your thoughts never let go of me"
Sister-in-law! Let me take it.
What are you making?
-I am baking a cake. Bujji asked for it.
-Oh!
Will you have coffee? I will make it.
-Let me do it. Do you want it?
-OK.
Sister-in-law! Are you
missing your village?
Hmm...
What about Bhanu?
I miss her a lot. She's a chatterbox.
She's fiery!
-It'd be nice if she comes here, right?
-It will be great.
But, how? That won't happen.
Sister-in-law! I actually proposed Bhanu.
What?
I proposed Bhanu.
-Did you propose to her?
-Did you say I love you to her?
-Yes, sister-in-law.
That's the great news.
Bhanu will get married and come here.
Why didn't you tell me earlier, Varun?
Oh! Are you feeling shy?
I had a doubt on you guys.
But, I didn't know that
you guys are so serious about it.
You guys look great as a coupe.
I will call her.
Sister-in-law!
-Where is my phone?
I am waiting for her response.
Is it Bhanu?
What happened?
Why don't you say something?
What happened? What did she send?
What happened, Varun?
It is my first love and first message
to someone.
I haven't liked anyone as much as her.
She rejected me and that's clear.
You just wait. I will tell her.
I will talk to her.
What's this? Are you out of mind?
What do you think of yourself?
How can hurt him like that?
Think about it. Varun is a nice guy.
He proposed to me and I responded.
What's wrong with that?
How can you that you're not interested?
Why did you send a
picture of your footwear?
I am not interested and I just said that.
Do you need clarity?
Everyone likes him. He is a darling.
Girls are crazy about him. I know it.
That's great. Keep supporting him.
He is your brother-in-law, right?
I don't need him.
I am not someone here for time pass.
Why do you talk about time pass?
That's strange.
My beloved sister!
Please give it a second thought.
Guys cannot be trusted.
You're lucky that he likes you.
I don't want to be that lucky.
I do not like him and that is final.
Hello? Hello!
Sister-in-law! What did she say?
She is crazy. But, you don't worry.
Congratulations on your first love.
Congratulations, my friend.
Hello! Congratulations.
Bro!
Footwear? Why did she send that?
She kicked my proposal.
Did she reject you?
Hey! There are many girls
who are crazy about her.
Forget about her.
Sister-in-law!
Don't tell anything to brother.
He might feel bad.
There'll be unnecessary mess.
Hey! Hey, Ali!
Take them all away from here.
Sister-in-law! Go.
What's that?
-It is my take-away Biryani.
Hey! What happened?
Have dinner first and then cake.
What happened to him?
-Nothing. Will you have cake or rice?
He can't wait.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. There's nothing.
Sister-in-law!
Sister-in-law she's not ignoring my calls.
Ask her to attend my calls.
At least she should tell me
what has happened, right?
I will talk to her.
[phone buzzes]
OK. Note down the composition of
zinc-sulphate.
Hello, Bhanu.
Please don't do that.
Talk to him for once at least for my sake.
My dear, listen!
He is your brother-in-law's brother.
How can you do that to him?
OK! Stop it. I will talk to him.
Talk to him now. Call him.
Bhanu? Bhanu.
Bhanu, are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
Why do have such an ego?
Hey! At least pick my God damn phone.
Hello, Bhanu. Bhanu?
Don't shout. Tell me.
Shouting? Am I shouting?
Do you know what you've done?
Why? Tell me. Why?
I don't like you, Varun.
That is the reason. Is that OK?
Varun! Varun?
Varun.
It has been many days
that you called me like that.
I don't like you.
Why?
There is no reason.
I don't believe this.
It is not acceptable.
You like me.
I could sense it.
We had moments, Bhanu.
That day in your room.
What happened suddenly?
-See you. I have to attend my class.
-Class? Useless class.
It is my life.It is my freaking life.
What do you think about me?
I am a doctor from
one of the tops schools in America.
Millions! I earn millions.
You are simply a village
girl who does farming.
Huh?
Average! No, you are below average girl.
Are you dizzy?
Do you know what you're doing?
What should I do with the
picture of your footwear?
Can you find a person like me?
Can you find anyone
who could match my range?
Bhanu? Bhanu, are you there?
Hello? Bhanu.
Hello!
My class is useless,
my tractor is useless,
And I am an average girl.
Sorry. I am below average. Is that right?
Is that what you said?
Forget about someone
who could match your range.
I will find a much better person
than you very easily. Wait and see.
-Bhanu.
-OK. Bye.
Hello. Bhanu!
Oh, God!
Can you find a person like me?
Can you find anyone
who could match my range?
-Have we received the email?
-No, Sir.
-Hey! Call my mom.
-No! I came for you.
-We will meet you later, Sir.
-OK.
-We'll meet tomorrow.
-Yeah. OK.
Yeah. Thank you.
See you, Sir.
-Have a seat.
-Thanks.
-I am Bhanu. I stay nearby.
-Yeah. I know!
Can I take a selfie with you?
-You did your studies from London, right?
-Yes.
You studied there but
started your business here in our village.
Yeah. Farmer!
You're so great.
That is why I want a selfie with you.
OK.
Thank you.
Left or right? OK.
-What is Bhanu doing here?
-Hey! Why do you care?
-Say it, bro.
-Who's that? She is Bhanu, right?
Mom! She says that I am great. So,
she came here to take a selfie with me.
-Oh! Selfie?
-Oh!
You have to get up early at 3 am.
That's a tradition.
You have to bath with cold water.
Can guys living in America do it?'
Sister-in-law!
Is Bhanu really your sister?
What happened?
She is so violent, sister-in-law.
She's made me violent as well.
Varun! Please don't feel bad.
She's like that.
You know about her, right?
Don't be sad. It does not feel good here.
She is crazy. She's always at pace.
She understands it slowly.
I will talk to her.
There should be some
limit to her craziness.
She does not have any limits.
She is just crazy.
She tortures me, sister-in-law.
Oh, shit!
Hi, sister-in-law!
Here are your curry leaves and vegetables.
I took an appointment for driving classes.
Get ready.
Will you have crepe?
Did he eat?
-No.
I will have crepes.
What is it?
Did you get a picture of footwear?
Who is he?
Cry! Simply cry.
Become a slave of her heart!
Shall I get a drink and a pet?
That's curry leaf.
You are just that for her.
She's a village girl.
She found a guy so easily.
You are in America but there is no use.
It is a shame to Americans.
Trump might feel bad.
She cannot understand, dude.
Call up Suzie.
See this. See it clearly.
She took a close selfie with him.
Call her.
Are you sure?
I am not asking you to love her.
Send her a picture with Suzie.
OK.
Hey, Suz! How are you doing?
Do you want to catch up tonight?
Oh! This looks so good.
Thanks for calling me.
So, let me tell a little about myself.
My mom is from Hungary and
my dad is from Slovakia.
Two lovers watching favorite star's movie.
That's an awesome scene!
I had a really good time.
-Yeah me too. Thanks for everything Varun.
-Yeah.
Do you have such girlfriends
with whom you had fun with?
Couldn't you even kiss her?
You couldn't kiss Suzie.
Your love is true. But,
that crazy girl cannot understand that.
I am totally impressed.
I can't take her out of my mind.
We dream to live with someone for life.
She's that woman.
She's the one.
Every day will be new.
No one knows what she is up to and
it is not so easy to understand her.
It is like a thriller story.
That isn't a thriller story
but a horror story.
-You cannot rely on her.
-Hey!
Hello.
-Hello.
Hello. Who is it?
This is Ali from America.
Your sister is my sister-in-law as well.
I don't believe that you are her sister.
You are torturing him.
Do you think he has no one?
There are many girls
who are ready to kiss him.
Is it? Call up someone from
Guinness world records.
Why are you calling me?
What? Guinness world records?
This is definitely a horror story.
Let me show her.
Let us take a selfie.
Let this Saturday be an occasion for us.
It is just a small celebration. OK.
Close your eyes.
-Why should I close my eyes?
Do what I say.
Mom! She is here.
Hey, Bhanu.
She is Bhanu.
Hi.
They're family of Narsing Rao.
They came for you.
Did you take a selfie with that guy?
I just took a selfie.
Why should I marry for that?
What is this?
Kill me. Crazy!
You want to stay with your dad, right?
They live close by.
What else do you need?
That guy is handsome.
Hey! I do not like it.
Who is he, sister-in-law?
Who is he?
Aunt talked about a match.
He must be the one.
They liked her.
Did she get ready for the wedding?
So soon?
There's nothing like that. She should
be ready for the wedding, right?
You know about her. She is crazy.
Don't worry.
Varun! Are you fine?
You go and sleep, sister-in-law.
Sorry.
Varun!
You do not sleep properly.
I am unable to sleep, sister-in-law.
You sleep, sister-in-law. Goodnight.
Sorry. Goodnight.
Aunt!
Hello.
Bhanu's match got fixed, dear.
Is it?
Hey! It seems Bhanu's match is fixed.
That's good to know, father-in-law.
What does the groom do?
He studied in London, dear.
This is a very good match, dear.
Yeah, dad.
Your sister's wedding is confirmed, dear.
Hand over the phone to her.
Here. Your sister is on call.
What's this? Have you gone crazy?
Do you know what you're doing?
Why are you so hasty?
Do you really like him?
Don't be foolish, Bhanu.
Listen to me, my darling.
Sister!
I asked what something that
you like about brother-in-law is.
Do you remember?
Why are you talking about that now?
Let me say it.
You talked about trust.
I do not trust your brother-in-law.
Hello? Bhanu!
-Mr. Raju.
-Yeah.
Mrs. Raju.
Congratulations!
You are going to be parents.
Wow!
Thank you so much.
Come.
I am so happy.
-You come with me.
Make sure to take care of everything.
Hey, Varun! I will get the car.
You guys come down.
Just wait.
Be sure to watch her food
you should be very careful.
Make sure she has a very good diet.
Hey, doctor.
-Hello.
Sister-in-law!
What happened, sister-in-law?
Forget about Bhanu, Varun.
She is not so special.
She is not as special as you.
It will be good to be
with her for a few days.
But, she is stubborn and crazy.
You know it, right?
She is not so beautiful as well.
She had relations with
many at her college.
Sister-in-law! You are lying.
What else should I do, Varun?
I cannot see you like this.
What should I do?
I tried to convince her but
she doesn't listen to me.
She does what she wants.
You are worried about her.
She agreed to get married.
Marriage?
-Dad told me.
-Oh, Shit.
You are getting worried and
spoiling your mind.
You don't eat or sleep well.
Tell me what I should do.
Let it be, sister-in-law.
She's out from and my mind and
my heart from this moment.
You wept for me and
made her low before me.
Can't I forget her?
I can forget her easily, sister-in-law.
We have you and there'll be a baby.
That is enough.
I'll be happy.
Don't worry about me, sister-in-law.
Take rest. Don't think about anything.
OK.
[chorus singing]
I am out of words, Renu dear.
I am so happy.
Everything good happens to us.
You'll be a mom and
she is getting married.
"The lush green village
welcomes dawn with celebration"
"As the floret idol is placed"
"Prayers are made to the sacred
Goddess to shower her mercy"
"A girl child brings
luster in her parent's eyes"
"All the delicacies make eveyone crave"
"Guys wakes up early to gather flowers"
-Hi, Bhanu! You are looking beautiful.
-Hi.
"Girls decorate the divine floret idol"
-Shall we take a selfie?
-Hmm.
Come.
"Prayers are made to the sacred
Goddess to shower her mercy"
OK. We'll take from the left side.
Thank you.
What happened, Bhanu?
Where are you going?
What is it? Why did you walk away?
There is no chemistry between us.
Chemistry? What do you mean by that?
He held my waist.
I didn't like it.
There should be some feeling, right?
-I have to get impressed.
-You can feel it after getting married.
What if that doesn't happen?
How can you get impressed with
just one touch and start enjoying?
Stop it. Don't have such expectations.
They're not just expectations.
It is way beyond that.
You silly! Everyone talks like that
but they get married.
I am telling you, it feels like that.
Bloody idiot!
You went back to America and
you enjoying with girls.
I am feeling that torture. Damn!
Yeah. Are you feeling pain here?
-Yeah.
Yeah, Sir. See this on the scan.
You need to take some bed rest.
Bhanu dear!
-What is it, dad?
Your sister needs bed rest for 3 months.
She should take proper care.
Raju is worried.
He asked me to send your aunt.
I want you to go there, dear.
Will you go?
Me?
Should I go to America?
I cannot go to America, dad.
Leave it. Let aunt go.
She can't go. She will not be comfortable
with the flight journey.
It will be nice if you go.
You cannot understand, dad. I can't go.
You say that you are everything to me.
Try to be her mother.
Mom would've done it.
She's all alone there, dear.
Don't worry.
Nothing will happen if even she comes.
Be strong.
I am there with you. Shave your beard.
Try to look good.
-OK.
Suzie is your girlfriend.
She is your girlfriend and it should
be shown that way. Do you get it?
She sent a picture of her footwear, right?
Keep it with you.
I can give another symbolic representation
that you're nothing.
Mark my words!
Be strong.
It is just me. Bhanumati! All in one.
You might've never seen a girl like me
who works hard.
You saw girls who work in AC rooms
with several gadgets.
Hey! How are you?
I am good. How about you?
I am good. I am actually happy.
You look strange.
Ah?
Braided hair is not suitable
while wearing jeans.
It is not good.
-They will not arrest me for that.
-Hey, Suz!
-Hey!
That's Bhanu.
Hi, I am Suzie.
-Hi, I am Bhanu.
Nice to meet you.
Hey! Could you open the trunk?
-Yeah. Absolutely.
Bhanu! That is Suzie. She's my girlfriend.
She is my girlfriend.
Oh!
So, awesome! How'd you like it?
Will you have palm shoots?
No. Thanks.
You told my aunt that you like them,
right?
She asked me to give you.
That is why I offered.
Do you want to eat?
-Oh! Yeah. Sure.
Yeah. It is interesting.
-That's fibre.
Yeah. Thank you.
-They don't allow it. How did you get it?
Nothing will happen to this place.
Hey.
You denied already.
-Give.
Bujji.
-Yeah. You are finally here, Bhanu.
Suzie!
-Hi. How are you?
I am good.
Alright, Suz.
-Bye.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
-OK, Bye.
Take care. Bye.
-Bye! Thank you.
Oh! Bye. No problem. See you later.
By the way, I really like your style.
The braid, the bindi, and jeans!
It really suits you.
-Hey, Suz! Aren't you getting late?
-OK. See you later.
-Bye!
Yeah. Bye!
Brother-in-law!
-Hey, Bhanu!
How are you?
-I am good. How are you?
I am good. Where is sister?
-She's over there.
Hey, Ali! What are you doing here?
-Raju asked me to get Biryani.
Moreover, I am excited to see this girl.
Did she get shocked looking at Suzie?
She is a village girl but looks good.
She's average.
Listen! Maintain your attitude.
I'll be there for you.
OK. Let's go.
How are you?
-I am good.
How's the baby?
I placed your luggage in
the room upstairs. OK?
Hey! I got something for you. Wait.
Hey, wait. Freshen up and
eat something.
Bujji! This is for you.
Sister! These are for both of you.
-What is this?
This is for you.
Its OK. No need for that.
I don't want any gift.
Its OK.
Try it like this.
You own a restaurant, right?
Place this at the counter.
Look at it whenever you are stressed
and you'll feel good.
You will be calm.
Stress?
You are the first one
who worried about my stress, Bhanu.
Great. Thank you.
I will be there for you in America.
Our friendship will be there lifelong.
I am there for you.
Sister-in-law! Your sister is amazing.
Hey, Varun! She has a point.
She didn't like you and
that is what she said. It is fair.
You better be with Suzie. That's it.
-Hey!
But, there is something about her.
I am impressed within moments.
You are in love with her. I can
understand that it is hard to forget her.
I pity you. I feel you. I get you, bro.
Why should I care about what you feel,
you idiot?
You're my friend. You are my freaking
friend. You have to support me.
Don't you understand my suffering?
Hey, Varun! You got Suzie.
-Hey!
Shit.
But, I promised her, dude.
Sister, look what he's doing.
Hey! Give these pills before
breakfast and these after breakfast.
Give these after lunch and
these pills after dinner.
Sister-in-law! Your food is ready.
Won'tyou eat?
No, sister-in-law. I will have it later.
I have to study. You guys have it.
Did you reach safely?
What's the time there?
-It is 11 pm. Did you take medicine?
Who will give me when you're away.
-Dad!
I took them, dear.
Bhanu dear! I am missing you guys.
Both of you aren't with me.
You are the one who sent me.
I feel the same.
It is getting for you. Sleep.
OK, dad.
Bhanu. Hey!
I will show you the kitchen.
Milk and juices will be inside this.
Coffee cups and powders
are in this cupboard.
This is the grinder and
this is a coffee machine.
-That is jet lag, Bhanu. Nothing serious.
-I know.
This is dishwasher and that is a toaster.
Where is my gift?
You got something for me, right?
-You denied taking it.
Man!
Why?
Bloody shameless bugger. Is it needed?
O' God!
You sit in the front seat, Bhanu.
Bye, Bhanu.
Thank you.
Hey, no problem. I will clean my room.
It looks good on you.
[Karaoke to Pilla nuvvu leni
jeevitham song from film Gabbar Singh]
Come on, dance.
"He's here. He came with a low pace"
"He tricked with a lovely trap"
"He won't let you be calm and be steady"
"He gave a smile that
led to sleeplessness"
Kids! Just keep it a little low.
This is America. Not Banswada.
You enjoyed
when I danced back in Banswada.
You were good back then.
But, you're bad now.
Yeah. It's turkey time.
Yeah. The turkey is ready.
-The turkey is ready.
The turkey is here.
What's so special about it?
It is like a broiler chicken.
What? Broiler chicken?
Wow!
That's Suzie. You can go ahead
for a committed relationship.
Wow! You look stunning.
-Thank you so much.
-You're so beautiful.
Thank you. It was all her.
No. Hey! I just figured
that you can carry any dress very well.
-But, she can't carry yours.
-Varun! That is not true.
She would do so beautifully.
That is so mean. Come on.
She looks good. Doesn't she?
Ouch!
Hey, Suz! Are you OK?
Oh, my God! Is everything OK?
Suzie! Are you OK?
-Varun! What happened to you?
-Go away.
Suzie, are you alright?
-Yeah. I am fine, Varun. Thanks.
-Is it OK?
-Nothing will happen, Bhanu.
Everything will be alright.
Hey! What happened?
Why did you get Bhanu to that place? Why?
Kill her, both of you.
I would be in the prison
if something happened to her.
I'd behind the bars.
She wanted to have fun.
So, I brought her to the party.
Why should there be fun?
Who bought her this dress? Was it you?
She liked it when we went shopping.
So, I bought it.
Shut up, man! Are you even my friend?
Bringing her here will make me furious.
But, you did. Can't you understand?
Varun! Scold me if you want.
You are angry with me.
What has he done?
-Why are you telling me?
-He is my friend.
-That is my wish. You just shut up.
-Why should I be calm?
You have a problem with me.
I've been noticing from the day I came.
You don't want me to stay here.
Yes. You are right.
I don't want you to come to America.
I don't want you to visit our house.
I don't like it at all that you came here.
I dropped Suzie after seeing you.
What did I do?
-You dropped her. Why are you scolding me?
-This is all because of you.
What's this dress?
Did you ever wear such a dress?
Do you know how you look in it?
I will wear it. I will wear it for sure
and whatever I want.
Don't look at me if you have any problem.
You never talk to me properly.
You always ill-treat me.
You have to be straight forward.
You should be gutsy.
I am gutsy and I express my feelings.
That is my character.
I don't different kinds of emotions.
I've known a lot about your character
in the coach and in pictures.
-I've seen a lot.
-What?
Coach? You mean Sailu and I?
Damn!
Can you think like that just because
I am with a girl?
How can you get to conclusions?
You made me bad and rejected my love.
Just like that.
-Do you want to talk with Sailu?
-I don't care.
You definitely care.
That is why you came.
You came even though I denied.
I came to see my sister.
I'm not here for you.
Then, why did you wear this dress?
Whom did you wear it for? Why?
Why did you come to me wearing it?
It is not for you.
I will leave right now
if you talk like that.
Go, please. I please you to leave.
I plead you. Go.
Go. Go back to your village.
Hey, you! Are you alright?
Sister! I will leave.
Where?
I will go back to dad.
I am missing him.
You are feeling better, right?
Where will you go?
Are you crazy?
Will you not stay until I conceive?
Won't you see the baby?
I will leave.
-I will leave.
-What happened to you? Why are you crying?
Please book my ticket.
I am not feeling good here.
Bhanu, stop crying.
Bhanu!
Wait! You sit down.
Let's book her ticket.
She might be missing her dad.
What happened, dear?
Nothing. I just can't be here.
How is your sister doing?
She is doing great.
The doctor said that there's no problem.
I will come back, dad.
I will talk to your sister. Don't worry.
OK, dear?
How can you leave?
Will you leave
without visiting me in America?
It won't be good on your part.
Listen! I will stop talking to you
if you don't come.
Give to your brother-in-law.
I will talk to him.
Brother-in-law!
Sumathi wants me to visit her.
Shall I go for a week?
-I've to meet her before I go back.
-You carry on.
Otherwise, she will kill me.
She's on call.
OK. Sure.
Hey, he said OK.
I will come.
-Hey, Varun! Drop her at Sumathi's house.
I am on duty,
But, I am going out of town.
Will you go tomorrow?
-Yeah. OK.
Just drop her.
-OK.
Get down.
Take this ticket and get on the bus.
You can go to Sumathi's house.
Didn't you go?
The bus left. Come.
No need. I will go by bus.
I said that the bus left.
That's the last bus.
Bhanu, stop messing it up.
Shut up and sit in the car.
I won't come. I will not come with you.
-Bhanu, come.
Varun! Leave me.
Pat! There seems to be a problem. Over.
Bhanu! They'll put me behind the bars
for harassment if we stay here any longer.
Please don't make a big scene.
Bhanu.
Bhanu, what happened?
Bhanu, why are you crying?
You should be put behind the bars.
Yes. You are harassing me.
I came to a different country.
You don't at least care about me.
What have I done, Varun?
Why are you angry with me?
Are you taking revenge on me
for rejecting your proposal?
No! I am not taking any revenge.
You have that right to express.
I have a problem. That is why
I am trying to stay away from you.
I am trying to be busy or
fall in love with someone.
But, nothing seems to work out.
Neither mentally nor physically!
I was in my trials and you came.
How can I handle myself?
It's horrible.
Bhanu!
Do you know why I don't look at you?
I might like you even more if I do that.
I miss those crops at
Banswada and that tractor. Especially you!
They're still in my thoughts, Bhanu.
I like you a lot, Bhanu.
I like you very much.
Bhanu! Why don't we just be friends?
Isn't that possible?
You moved on and you're happy.
I will take care of myself, Bhanu.
I'll be fine. I will get over it.
Let's be friends.
Bhanu?
-OK.
-OK?
Bhanu! Do you want to see my world?
I mean just like how you showed me
your place Banswada.
OK.
"Her feelings within are manifested"
"But, my heart seems to be ignorant"
"She must've found what
she was in quest of"
"But, she is helpless in claiming it"
"Though you call out to me
and ask me to leave"
"I am coming and I'll be by your side"
"I feel tremors in my heart"
"I feel questioned in your presence"
It has been many days.
-How can I leave just like that?
Thanks for coming.
-Nice meeting you.
He's my brother-in-law's brother Varun.
Hi. How was your trip?
-Hello. I am Varun.
Do you have the picture of your fiancé?
"The agonizing pain in my heart"
"It makes me feel so out of place"
"Are you paying heed to my silence"
"It speaks its heart out to you
Hey! I'll take you to some place.
Is that OK?
Why are you specially asking me?
-That's something. Are you OK with it?
-Hey!
-Brother-in-law! Hi.
Shailu.
-What is this sudden surprise?
-I wanted to see you.
-You didn't even call me.
-I am just kidding.
-Where is Vamsi?
-Vamsi. Come.
Hey, Vamsi! How are you?
-Hey, Varun! How are you, man?
Long time, man!
Vamsi, she's Bhanu. Bhanu, he's Vamsi.
Hey, Bhanu! We got married because
of your sister's wedding.
We are very thankful to you.
It's not because of her sister's wedding.
It is because of that coach, right?
-That's on the train.
-We had discussed in the train that day.
You'd not be married if we did not plan to
arrange visa documents. -Oh, yeah.
True.
Isn't that right, Vamsi?
Hey, Bhanu! Why did wear a saree?
We are not going out, right?
I don't have anything other than this.
I have to wash my clothes.
Bhanu!
You can sleep in the room upstairs.
I am not sleepy.
Say something.
Bhanu! Don't mind me asking you something.
You never say sorry,
thank you or love you.
I can. But,
it depends on the other person.
You are a famous doctor, right?
There is nothing about being famous.
I am just a doctor.
That is my mom's wish.
That is why I study medicine and
I am serious about it.
Will you start up a hospital in India?
No.
I applied for America's top university.
I am waiting for my admission.
It is my dream to become a neurosurgeon.
Brain doctor?
Varun! Get up.
Varun.
Bhanu, where are you going?
"Distance between us begins to melt away"
"Dream like reality promises to persist"
"Though there is everything in my world"
"You must be the missing
piece of the puzzle"
"Though there is no distance parting us"
"I might still be in hesitation"
Hey, Bhanu! Your wishes might
come true if you pray here.
It is meant for lovers.
But, you can still try.
All I wish for is that
Bhanu stays with me in my world forever.
He should come into my world.
I might stay here forever if
I stay here any longer.
God! Please send me away to my place.
What did you wish for?
-What about you?
Come in.
Thanks.
-Congratulations!
-Thanks, buddy.
Congrats, bro.
Bujji.
-I am really proud of you.
Thanks, guys.
Emory! Emory!
Are you leaving, then?
It is just 3 more months. Stay back.
I cannot go if I do not leave now.
You like Varun, right?
Why don't you stay back?
I like him. That is why
I am saying this.
I can't stay here by his side
with all my heart.
Ask Varun if he will come.
You told me to ask Raju.
Shall I ask him?
Varun won't be happy if he comes there.
He cannot be complete.
He should become a famous doctor here.
Look at him.
How can there be conditions in love?
Bujji! what happened?
-I'm sad.
Why, dear? What happened?
I don't want Bhanu sis to leave.
You can make her stay.
No.
You could.
-I can't.
Yes. You could.
I could maybe if I leave.
She might stay if I leave. Is that OK?
No! I don't want you to leave.
Take care, Bhanu.
See you, brother-in-law.
-Take care...
You're very special, Bhanu.
Varun.
Thank you, Bhanu.
It is so disturbing, Bhanu.
I feel like losing my life.
You are a good person, Varun.
You're special.
Impressed!
I saw it. You can see.
I'll stop it.
Hey, Bhanu!
You said that our wishes come true
if we pray. Shall I pray for it?
Hmm.
Stay back, Bhanu.
That's what I wished for.
Let's go, Bhanu. We are getting late.
Bhanu! Keep your passport
and boarding pass ready.
[flight announcements]
Announcement!
Bye.
Thanks for everything, Bhanu.
Varun!
What is it, dear?
Why did you come suddenly?
Nothing, uncle.
Is everything alright?
-Yeah. Everything is fine.
Give me your bag.
That's OK, uncle.
Uncle! I should talk with Bhanu.
Do you want to talk with Bhanu?
OK, dear.
Why did you come?
Why did you hug me at the airport?
You left. But, you came back to hug me.
What's this?
You don't like him. You like me.
But, you got ready to marry him.
Why? But, why?
Oh! Right. You're Bhanumati! One piece!
I told you many times that I like you and
I love you.
I told you that
I will wait for you any longer.
But, that groom doesn't wait.
Remember that.
You'll get married.
Both of us can't do anything after that.
Think about it and let me know.
Bhanu!
It's OK if you do not like me
and marry someone else.
That's because it is your choice and
I hope that you will be happy.
I can't take it if you do not be happy.
I won't accept and live with that lie.
You can lie to me but
don't cheat yourself.
Darling! Haven't you slept yet?
-Dad.
My dear!
Shall I ask you something?
-What happened, Dad?
Dad likes him.
The wedding should be done anyway
and it is getting late. He's our neighbor.
Did you agree to the wedding
because if those reasons?
I can't bear it if you love someone
and marry someone else for my sake.
Not just me. Dads can't bear it.
I can't be happy even if you stay here.
Dad!
I know it all.
How can I be happy if
you don't marry Varun?
My darling! Listen to me and marry Varun.
I will take care of the rest.
Will you marry him?
My darling will listen to her dad.
What happened? Why are you sad?
I have different ideas
but something else happened.
That's life.
Wonders don't happen in this world.
You are right.
We take birth and grow up in one place.
We marry someone and
go to some other place.
That's how it is. It is the same for all.
Hey...what's this?
That's not needed.
It is not needed at all.
Your prince came for you
but he's taking you away.
He came into your world for you
to stay with you by your side.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Really?
You prayed for it and that happened.
"He is special and it's
not easy to get him"
"He's is a good person"
Sister! I'm not going to America.
I will stay here.
Oh! Is it?
Varun!
Bhanu.
Bhanu...what happened?
Why are you crying, Bhanu?
Pick me up.
Hey...
Bhanu.
Oh, my! What is this?
Did you come here for me?
Will you stay here? My darling!
I didn't understand you.
I troubled you and
I'm sorry about that.
Why did you think a lot about this?
You should've told me that.
You talked about your world.
But, you are my world.
You're my one piece.
I'm not the one. You are my one piece.
You are my one piece. My husband!
It's raining.
Shall we go?
Hey, Bhanu! Did you see that?
Our hospital is behind that.
Anything is fine. But, no kisses!
-Why?
-See this.
Oh! This one is morphed by my friend Ali.
I won't believe it. He should say that.
Hey, crazy! Bloody!
Are you out of your mind?
Hey! This is Bhanumati.
Is it? Let me show you.
Hey.