What is life? A manifest order between the elements
What is death? A confusion thrown between these elements
~Brij Narayan Chakbast
[Public toilets]
- Ah yes. Wait a moment.
I have a gift for you.
- Thank you.
- What?
- I don't know, it makes me a little weird.
- Open the door !
What the hell are you doing in there? Open!
Open!
Ah !
Look at me there.
It feels like a love hotel.
- Please ... - Come over here.
Go!
- We take their identity. Your name !
Your name !
- Piyush Agarwal.
- What are you doing ? - I'm a student, sir.
- Where do you live?
- Allahabad. - "Allahabad." Are you studying anatomy?
- Sir, can't we agree on a settlement??
- Tiwari, show him good "settlement".
I'll make arrangements with the young lady.
- Hey! What's your name ?
What's your name ?
- Please ...
Say it!
- Devi
Devi, your life is now ruined
Piyush!
- Catch him!
Bring him back here.
- I thought you wanted us to work it out.
- What do you want ?
I am a student.
This is the first time I have done this.
- Start by opening the door. Go!
Open!
- We're digging.
Find me his wallet.
- You're going to open up, you little asshole!
What the hell is he doing? Open that door!
- So you found him? - Get out!
- I'll get it out for you.
Father's name: Ramdhari Agarwal
Phone number: 94-15-25-75-47.
You have 2 min to get out of there,
Otherwise I call your father.
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- You'll shit in jail. Your dad's phone is busy.
- Have a pity, don't tell my father.
- I'm going to embarrass myself, here.
Where are you from? From the whore district?
- Look at him !
- No.
- Are you imported from Nepal?
- You are wrong.
- Is that so ? Are we wrong?
If you don't open, we'll drag you naked in the street!
Open!
What are you waiting for ? Break open the damn door!
- You're going to open!
Open!
Are you going to open up, you little asshole?
You will open, yes or shit!
- Break down that door!
Are you at a confessional?
Chief ! - What?
- Come see what he did. - Piyush!
- What's the matter ?
Hey Pandev!
Call the ambulance
- Piyush...
Slowly slowly.
Raise his arm. Piss the blood.
Is the ambulance coming?
Janaki, get her dressed, we'll get her on board.
What are you looking at ? Unleash!
Move around!
- Ah! Here is my son.
I'll bring you a glass of water.
- I'll help myself. - I'll take care of it, mother-in-law.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- We must light the stove.
- My son, go get a fire. You have to light the stove.
Wake up your big brother, by the way.
He's gonna be late for the funeral.
Brother!
Sikandar...
Hi, Brother! !
Get up. Mom told me to wake you up.
Come on, get up. Standing.
Dad, I'll light the stove and be back
- What about Sikandar?
- I woke him up, he's coming.
- Hi, Motilal !
Come, have some sweets.
-I can't leave my shop unattended
- So what ? Like every day.
Nobody's going to steal anything
They brought this to us, they are students. Tell him.
- We are doing research in anthropology.
- They are interested
in the history of the ghats (cremating site).
Tell them. - Me ?
You are the specialist.
- And you, the alley specialist.
- The badly frequented alleys.
You're recording this?
- Yes, sir.
One tends to miss details while writing
History... Huh?
Before, on this shore,
it was the forest as far as the eye can see.
The Ganges is sacred.
People brought their dead,
for the ritual of cremation.
The Maharajahs built gahts.
Now there are different priests there,
different customs,
different castes and different funeral rites.
You see ?
The ghat on which we are, for example,
is a hotly contested location.
- Like Kashmir. - Yes.
The people of Bombay claim it.
The people of Gujarat also claim it.
Do you agree? What are we going to do with him?
He's little Jhonta, a hell of a trickster.
Later he will study, but he brought me no clients.
Not a pilgrim since this morning.
- I go.
Bring me the phone. Hurry up.
Another example, the Scindya ghat, a little further away ...
Hey! - I'm bringing back pilgrims.
- It's not true. Kids today ...
They are smarter than us. - That is true.
- And that damn phone ... It keeps ringing.
A real calamity, this invention.
Yes, hello?
It's me, yes.
What ?
- She prepared her action well. She put on a saree,
got a red dot on her forehead.
They had only seen each other twice,
and there we go!
How does she explain that?
I'm talking to you.
Repeat what you told me. Come on, tell him.
Tell your father.
How do you explain it? Ah yes, it was "out of curiosity".
lf l tip off a journalist...
Count on them.
It will make the headlines.
What is this?
A file of another department,
on my desk?
Whatever ! Who gave me such incompetents?
Bring me the right file!
Your name ?
- Pathak.
Vidhyadhar Pathak.
I help the pilgrims to perform the rituals on Nandeshwar ghat.
I was teaching Sanskrit at the university.
I translate...
- You will be summoned in 3 days.
Pay the bail here
and take your daughter for now
- Sorry, Mr. Mishra.
What do you mean "for now"?
It means ...
- If anything happens to the guy,
she will be continued
for incitement to suicide. It means a trial,
Court, media, journalists,
the whole thing!
No need to whine.
Go pay the bail over there
- We're from the same community
- Go pay the bail and get out!
- The centrifugal force is converted into centripetal force,
by rotation.
The body rises vertically.
This is where the civil engineer comes in.
Questions ?
- NO, PROFESSOR.
- Are your lessons over soon?
- I have two months left, Dad.
After the exams, then the recruitment.
- The ... what ?
- To land a job.
Don't you need to pay lots of money to get a job?
- Not anymore, Mother
The Railway and Electric companies...
we have an interview. They hire on merit
Instead of supervising the ash cleaning,
you're eating here?
What if they stole the money again?
- Uncle Shambhu is there.
- Shambhu is depressed.
- I no longer have the right to eat?
- How much will you be paid?
- They tell you after the interview.
- In any case, that's a good thing.
The sooner you are gone, the better.
If you stay, you'll waste your life setting the corpse on fire.
- Good food.
- Look. I found some silvers.
- Show me ?
You really don't know anything about it. It's aluminum.
- Hello, prof. I had time to wash myself, while waiting for you.
You have not come for 3 days.
- Shut up and work.
- Is your father here?
- No, he's in the ghat. - Call him.
(* - following landslides caused by floods,)
(* many houses were destroyed in Sherpur and Semara.)
(* The inhabitants went in front of the building of the local authorities)
(* to require assistance and rehousing solutions.)
(* This sector has suffered from landslides for a long time.)
(* The land is regularly washed away by the waters of the Ganges.)
(* The demonstrators complain of leading a nomadic life.)
(* They claim to have received no help,)
(* despite the many steps taken.)
(* The villagers seized the Mandala commission to ...)
- He is dead.
(* -The organizer of the movement, Mr. Prem Nath Gupta,)
(* is ready to continue)
(* as long as the families have not been rehoused.)
- You offered tea
or something ?
- Sit down.
- Sorry. I took some time.
- The young man is dead, Mr. Pathak.
Apparently a piece of glass
entered the vein. I brought the court papers.
- You sign them. - No, wait ...
How does this affect us?
- It's a case of incitement to suicide.
- Wait, Inspector.
Excuse me, you were there when he killed himself.
It was you who threatened him.
- So here, it's the world upside down.
Listen to me, Pathak.
Keep your little reasoning to rip off your ghetto pilgrims.
It's understood ?
Did you see the stories on the TV?
The high school porn texting affair,
that of Kashmir, and now,
it's your daughter.
- Tell us what we can do to get out of there?
- How much do you earn ?
- Within 8 to 10,000 rupees per month.
- Does she also have a salary?
- Yes. At a computer coaching institute
- Well. So it's very simple.
Incitement to suicide,
the press, the legal proceedings, I take care of it.
You have to find 300,000 rupees.
Within 3 months. I'll give you 3 months to find.
- Excuse me, you misunderstood.
We are a very modest family.
Comment...
I can't bring together more than 50,000 ...
- Never haggle with me again. Never again !
I did not come to negotiate.
Do you take me for a carpet merchant?
Pathak sanglote.
I am here to save your honor. Yours!
Hold.
You see it. I have the entire arrest on video.
Do you want me to put it on the Internet?
I'm gonna do a hell of a pub for you and your daughter in Benares.
I give you 48 hours
to find 100,000 rupees.
Stop nodding your head!
What did I say ?
- 100,000 rupees in 48 hours.
- And in 2 months?
- 200 000.
- There. It's easy to understand.
- Where are you going, madame?
- I'm going down to the ghat.
- It's forbidden for women.
- Mister.
You have to hit hard on the skull, 5 blows.
- Piyush !
- Deepak, help him a little.
- Piyush...
- Hit hard. It is like this that the soul is liberated.
- I collected 26 rupees. Look.
- Yes. Where?
- I dived and held my breath for a very long time.
- So what ?
- Let me play with the others.
- You want to go bet?
- It's not a bet, it's a sport. I am old.
- You speak...
Queue! Go get clients.
- You have a broom stuck somewhere.
- That's my pretty Pooja.
She's cute, isn't she?
- Can you ask her the name of her friend?
- And what do I say then?
"Miss Pooja, your friend who loves poetry,
"my friend really likes her and would like to talk to her.
"Give me her name, please."
No, I know. We're going to write to her.
- He's in love. Must be crazy.
- His bed is too big for him alone.
He's tired of playing 5 to 1.
- What is this noise? - Shhh!
Wait, I know.
Do you remember her face? Yes ?
Are you sure? Really sure?
We are going to watch
on their university's Facebook.
- You were on Pooja's album. There will be her photo, right?
- Yes, she must be on her friends list.
Do you see her ?
- It's her ! Look .
- "Shaalu Gupta."
She comes from a good family caste.
- You aim high.
- Open a Facebook account. Afterwards, it will go by itself.
Are you listening? Ask her if she wants to be your friend.
Should I do that to you?
Huh? - Yes.
- Lets' go ! Nothing to lose and everything to gain.
It's madness what's going on here.
In just 30 minutes, 10 rupees will become 50 rupees.
And 50 rupees brings in 200.
- Come on. You can start betting.
4 plongeurs: Lokwa, Munwa, Netwa, Baboua.
- 20 rupees on whom? - Lokwa.
- 10 on Lokwa. - Encore on Lokwa.
- 20 rupees on Netwa.
- Okay. 20 rupees.
- It will start.
Children ...
1...
2...
[Whistle]
Let's go ! The competition has started.
Which one will reassemble the 1st parts?
We wait for the moment of truth. Lokwa is the first to go up.
- Hurry, Netwa.
- Baboua, also with 3 pieces.
Who's going to come back up now?
Munwa also brings back 3 coins.
Look...
- I want to dive too.
- No way. No, I'm telling you.
- 6 more pieces!
Those who bet
on Netwa will win 3 times the amount they wagered.
- Sikandar !
This foot protrudes. Put it back on the fire.
- Hi, Sikandar !
The old man got drunk.
- I'd have a drink,
king of the ghats, just a little last.
- Do I look like a king?
- As they say, there are only two kings in Benares.
The Maharajah and the King of the Ghats.
The first, above,
and you guys at the bottom.
- He looks like a king,
Shambhu Chacha ?
How many days of work do you have per year?
Shambhu Chacha !
- What do you think, boss? Only one day every 10 years.
One day.
- His turns...
only once every 10 years. You heard ?
You understand ?
This means that on that day,
all the money there is to be made in the ghat is for him.
When you think that Shambhu's father,
his turn came back once a year ...
And imagine that this idiot had 10 children.
We divide by 10.
Her father could earn a living once a year.
Shambhu can earn it once every 10 years.
Oh yes, poor man.
His turn only returns every 10 years.
When is the next time you work?
- I finished.
No next time. I sold my cremating spot
Lala Chaudury.
He gave me 100,000 rupees.
I will be a beggar until I die.
- If I sold you my cremating spot, Lala, would you give me a million?
- I would be surprised if you sold it.
- Son, can I sell it to him?
- Why are you asking him?
He doesn't give a shit, of the ghat,
since he studied.
- Are you criticizing my son? I won't sell you my cremating spot.
- But you never meant to.
- Papa,
do you have some money? I'm going to Durga Puja's party.
- Yes. Look in my tunic.
- Can I take 300 rupees?
- Take what you want.
All I have is for you.
- Are you going to tell me?
- What do you want to know ?
- I want to know what happened.
Who was it? Why did you do that?
- He was coming to take computer lessons.
I typed for his 2nd year thesis..., and voila.
We became friends. That's all.
- And that's all ?
- Yes.
We got along well. I liked talking to him.
- You did this without thinking, without asking yourself a single question,
neither why nor how, without thinking of the consequences.
Come on, answer!
So ?
Are you listening to me?
- I don't know!
- A young man died.
Your father has a debt of 300,000 rupees.
I had to empty my savings account.
You risk ending up in prison,
and you answer me: "I don't know."
[Friend request sent]
Are you coming to the Durga Puja party?
- 20 rupees.
* -Put your watch here.
*Slowly !
* The watch is at the bottom.
* Blow hard on it.
* I am looking for the watch.
* She is no longer there.
*Rest assured.
*Your watch
* is in the pocket of one of the spectators: this one.
* The red checkered shirt.
* Look in your pockets.
* And voila, we found the watch. Come closer.
* Come join me on stage.
*What is your name ?
*-Deepak.
*-"Deepak."
- Swallow the smoke.
He can't smoke.
Come on, try.
- Why are you throwing it away?
I will never smoke again. Yesterday, my friends forced me.
- What are you watching ? - She released her balloon.
[Shaalu accepted your request to add.]
- I used to earn 12,000 rupees. It's the minimum.
- Shut up. He is the son of Tripathi.
- Your father
taught me Sanskrit. All that I am I have to
To his knowledge.
Bring him some tea.
- No, we're in a hurry.
I have a book translation to finish.
- A glass of water ? Bring water.
I read it, you sent it to me.
To tell the truth,
we don't have a trainer position.
We are missing someone at the reception,
to welcome new students.
You also need to do some data entry.
We can go out of 5,500.
- Okay. It's perfect.
She can start tomorrow. Thanks a lot, Sanjay.
- You're welcome. It is my duty.
I have a call.
Have a drink. We have a new bottle.
The water tastes very good and it is very fresh.
If you allow ... Hello ?
Yes, Mr. Shoukla. Hello.
- Only 5,500?
- Did you hear how respectful he was?
- Thank you.
Are you a student in engineering school?
- Yes. Civil engineering, in the final year.
We had a strike last year
otherwise I would already have a diploma,
and I would have a job.
What are your favorite hobbies? - The music.
- You sing ? - No.
I listen to a lot of music on the radio, and I have lots of CDs.
- And apart from the music?
- I really like poetry!
- Poetry? - Yes.
Bashir Badr ...
Akbar Allahabadi, Mirza Ghalib ...
You know him ?
- Yes finally...
Thank you.
Please.
Can we have some sauce? Chilli sauce?
You have some ? We would like some.
- Serve yourself. - You want some ?
- You first.
So...
Is it decided? We are friends ?
- Yes.
I want to tell you something important.
If ever, one day, you have a problem,
it will absolutely be necessary to speak to me about it.
- And what will you do?
- Well, I'll come and fix it.
If a boy annoys you, harasses you, makes you cry ...
It's dangerous here. There are thugs.
- Yes. Okay.
And if ever ... - Hot sauces.
If you make me cry?
- Me ?
How I... ?
Say it, I'll fix it.
- The name of the student at the top, in capital letters.
Here is the establishment's brochure
and a free CD with all the information.
Read this and come back tomorrow. We will register your son.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You explain it to them.
Is this your ever first job?
- Nope.
- What happened before?
- I didn't like work.
- You were in private Yadav class.
* -Participate in the game "Who is this face?"
* If you know who this actress is, answer today.
* If you give the correct answer, you can win a car.
* Our lines are open.
(2nd Year Thesis. Piyush Agarwal)
(Piyush Agarwal Death Announcement - September 17, 2014)
- Lets' go. Nothing to lose, everything to gain.
- Do you want to dive? - Yes.
- Slowly. - Come on!
- How much did you collect this morning?
- More than all these guys.
- But be careful. - Okay.
- So let's go.
Come on, go!
Whistle
- We have a new participant. Jhonta!
How many coins will he bring back?
Well done, Jhonta!
Jhonta goes up like a rocket.
- Place the pieces.
- Will he beat the champion?
- Yes, dive in!
- It's good.
Hurry up.
- 20 rupees?
- Do not miss the opportunity to bet.
We can win big.
Jhonta brings back other coins!
- Piyush Agarwal,
Hometown: Allahabad?
He is deceased.
Accidentally.
- I read the announcement.
I come from the school where he took evening classes.
He left a file that belonged to him.
There is an overpayment to repay.
He had also forgotten a few books.
Can I get his address?
- We're going back up. It's over. Get out.
Who has the most coins?
So, Munna?
Who is the winner?
- It's Jhonta! - Jhonta!
- One l .
- I told you I'd win. - You are the best.
I'm proud of you.
Piyush's father: Ramdhari Agarwal
*-Hallo?
* -I tell you:
* "Keep the stars captive to your eyes
* "The night is dark and long and the morning, far away
"Travelers, vagabonds
"We both are
* "We will meet again at the crossroads"
- It's finish ?
- What? Yes, it's over. I have finished.
*-Pardon.
The little that I understood, I found it great!
- What, you can be stupid!
And adorable.
- What? What?
*-I said nothing.
- I heard.
- If I read Chakbast, you will faint.
- I saw that it was soon your birthday.
- Yes, but you don't know what I'm going to do.
- What?
- A picnic.
- Shaalu? *-Ah yes ?
- Shaalu?
- My mother is calling me. See you later.
- Wait!
* Don't hang up.
- What?
- Please call me by my name
* Talk to me.
- Learn 2 lines, and recite them to me.
* (Afterwards, we'll see. I'll hang up.)
- Hallo ?
- Goodbye.
He's laughing.
* This one is from Dushyant Kumar.
* "You are the passing train
* "I am the quivering bridge
* "Your eyes are a jungle
* "Where I lose my steps"
* -But finally, who is on the device?
- May I speak to Mr. Ramdhari Agarwal?
*-It's me. I listen. What do you want ?
- Uh ... I ...
* -But talk, finally. Gone?
This is the Kashi Cooperative Bank
about our new savings plan.
*-No thanks. I am not interested. Goodbye.
- I'm asking you the question frankly.
Will you sleep with me?
No one will know.
You had sex with him too, right?
- It's good quality.
- It's too expensive. - Let me give you a discount
320 rupees for the two mats. And I add ...
Think it over and come back later, okay?
Okay ?
- I quit my job.
- Your daughter hadn't come for a long time.
- Hello.
- Go away. Don't stay there.
- What?
- Should I drown myself with shame?
Go away!
Indian Railways - Recruitment Madam admitted.
What went through your mind?
- Nothing.
- "Nothing", "I don't know", that's all you say.
Am I a bad father?
I left you free to study like a boy.
I deserved that you caused this scandal?
- It's not a scandal.
- Then what is this, then?
Why am I dying to pay?
On the ghat, in the streets,
I'm always afraid people will talk to me about you.
It is a scandal.
- That's your fear, not my fear
Hence, I've decided not to live here anymore
The smaller the city, the narrower the world-view
- You live under my roof and my world-view is narrow?
- Is that where you wanted to come from?
You want me to pay you
a rent ?
- Look at me.
What are you looking for ?
Are you looking for revenge on me? About what ?
- Mom !
- "Mummy mummy"...
You don't even remember her. You were 6 years old!
- A 6-year-old is blind?
- I took her to the hospital, didn't I?
- For 2 days, she begged to go to the hospital.
"I have partials to correct."
You didn't try to help her.
- We thought we had a fever. And that's in the past.
Do not complain.
I quit teaching for my daughter!
I find myself in the ghats for my daughter!
Did I kill your mother?
- And I killed this boy at the hotel?
Did I kill him?
He killed himself! Alone.
- You're crazy. You mix things up that have nothing to do with it.
- I'm not mixing anything up.
Drop it. Don't worry.
I won't go to jail.
- Make it up to you.
Me, I'm looking for money, like a poor idiot.
- I'll manage to pay the policeman.
- I see, you don't need your father anymore.
Do as you like.
* - "I am the quivering bridge
* "Your eyes are a jungle
* "Where I lose my steps"
* -I don't have a favorite season. I love them all.
*-Idiot. How can we love them all?
* My favorite ... - It's the rainy season.
* Indian music
- Are you recording her voice on the phone?
- Yes, and I put songs that go well with it.
- A real genius. Thanks to my dating lessons.
- Nice birthday present.
- She's of high caste.
Don't get too carried away.
Did you tell her, your caste?
Start by telling her, and you'll see.
Not everyone has broad ideas.
- I know. I have the time. I'll tell him later.
- We're not there.
When he gets a job,
none of this will matter
- Give him the keys to your motorcycle. - Why ?
- He's going to surprise her.
Give the keys!
He'll pay you for the fuel
- First word.
A plant ?
- A lamp ?
- An oil lamp. - A candle.
- A Bush ?
I dunno. A tree ?
I don't know.
- A motorcycle ! - No, a flower.
- Look!
- Where are you going?
- Where you want.
Get on
- Your bag.
Shall I sit?? - Yes go ahead.
Do you know what we call your bus?
- No. Tell me.
- Chick-Wagon!
You never told me.
Where do you live?
- Uh ... Bhelupur, you know?
- Bhelupur? - Yes. At home, it's after.
- My friend Prerna lives in this neighborhood.
I will text her then come to see you.
Isn't that great?
- You will come to my place ?
If your parents find out, how will they react?
- If you do not want...
- Of course it is. I didn't mean to say that, excuse me.
Hold it for a second.
Gift for your birthday.
Put them on
* - "Where I lose my steps"
* -I don't have a favorite season. I love them all.
*-Idiot.
- How are you? Can we hear well?
* -My favorite is the rainy season.
Thank you.
* Indian music
Have you been to the Sangam?
I've been there plenty of times.
In few days we'll be off on
a pilgrimage in a bus
We all go: uncles, aunts, grandparents ...
Will you come along?
- Where? - On the pilgrimage.
- With your family ? - Yes.
- I have to think about it. We'll discuss it again later.
- What?
You must be the youngest
in your family, right?
- Yes.
How did you know?
- It's always the last one who says the most nonsense.
That hurts!
Your hand is like a hammer!
- It's because of my ring.
My uncle
Gave it to me when I was little.
I can't take it off anymore.
My finger has grown, but the ring has not.
As I am the youngest, I have always been cuddled.
What?
- I dunno.
Suddenly, I too wanted to cuddle you.
Shaalu. - Yes ?
- Will you marry me ?
- I dunno.
- Would your parents agree?
Do you want to come and see them?
- Would you like to introduce me?
- You don't give me your address, and you want to know my parents?
I go.
- Is your house not far?
- Just there. First on the right, first on the left.
And where is your place?
After Bhelupur, you said. This is ...
Shivala?
Or then ...
Kamacha!
No, I know.
- Durgakund. - Why ?
Did what?
I told you I stay near Bhelupur.
You have nothing else to talk about?
- I was joking...
- Do you find it amusing?
You want to know ?
Okay. Come on, I'll show you.
Hop on. I will show you, since you are so impatient.
Do you want the truth?
I live in Harishchandra ghat . I was born there.
We burn bodies, light pyres
The work of me, my father, my brother, my uncle. For ages
Have you ever seen a body burning?
Answer me: have you ever seen any?
I see them all day. From morning to night, I burn bodies.
In the fire, the skin comes off. Only the skull remains.
We smash the skull with a stick. The ashes are purified in the Ganges.
Can you watch that? Do you want to come and see?
What happened? Will you send text to your friend now?
Where's my tip?
- Why ?
- A letter for a job in the railways, it is celebrated.
Goodbye.
[Ministry of Railways]
(* -Train 54 492 Pratapgarh Express)
(* will enter the station on track 4.)
- Are you the new employee?
- Yes.
- Get comfortable.
(* -Arrival of the Benares express train, track number 3.)
(* The train arrives an hour late.)
(* I repeat: about an hour late.)
(* We apologize for the inconvenience caused.)
- If you left two minutes later,
I would have given you my water bottle to fill too.
I am M. Sadhya.
- Namaste.
- It is well done, the brochure of the ministry.
We didn't have a manual. We trained in the old one.
Look.
I have a photo of Mr. Mukherjee.
He worked here. You replace it.
He refused to learn computers.
- Can I plug it in? - Go for it.
He was transferred to a small station.
They sent him to Dungarpur, Rajasthan.
He's stuck there, filling out tickets by hand.
You know
computers?
- Yes.
- It's good.
- Ticket!.
- Hello. - One way to Jalalpur.
(Beep)
- Shaalu, auntie is waiting outside.
*-You know...
* You are different from other boys.
*-I did not know. How different?
* -You have a certain sincerity.
* Like the one in Nida Fazli's ghazals .
* -Who is this one again?
*-That is what I am saying. What sincerity!
The food was delicious...
Except the salad.
Even the lentils were brilliant
It doesn't surprise me that it's good,
it's run by people of same caste as us. The Ghupta.
So, you finally called, huh?
- It was you who made a scene, and you are angry with me?
- Sorry.
- I'm not waiting for an apology.
- I'm a fool!
*-That is true.
- I don't know how to express myself.
- That is also true.
- Are you coming soon?
* -We still have 5 or 6 hours on the road. We are in Saharanpur.
Ok, listen...
My parents, as I know them ...
They won't accept you.
* They have a very traditional mentality.
But I am on your side.
With time, parents do come around
Just get yourself a good job
- Yes. I started sending CVs.
I'll give my all to find
* a good job.
- Yes. Courage. For the rest, we'll see.
And if I have to run away, I'll run with you.
*Take care of yourself.
Hey man! Let's go back!
- We just left.
I have plenty of classes to review.
We turn around!
Sir, another sheet.
I am in the last year of civil engineering.
from Seth Kinaram Agarwal
Polytechnique College
My career objective is to
pursue a career in engineering...
with focus on mechanical drafting
I have a job soon. Come back soon.
- We were brought bodies.
Shove the skull inside
- We need help.
I will be back. I'll go get Deepak.
- Deepak !
- What? - Get up!
Dad's drunk again and there
are lots of bodies to burn
Get up, I tell you!
They only think of sleeping here.
I can't take any more of this doggy job.
Come on, Deepak!
- Dirty thief!
Catch them!
Give him a beating, that little jerk. Dirty thief.
Get out ! - We are leaving.
- Watch out, or I'll throw you into the fire! - Don't stay here.
- It's a plague, these thieves.
We have already had enough trouble like that.
- Don't stay in the middle.
- Hey, go ahead!
- You didn't cover the body.
- Shambhu Chacha! We must add a beaker here.
- Yes I am going.
- Prepare a beaker.
- Where is your father? He is drunk.
- Deepak! Come see.
Finish this one and prepare a beaker by the water.
- Over there?
- Yes, very close to the shore.
- Shall I finish this one? - Yes.
- Sanjay! We're not going to get there, alone.
- I can't do it either.
But I'm not asking anyone for anything. - Warning !
I told you to be careful. Ah, there you are.
- Bring me some sawdust!
- It's always the same.
Take them all.
- Manohar, go get another one. What are you doing ?
- We will see tomorrow. I am tired.
- Hey, Deepak! Give us a hand.
Careful.
- Slowly.
- Where do all these deaths come from?
- A pilgrim bus had an accident. It fell into the Ganges.
Really?
Public aid workers dumped
all the bodies here
- Isn't there a single survivor?
- Nope.
- On all the trains that pass here,
there are 28 that stop at our station.
How many do not stop,
In your opinion?
- Exactly 64.
Which means, it's
easy to come here...
but it's more difficult to leave!
- It's not true. - You drank too much.
- But it was way too strong.
- Whiskey. - I don't have the alcohol?
- Following.
- I didn't say that.
- We have tickets on the waiting list.
Can you check?
It was nice,
but we have to go home.
- One more day.
- No seats.
- What about last minute cancellations?
Even one seat for both of us is fine
- Naughty.
- Stop it, idiot.
- Come on, we'll stay until tomorrow.
(26 places available)
- I'm not going back to that rotten hotel.
- No, I have nothing.
- No cancellations? - No.
- Shit ! What are we going to do ?
*-Hello?
* -I am the father of Piyush. I know who you are.
* Were you at the hotel with him?
*-What are you doing ? Let me talk to her.
* -It's me speaking. Go back to the kitchen!
* Did you kill Piyush? Answer!
- Get closer ! - You bet 30 rupees on Baboua.
- 20 on Munwa. - A real spectacle.
- Jhonta!
- Now these 4 boys
are going to dive ...
- Jhonta!
- Stop screaming. Bet on another boy.
Bet on Baboua, he is very fast.
- Baboua, okay.
- How ? - 200 rupees.
- The professor bets 200 on Baboua!
Prepare to dive.
Attention. 1, 2...
- I have something
in the mouth ? - NO !
- I'll swallow that bullet. Look carefully.
Warning. 1 ... 2 ... and ...
- 140, 150 ... Here
I deserve at least 500 Rupees
- We'll adjust it next time
300...
How much have you lost, professor?
Look how late it is!
Heh ?
Responds.
Little snot!
Your responses?
Heh ?
Do you hear me?
- I was having fun !
- You're here to work, you little shit, not to have fun.
- It's my money. Mind your ass.
- Shut up. You sound like thugs
Those other orphan kids
have ruined you
I want you to be here
when there is dive competition.
He takes himself for the King of Benares. He wastes money!
- I'll tell Devi everything!
- I do not care. Tell her what you want.
Start by sitting down!
I don't want to see you move.
Sit down, I tell you.
Mule head.
From now on,
I want all your winnings
- Hi, Deepak.
Come on ...
Stop crying. Try to sleep.
- This test will count towards your recruitment.
Here is the theme of the debate:
"The effects of industrialization
"on the individual and life in society."
- I think the negative impact is minimal.
- How can you say that?
- The effluents are released into the water.
- If we see it that way, we can't help it.
- Do you think it's better to close your eyes?
- It's easy to accuse others.
What do you propose ?
How are you going to reduce poverty?
- Deepak.
Speak, say something.
You've been silent too long. Say something.
No, it's okay.
Deepak.
Take all your time.
- "I really like poetry."
"You are the passing train
"I am the quivering bridge"
"And if I have to run away, I'll run with you."
Damn pain. Why doesn't it stop?
He is crying.
- Deepak, you have to hold on!
We are here.
- I'll give you the keys to my motorcycle.
- Shaalu!
- Hang on, Deepak. We are here. We will help you.
- You promised me the translation for today.
The printer is waiting.
Mr. Pathak?
What is happening ?
- Give me three days.
- I've done it before.
- My daughter is not well. She was ill.
Mr. Verma ...
an advance would be possible?
You've already kept me hanging like a bat
for this translation.
But I would have a hard time telling you no.
Hold.
You're welcome.
Come on.
- Excuse me. I am late.
- How many ?
- Only 30,000, so far.
- Come.
Do you see the gate?
- Yes.
- on the right you will find
Pappu, a blacksmith.
Sell your bike for 10,000 or 15,000.
- I do what I can.
I'll be able to find the money.
- Are you kidding me ?
I want the full amount or nothing.
Are you a kid?
- I'll bring you the rest this week.
Take that in the meantime.
I beg you.
- It will be fine this time.
But next month I want the whole thing.
Lala bought your cremating spot?
- I will never sell him!
- Sikandar sold to him for 300,000 rupees.
- How could he sell it to him? - it will go.
- He's not at Kallou's.
- Where is that bastard?
[Luxa police station]
- What can the police tell us?
Ah, Deepak.
You haven't found Sikandar?
- I knew it was rubbish.
- Come. - Dirty thief.
We are going to clarify everything. Come.
- See you later. - What a story.
- The law authorizes him to sell your cremating spot.
- Show me the law!
- Why talk about the law?
You had been advised against it. Arrange it between you.
- Between us, he may not live long.
- Give me the money back, and take back your cremating spot.
- You won't have a rupee! - Calm down.
- There is no evidence that he paid Sikandar.
- Go get him, your Sikandar.
Ask him if I haven't given him 300,000.
- Where am I going to find 300,000?
- I do not care.
Mr. Dubey, I make this commitment in front of you.
If he repays the 300,000, he may have his cremating spot back.
I will not forget how I was received here today.
Looking forward to it.
- No one will offer you better in all of Benares.
- 70 rupees.
- Sir, I'm in a hurry.
- Arrival station? - Calcutta.
- That's good,
your goddess name. Looks like you have 8 arms.
You sell 4 tickets per minute.
I had never seen that.
- Sir, I'm in a hurry. - Yes.
Where are you going? - Mirzapour.
My father said: "The one who has never eaten
"fragrant rice pudding does not know how lucky it is to be human."
Taste, please.
- It's for you.
- I know you'll leave some.
It was my father who prepared it. It is his birthday.
- Well.
- It's good, isn't it?
- Delicious
- You live alone ?
- Nope.
I live with my father.
It is my father who lives alone.
I mean, he's alone during the day.
- Ah yes.
- Rice pudding?
- I haven't done it for a long time.
- I'll eat it tomorrow morning. I'm not hungry anymore.
- Yes, eat.
I know you love it.
- It's very good.
Is there any milk left for tomorrow morning?
What's the matter ?
- I finished my first month of work.
I got my salary.
- How much?
- 20 000.
- Well I ...
Come on, sit down.
You didn't tell me you had this job.
It's temporary
I will work on it while I collect the money we owe.
Then..
-And then?
- I want to go to Allahabad University for training.
I will work part time in IT.
- Do you want to leave the house?
- Heh?
- Yes.
- Why ?
- If it wasn't for this case,
I would have already left ...
Maybe I'm better off alone
Anyway, it's not far.
I'll be back.
- And your father?
I don't even exist for you?
You've thought of everything except me.
It wasn't my fault. I didn't kill your mother.
I'm going to go to bed in a ghet and I'm going to die.
- Papa, please
Don't cry, please.
- Do I have to specify it? - No. Tell the interview.
- The narrow lanes will disappear. We do not use them
more than in the mountains. Normal channels will prevail.
- Are you available immediately?
- Yes sir.
- You are offered a 6-month mission to Allahabad.
- Thank you. - Excellent profile. Congratulations.
- It will be necessary to secure the access.
* -Today for the great feast of Shiva,
* great diving competition! All together...
- OM NAMA SHIVAYA!
- You are in shape ?
I bet on Jhonta. - What are we waiting for ?
* -Patience, we will start. - 10,000.
- You will win ? - Yes !
* -Prepare yourself.
- Come on, Jhonta!
* -Who will win this competition
* divers? - This way,
there is more!
* -What an extraordinary spectacle!
- Come on, faster!
* -Our divers are friends ...
- Further from the edge.
* -... but are in competition
*under water ! May the best win !
* Budua has left 5 more coins
*on the shore. He took the lead in the competition.
- Jhonta! * -Nothing is played.
* Munwa goes back in turn
* and put down a handful of coins!
- Go back up, Jhonta!
- What is happening ? - What are you waiting for? Dive!
Jhonta! - Go and get it. Bring him back here.
- Come on, Munna. Bring him back to me.
- It's nothing. - How are you, Jhonta?
- It will get better. Bring him here, Munna.
Put it here. Unleash! - Lay him down on the floor.
Make room. This game is starting to do well!
My little Jhonta!
I'll never make you dive again, my boy.
- What? - Are you sad to have lost?
- No.
- What is it ?
- A magic trick ?
Do I have something in this hand?
- No.
- Do I have something in my mouth?
- 1, 2, 3...
- Who own it?
- It is yours now.
- Where does it come from?
- The Ganges gave it to me earlier.
- Okay. This is very good.
- Hold. - Good.
Thank you.
- Quick, it's hot.
I put you some pancakes for the train.
Eat. I'll finish your bag.
- It's very good.
Let's go ?
- Phone me when you get there. Okay ?
- Come on, I'm going. - Yes, get in.
I'll pass the luggage to you.
Sorry, big boy.
Well. Come on, go sit down.
- Take care of yourself, dad.
- Don't worry, I'll take care of him.
- Hello Madam. - Hello.
- I come to see Mr. Ramdhari Agarwal.
My name is Devi Pathak.
Piyush and I were friends. I was with him the day ...
- Okay. Come in, we'll talk inside.
It's Devi Pathak.
She was the one with Piyush when ...
[Slap]
- What's the matter with you ? - How dare she?
- Are you okay, my daughter? Sit down.
- Why him ? He hadn't done anything to you!
Water?
- You want to go to the Sangam?
For 30 rupees, I'll take you there.
Are you interested, madam?
And you, sir, are you coming?
I take you to the Sangam. 30 rupees is cheap.
30 rupees. Wait, I'm coming.
- Thank you.
- Hop on.
Give me your hand, lady.
Put yourself in the front.
Go up, sir.
- Is this the first time you're going?
- Yes.
And you ?
- This is the second time.
They say you have to go twice.
- Why?
- Alone the first time, and with
someone the second time around.