Rocky and Rani
Rocky and Rani's Love Story
Welcome friends! This is our
White House.
First copy of the famous USA
We are crazy rich Indians.
In other words, the Randhawa family.
Standing on a foundation
of flour laddoos.
Mind you, they aren't your
run-of-the mill laddoos.
Made from grandma's recipes -
the one and only Dhanlakshmi Randhawa.
Through blood and sweat, grandma made
our business reach a turnover of millions.
What a woman! Wonder woman!
Wakanda Forever!
So bland!
These artificial sweeteners spoil them.
Better to be struck down
by diabetes.
We have further options, ma'am.
What are you waiting for?
Go! Get another!
According to grandma, the sea is
made up of tiny drops of water,
and a laddoo is made up
of tiny flour balls.
Quick FB. Not Facebook, I mean
flash-back!
Grandma married Kanwal Lund.
Son of Lund, the sweet maker.
She thought a sweet life
would follow.
But on the very first day, just as she
was about to bow in respect...
No!
Girls don't bow.
Keep your head covered.
Their meeting was bitter.
Her mother-in-law was a witch,
and her husband a total failure.
No head for business, but a great fan
of Javed-Gulzar's poetry.
Grandma's mother-in-law soon became
a photo frame and she - a lucky mother.
She was so obsessed with money,
that she called her son 'Tijori'.
Yes! My father's name means
a 'coffer'!
Grandma was scared he'd become
a poet-type like her husband.
So she kept him far away from
his father. Soshal distancing!
Lost in poetry, one day, grandpa met
with an accident.
Sadly the damage was permanent.
The poor man never fully recovered.
And his memory became an ebbing
and flowing thing.
My sweet grandpa, always living
in a dreamland.
While Dhanlakshmi Sweets became
a global brand.
Then the wedding band played
in our home.
Finally, grandma brought home
the family's prize possession.
That's my Mummy - Poonam.
Girls don't bow.
Keep your head covered.
Though we were selling sweet laddoos,
bitterness continued to reign supreme
in our family.
But I haven't told you my name.
Listen to it in the chorus lines.
It'll sound batter!
Rocky! Rocky! Rocky!
He's a charmer. Made in India
A real fashionista
The guy's a cool dresser
Such a heartthrob.
Such a heartthrob
A hot looker!
What a stud!
Gurgaon's handsome Casanova
Look at my swag
I look like...
...Prada and Gucci got together
to give birth to me
A six-footer
Looks too good
When they look at this package
Girls can't stop winking at me
Such a heartthrob-ji!
This guy has no match
Oh my God!
I drink a glass of lassi every day
A big protein shake makes my way
If being so handsome is a crime
Then I'll happily serve jail time
You turn the heads of us aunties
By God! I feel a heart attack
coming on
The uncles who loved and raised you
Will soon end up divorcees
That's for sure!
You'll be the death of me
My broad chest fills
my Louis Vuitton jacket
I cruise the streets
in my Maserati
Aunties, am I for real?
Or a walkin' talkin' kebab?
Such a heartthrob-ji!
This guy has no match
Oh, such a heartthrob-ji.
Oh my God!
Hey, Dinky, come here!
Harpreeto, come close!
A force of nature
A real rule-breaker
There's no difference to me
Between buds or flowers
Like spring
I embrace the whole garden
The day I get my hands on you,
I'll get even with you.
Such a heartthrob-ji!
This guy has no match
Oh, such a heartthrob-ji
Oh my God!
The government gave me
a title and crowned me
'Lady Killer'
Such a heartthrob-ji!
Oh, such a heartthrob-ji!
You moron!
Didn't I tell you to warn me
if they showed up?
Sorry! I was lost in your dance, bro.
I saw just how lost you were!
Bloody useless.
I won the award for the third time,
so I had to come.
What a rocking performance, Rocky!
- Keep it up, my boy.
- OK. See you later.
- What was that?
- Papa, I didn't want to dance.
But you know I have so many followers.
They kept saying, "Please, please."
So I thought it's a party...
The day I get mad, that'll be the end
of your swagger.
Understand?
- Know who you are?
- Rocky.
The Dhanlakshmi Group's
future CEO.
You're not some Bollywood item dancer.
Do you get it?
- Come on.
- Welcome to the Punjabi of the Year!
Now to follow on from Rocky Randhawa's
amazing performance,
and on this wonderful occasion,
I'll a recite a verse by Firaq.
"The evening was filled with mist
"She was wistful and sad
"Old memories stirred this heart
of mine"
Bravo! Wonderful!
Are you the full moon
or the glowing sun?
Whatever you are, I swear
You are without compare
Jamini!
For the third year,
"The Punjabi of the Year" award goes to
Dhanlakshmi Group's CEO,
Mr. Tijori Randhawa.
Her hair falls on her shoulder
like lowered clouds
And her eyes...
I'd like to dedicate this award
to the goddess. And another goddess...
Jamini!
My mother, Dhanlakshmi Randhawa.
Thanks to her blessings, I've won
this award for the third time.
Jamini! You've come.
- Third time winner!
- Mummy! Grandpa has gone.
- What?
- He's gone!
Jamini.
Rocky, look. Grandpa!
Did you come for me?
Oye!
What's he doing?
I'm so sorry, so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Madam, it's the side effects
of his medicines. He gets restless.
Actually, it's absolutely fine.
- It happens often.
- Really?
Yes, I'm Mona Sen.
Kashmiri Gate.
Mona. We are friends!
What you doing, Grandpa?
Doctor, is it serious?
No, nothing to worry about.
I just want you to focus on his physical,
emotional and social stimulation.
Most importantly - his memory.
Jamini!
The name he keeps calling out...
"Jamini".
- Yes?
- I'd like you to find out who she is.
It might trigger his memory.
What trigger? He doesn't know any Jamini.
Let's go.
OK. Can you give Rocky the prescription?
Rocky...
Tijori.
Let's go.
This is good news.
Papa may be coming back
to his senses.
He was never in his right senses,
nor will he ever be.
Tijori!
What are you doing?
- You must leave for work.
- I'm coming.
Papa-ji...
Tijori!
When will this red colour
let go of me?
When?
What's going on, Grandpa?
You were OK.
You're switched on like a radio.
Who is this Jamini?
When will this red colour
let go of me?
When?
I found this in his book.
- Is she a black and white movie star?
- Looks like one.
- Hope she's not RIP.
- Be positive. She's grandpa's GF.
GF? She looks the sister-type.
Who keeps a photo of a sister-type
in their diary?
Jamini must be an old flame.
OK! Jai Mata Di!
Jai Mata Di! Jai Mata Di!
Jai Mata Di!
Shimla Coffee House.
Shimla Coffee House. 1978.
Rani Chatterjee?
My grandmother.
Her granddaughter.
Oye!
- She's a TV host.
- Yes!
She hosts an evening show.
Rani!
Golu watches her most evenings.
She has a catchphrase.
What is it...?
"India wants to know!"
Yes! India want to know!
Rani, Rani! I am Rani
The girl who knows it all
Argue and you'll look foolishly small
Do you think you can beat me?
Don't you know I'm the queen bee?
Queen of my dreams
Thank you.
How's it going, Somen?
Yes, yes, fine, fine, fine.
I'm a bit nervous. Because of you.
Today's interviewee,
he's political elite.
Don't worry. I'll be sweet to him.
Then we're done for.
Shall we go for a take?
Give me a 20 on Pradhan.
Walking to set in
3... 2... 1... go!
Real Talk with Rani
- Rani-ji. Rani-ji!
- Namaste, Pradhan-ji.
In our culture, this is how
we say "namaste".
Sure! Have a seat.
Of course. I haven't come here
to lie down!
Take my phone. Switch it off.
The currency of our village
runs through foreign lands
Everyone steps aside
when the lads arrive
Tall and broad, the lads
drip with attitude
I am a lover of the beauty of spring
Sir, sir! Parking is in the basement.
And Shah Rukh's at home in Mannat.
The car stays here.
One scratch and my punch will make
breaking news.
Here.
Prasad.
My Ferrari adds value to your building.
So, Pradhan-ji,
- your constituency is Vasalay?
- Yes.
You didn't make any statement
about the recent rape case?
What kind of question is that,
Rani-ji?
Why would I make a statement
about such a trivial incident?
- A trivial incident?
- What else?
Today's girls are addicted
to junk food,
so such incidents are natural.
If you open a box of sweets,
flies are bound to gather.
Do you get me?
Girls should know what clothes
to wear, and what not to.
And when a two-year-child or an old lady
gets raped?
You misunderstood what I was trying
to say, Rani-ji.
Think what men go through.
They work all day, the tension,
the frustration, so they will...
I'm sorry, but you know
what's really frustrating?
That people like you get elected.
I'll tell you why rape...
Rani! Enough, enough, enough.
Because nasty men like you
are around.
The problem isn't our clothes,
or what we eat,
it's your dirty minds.
You compared women to a box of sweets,
didn't you?
Pradhan-ji, the day you stop
objectifying us,
perhaps then we'll no longer hear
of such distressing incidents.
Your minds are dirty and we're
supposed to cover ourselves?
What kind of justice is that?
Stop your damn camera!
Get my car!
Why invite me here only to insult me?
I had to invite you, Pradhan-ji.
To teach you about our culture.
Rani, Rani! I am Rani
Namaste.
Get my car!
Let's go.
Rani! You'll get us taken off air.
You be quiet!
- Rani, you're incorrigible!
- I know that.
OK, Somen!
There's a board meeting at 5.
- Madam-ji, madam...
- Yes, what is it?
- Have you taken out a loan?
- A loan?
Two debt collectors are here.
The currency of our village
runs through foreign lands
Everyone steps aside
when the lads arrive
What's going on in the country?
I am a lover of the beauty of spring
Hello.
Yes?
Nothing really... I was saying...
He's Vicky. My BFF-cum-trainer.
Soon to marry steady girlfriend
Minty.
Congratulations!
Minty is a lucky girl.
And you are?
Single.
Lucky for you.
Rocky Randhawa this side.
And if you come this side,
who will you be?
Meanz?
Nothing.
Shits! You're checking me out?
No, sorry...
Do you always wear your shirt
wide open?
Always. Low is good,
Lower is batter.
Don't mind, but if I said anything
about your neckline,
or commented on your blouse,
all hell would break loose!
Sorry. I didn't mean
to objectify you. I just...
No objection taken!
I'm made to admire.
A ton of hard work.
All natural, no steroid! Aks him.
Sit down.
What will you have?
Tea or coffee, or...?
One espresso shot before workout,
now protein time.
Rani-ji, my card. Here.
Twenty-two karat gold plated.
Anyway, full intro. We have a shop
in Karol Bagh market.
First shop, biggest shop, our shop -
Dhanlakshmi Sweets.
You must've heard the name?
It's as famous as "Rahul"!
I wouldn't say we're the biggest,
we are the biggest!
We don't have attitude
like South Delhi-ites.
For rum: Bold Monk.
For vodka: Simrin-pop.
Full ground to earth!
That's lovely... what did you want?
- Is Jamini Chatter your granny?
- Chatterjee.
You added the 'Jee' to Chatter?
No. It's Jamini 'Chatterjee'.
It's a Bengali surname.
To answer your question,
yes, she's my granny.
Yes!
Tell me, Rani-ji, is your granny
dead or alive?
Dead?
Sorry. When?
No, shut up! She's alive.
Alive? That's good news.
So why say "shut up"?
Can you confirm this is your granny?
That's Thakuma.
My grandpa, Kanwal.
He has bad health problems
and a failing memory.
He cannot walk or talk,
but suddenly two days ago,
he said: "Jamini" and gave
some pretty lady a kiss.
Then I found a photo of your granny
in his poetry diary.
"Jamini" is written on the back.
It seemed fishy to me.
Krezzy, no?
Crazy.
Rani-ji, I love my grandpa
the most in this whole world.
I just want him to be OK.
Our doctor said this "Jamini"
may help with his memory.
She called it...?
A trigger.
So I thought if grandpa met her,
his old memories would be revived.
And he'd remember us again.
OK.
That's all. Can you show the photo
to your granny and call me?
Facetime. 24/7.
For you - avaylable.
OK.
- Bye.
Lund.
- What!
- Kanwal Lund. Grandpa's name.
- For granny to remember!
- OK.
OK.
- Bye.
Oh my God!
- Share the joke?
- Oh God, Somen.
You scared me!
- Guess what?
- What?
I have two tickets
for a jazz performance.
Piano-man? Two tickets.
Great, who you going with?
This is my grandfather's
ancestral home.
Grandfather has passed away, but
he's still remembered with great respect.
My mother, Anjoli Ray Chatterjee.
Delhi University's most senior
English Literature professor.
All I can say is -
the British have gone, but they
left her behind!
Ah, the prodigal daughter returns!
Hi, Ma.
Well, this isn't a boastful
rodomontade.
But, darling, I had envisaged
quite correctly so
that you'd be rather tardy
in reaching home this evening.
Our in-house Shashi Tharoor.
She means: 'I assumed you'd be late.'
Is father's class on?
My Baba - The best father in the world.
Chandon Chatterjee.
He used to be quite a famous Kathak
dancer in Kolkata.
But Ma got a terrific job in Delhi,
so he moved here with her.
Things aren't the same for him
as they were in Kolkata.
He teaches dance at home now.
He never complains, but I know
he really misses his stage.
And this is Jamini. My granny.
She loves poetry and old Hindi
film songs.
Thakuma!
Sweetie!
Dinner nearly ready?
Enough salt?
Delicious!
Esh! Freshen up first.
Silly girl!
- Rani.
- Yes?
I spoke to Somen.
He offered you two concert tickets.
And you declined without
as much as a confabulation?
You really keep tabs on Somen.
Why not marry him?
If I was your age, I would!
I positively bombilate with anticipation
every time I see the two of them
together.
Seriously, Ma, think of it.
Somen weds Rani.
Somen weds Rani!
Think about it.
God forbid. Rani did give it a try.
But what happened?
- They broke up within three months.
- Ah! So what?
And on top of everything else,
that fool was a bad lover.
Ask Rani. Tell her!
Actually, the boys of today,
they lack rhythm.
What do girls want? Rhythm!
See?
And boys go thump thump thump!
- Chandon!
- Baba is right, Ma.
There's zero chemistry between
Somen and me.
The problem is we look for chemistry
where it's not to be found.
You find it where you least expect it.
Love hits you like a storm, and you get
swept away like a tiny twig.
Speaking of storms. A real storm
swept through my office today.
If only you had seen him.
A real museum piece.
He asked me to ask granny about...
what was his name?
Kanwal Lund?
I think that was the name.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Sometimes fleeting moments
give you enough love
for a lifetime.
I can never forget that week.
In 1978,
I went with my sister Nandini
to Shimla for a holiday.
That's where I met Kanwal-ji.
At a poetry symposium.
When we heard a couplet by Firaq,
we both said "splendid"
at the same time.
It was like
I had met a soulmate
for the first time.
At first, we became close friends.
Then friendship turned into love.
We were both married,
and didn't have the courage
to break our homes.
So one day,
we both
made the decision to part.
That's all I have left.
So I just got my PR this year
and like...
Ah, here comes the tea.
And Golu too.
Namaste.
She doesn't look a bit like
her photograph.
You didn't send a full-length photo.
She's a little...
Do have some tea. And try our
special Dhanlakshmi laddoos.
Serve everyone, dear.
How many sugars?
I'm on like a sugarless diet.
You have Stevia? Sugar free?
There you go.
- And how many sugars for you?
- Thanks.
I'm on a diet.
Shall I send you the details?
Diet? Diet!
Everyone in our family is super healthy.
Our Shonty is a fitness freak.
Hiking-wiking, Tai Chi.
You too?
- Exercise?
- Excuse me?
It's OK if they don't share
the same hobbies,
but their hearts must match.
Personalities must match.
Ask Gayatri anything you want.
Shonty!
Fine. So, like, does marrying within
like the community matter to you?
Answer.
As mother said, hearts matching
is more important.
I have nothing against intercourse.
We must do it. It's important
for the community...
Not intercourse, inter-caste!
She meanz inter-caste.
Auto-krect problem.
She gets her words in a twist.
But never confuses numbers.
Sister is a state topper in mathematiz!
They want a bride, not an accountant.
Have your tea.
There's little else anyway.
- She's funny...
- Funny?
- Forget it! He was too short.
- Just leave me alone.
If your words come out wrong,
then stay silent. Get it?
But I won't stay silent.
She's been rejected 50 times.
But she's sworn never to lose weight.
- Who does she take after?
- Who do you think?
Oh!
Don't worry, sis.
I'll help you. From tomorrow
no cheato, only Keto.
Get lost! Did I ask you to help?
Big talker!
See how she answers back?
Forget it. Do I care!
Have you verified these numbers?
Are you sure?
Rocky, hurry up. We're getting late.
Bro, I must work sometimes.
Officyal signaytures.
Hello, Rocky Randhawa this side.
Hello?
This is Rani...
Rani Chatterjee.
Is the fire burning on both sides?
Excuse me?
I was talking about Kanwal
and Jamini.
I see.
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning.
Or were you thinking about us?
Why? You in-trusted?
Depends. Try a pick-up line.
OK! I'm a pupy, take me home.
Puppy?
Prospruss Urban Punjabi Youth.
Pupy!
You really are unique!
Glad you're so informal.
Listen, I need to see you.
Know the wrestlers' arena
in Roshanara Park? Come there.
A wrestlers' arena?
Not a coffee shop?
Remember my BFF cum-trainer, Vicky?
Yes, Vicky.
We'll meet at his grandpa's arena.
They're sallibrating a golden jubilee.
See you there.
You go ahead. We can meet tomorrow.
Must you always argue?
"Korbo, lorbo, jeetbo."
Sending you the location pin.
See you at 4.
See you there. OK, bye!
Why are you smiling?
Good afternoon everyone!
Welcome to today's entertaining
wrestling tournament!
Let's have a round of applause
for today's wrestlers.
Hello, Rani-ji!
Valcome! Valcome to Akhada-mela collab!
- Look naice.
- Thank you.
I see. You brought your brother
for your safety!
Rani-ji, don't go by my looks,
we are a good nature!
- I'm her colleague.
- Yeah.
Colleague?
Mother's side? Father's side?
He works with me.
Bro!
Somen... Rocky.
Rocky... Somen.
And bro, I can look after my safety
just fine.
Taek-won. Whoa!
Bring it here!
This is the best lassi in the whole
of Old Delhi.
- The best!
- Washing machine special. Cheers!
We boys call our WhatsApp group:
"Drinks lassi, trapped she is."
Essclusive guys talk only.
OK.
Don't think Rani-ji is going
to drink that lassi.
Delicate South Delhi-ite.
What were you saying?
You got the...
What?
Think we're done. Let's go, please.
Thank you.
I want to talk to him. One second.
I want to talk to you.
- Private?
- Ya.
Keep busy. Come side.
- No, no, bro. Where you going?
- Yes, Rani-ji... tell me.
I spoke to my granny.
And she wants to meet your grandpa.
Bullseye!
OK.
Bring your grandpa
over to our house.
No way. Grandma has grandpa
in lockdown.
He's under house arrest.
Can't blame her. When he goes out,
he's out of control.
Izz a bad scene.
OK, no worries.
We'll come to your place.
Sure.
Rocky!
Valcome! Come.
Done!
- OK.
- But tell me.
You could've asked me
on the phone.
I could've.
But how else to check you out?
I'm melting!
- I had better go.
- Where going?
Wait! My programme is about to start.
- Dance party.
- You're gonna dance?
I can't see any rhythm
in your body.
Esscuse!
Challenge?
Yeah!
Come. Let me show you.
Pretty lady. Pretty lady
Can't take my eyes off you
You're in the Rai Bareilly marketplace
Flaunting your beauty
She'll take your breath away
when your eyes meet
Pretty lady. Pretty lady
You're in the Rai Bareilly marketplace
Flaunting your beauty
She'll take your breath away
when your eyes meet
Decked in jewellery from head to toe
Watch out for the gust of wind
Your earring may fly off,
so don't say, 'Where's it gone?'
Your earring! Oh no!
What earring?
Oh no!
Pretty lady. Pretty lady
Can't take my eyes off you
So innocent on the outside
So fake on the inside
Why are you after me, you flirt?
Stuck like sellotape.
Pasted on like glue
A good-for-nothing.
You're a right fool
You're just looking for the chance
to hit a homerun
In case you find a missing earring
What earring?
Your earring did fall off!
Your earring fell off in the
Bareilly marketplace
Your earring did fall off!
How long have you known
my husband?
We met in 1978
at a poetry symposium.
You write poetry?
Oh no. I just like poetry.
And your husband?
He has passed away.
How many times did you meet
my husband?
About five or six times.
Five or six times?
Hear that? They met 5 or 6 times,
yet he keeps calling her name.
My husband.
Kanwal-ji... how are you?
Yes.
I'm Jamini.
Shimla Coffee House.
The poetry symposium?
The Firaq verse:
"The evening was filled with mist
"She was wistful and sad
"Old memories stirred this heart
of mine"
We went on walks.
We saw a rerun of 'Hum Dono'
at the Gaiety cinema.
Our favourite old song...
It's time for father to have
his medicine.
Thank you for your valuable time.
Ma, let's go.
Jamini!
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
You have only just arrived
Blossoming like the spring
Let the air spread your fragrance
Let us exchange a glance or two
Let the evening settle into night
Let my heart recover itself
Let me live this precious moment
Let me drink of this sweet nectar
You've hardly said a word
You've hardly heard me say much
Don't be offended by what I say
This is love and not a complaint
Don't leave me now.
My heart hasn't had its fill of you.
Bro, can I say something?
Grandpa turned out like the kisser
Emraan Hashmi, but for old folk.
He has such strong emotions
even now, he's just...
You're fokusing on his love story,
what about me?
Go to hell!
Rani Chatterjee is so classy,
bet she even sneezes in English.
So what! Aren't I aejucated too?
Didn't Papa buy me a top place
in 12th class?
- Oh wow! You're aejucated, bro!
- Legit, bro!
Just because you read the label on
a protein box doesn't make you educated.
- Oh, hello.
- Silly boy.
Didn't grandpa floor Jamini Chatter?
All in the genes, bro!
But grandpa knows poetry.
Do you?
Piping hot fish! Any takers?
Ah! Culinary genius.
Thank you, Ma.
Ma?
Cool. I've always wanted
a little brother.
Hey!
Hello to the Chatterjees!
You're having a party
and didn't invite me.
Sonam, you're like Rani's network.
Where she, there you.
So clingy!
Ma!
Rocky, might I entice you
with a drink?
- Can you repeat?
- Entice?
Drink?
Sure!
You are take-ing?
I also take-ing.
We are all... take-ing.
For you, ice or water?
On zee rocks!
I'll get you on the rocks.
Hi, Rani. How's you?
I'm fine.
You here to deliver laddoos?
Grandma says never go anywhere
empty-handed.
This is just a small...
Put it inside.
Actually, I wanted to talk.
Go ahead!
Come to side.
Yes, let's go.
OK?
Let's go where there's no network.
Oh... Somen.
If you need me,
just give me a call.
You're right here. Why should I call?
Yes. Correct.
Not "Sonam". It's Somen!
OK!
- Hmm.
- Hmm?
Speak up!
"In 1978,
"a love story was incomplete
OK.
"In 2022,
"they just had to meet.
"So grandpa could get back
his mammery.
"Rani is as sveet as jaggery!"
Jaggery?
I couldn't find another rhyme
for "mammery." So "jaggery".
You really are unique!
Unique?
Coming back to "they just had
to meet."
- There's one problem.
- What?
What about your grandma
and your dad?
What?
What they don't know, won't hurt them!
Simpal!
But where will my granny and your
grandpa meet? I mean...
Seriously? No better place for lovers
than Delhi.
That's true.
They will meet... but on the sly.
Know vot I meanz?
I know what you meanz.
Come, let us do back party join.
OK.
A time capsule of memories.
Riding on the wind,
floating with the clouds
Careful!
Riding on the wind,
floating with the clouds
Darling, let's fly
Take me along with you,
every day and night
Careful, come with me.
Hand-in-hand, we go
Darling, let's fly
This intoxicating evening
Makes my head spin
I can feel myself being pulled
towards you
This intoxicating evening
Makes my head spin
I can feel myself being pulled
towards you
How are you, my dear?
What's on your mind?
You got all stirred up, oh ho ho...
And slipped away just like that,
aa aa aa...
Where do we slip off to next?
I'm sending a pin, be careful,
don't get pricked.
The weather can't be trusted today
The weather today
There's a storm on its way
The weather is stormy today
The weather can't be trusted today
The weather today
Gain something, lose something
Lose something, gain something
Life is full of meetings
and partings.
I always wondered why granny loved
these old film songs.
Now I get it. She loved the memories
associated with them.
Life has no meaning without
our love story
Our love song
Love? No, I'm not in love with him,
Granny.
Me and Rocky - it's just a fling.
It's just a thing.
- Is it?
- Yes, it is.
Are you scared?
Absolutely not. You're overreacting.
Why are you ignoring your feelings?
Look, my sweetie, you and I
are so alike.
You are a part of me.
And for us nothing is ever
just a fling.
Just a thing.
- When you think about love...
- It's not love, Thakuma.
Everything is permitted in love.
Just think before you act.
You may hold the steering wheel
of relationships in your hand,
but it's family that does
the backseat driving.
I mean both our families.
Good night.
It's not love.
What time tomorrow?
Not tomorrow, the day after.
Tomorrow's my birthday.
Burrday?
That calls for a spashal sallibration.
No way! No celebrations.
I hate cakes, parties - everything.
In fact, I prefer working
on my birthday.
A burrday is the best day.
Can I give you a gift?
Day after tomorrow.
Oh no, naughty Chatterjee!
That gift is my duty!
What else can I give you?
Gucci? LV?
No, siree. Your choice won't do.
Let's meet the day after.
What's wrong with my choice?
A party is a must for you, Miss Chatterjee.
Vait and vatch!
- So Rani, what birthday plans?
- None. You know me.
Come on, baby. Sit in my car
We'll go on a long drive, full speed.
Stopping nowhere.
- Didn't I tell you?
- Come on!
- Go away.
- Please.
- No.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Sweetie, where to?
- Where?
- Right here.
Why have we come to this junk shop?
No patience at all.
- Right. Take right.
- OK.
Now?
Rocky?
Hallos and valcomes.
Vintaege vibes.
Listen! Miss Chatterjee,
my heart's matter-jee
The Calcutta girl is mad at me
Gotta make it better-jee.
B-e-t-t-e-r!
Listen! Miss Chatterjee
My heart's matter-jee
The Calcutta girl is mad at me
Gotta make it better-jee.
B-e-t-t-e-r!
- Rocky, what's all this?
- I know you liking old Hindi songs.
Your lover listened to many songs
to find one with your name!
'It's Rani's birthday.'
I know, Alexa, thank you very much!
I aalso know you don't like cakes,
but you can't have something
against laddoos.
Cakes have refined sugar,
and these have Indian ghee.
So haalth benefits!
Come over here and cut the laddoo.
Make a wish!
May Rocky's hotness and cuteness
be everlasting!
May his body-fat stay
in single digits.
A Chanel bag...
Happy Burrday!
Have a little. Don't get fat,
even if it's your burrdday.
Many happy returns of the day.
Thank you.
I was thinking like
this is a-spacious day.
So let's go all the way.
Make it a bigger day.
Rocky, I must go home.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. It's...
Thank you, it's lovely.
But I must get home.
My family's waiting for me.
Yes, you must be with the family
on your burrday.
It's all about loving your family.
Yeah, it's all about the family.
- Will you drop me home?
- Of course.
- Huh? I'll...
- Yeah.
The NGO in Kashmir has agreed.
When do you want to go?
Rani!
- Rani!
- Rocky!
Somen! I'm sorry. I-I heard you!
Guys, can we please take?
I gotta go. Yeah?
All right, guys, let's go for a take.
Thakuma and your grandfather are sitting
in the garden. They're singing loudly.
Where are you?
Rocky?
Rocky, what is all this?
Come on, Rocky. Stop it.
Where are you?
Hi, babez.
Valcome!
To garden of the galaxy!
I know you were feeling awks
yesterday.
Everything was low-key.
Then I realised,
to sweep Rani off her feet, we need
big canvas moviemaker Rajamouli.
Rocky, you don't -
Today was legs day.
But I skipped it.
So I can go down on my knees.
Rocky, please! Don't do that.
We love one another. So marriage
is the natural next stap, no?
OK, Rocky, slow down.
Whatever's happening between us...
I'm having a lot of fun.
But it's not a love story,
it's a lust story.
It's just physical, that's it.
Just a physical... nothing emotional?
Emotional? How, Rocky?
We've only just met.
Do you really know me?
We should understand each other's
feelings, thoughts.
What about politics, social reform,
defence, education?
- Do you have an opinion about anything?
- Have you ever asked me?
The problem is you think I'm a duffer.
Ask me something.
I'll outwit Google,
or my name isn't Rocky.
- Rocky, let it drop.
- Ask!
- No...
- Today you must.
I don't want to take an IQ test,
Rocky.
Ask me a question.
- Let it go!
- Ask!
Where in India is West Bengal?
In the West. But obvio...
- The East!
- A trick question.
- Another one.
- Rocky, never mind.
Rani, do you think
you're the only aedjucated one?
- Who is India's President?
- Dr. Rajendra Prasad.
Droupadi Murmu.
Rajendra Prasad was our
first president, Rocky.
You didn't spacify! First or last.
Are you serious? You're talking
like a kid now.
Rocky, the point is we're very different.
And more importantly, our families
are very different.
I'll be very honest with you.
Seeing your granny and mother veiled,
I felt suffocated.
Don't attack my family.
So why did you start our affair?
Was it only me?
You did nothing?
Basically,
- you were using my body.
- What?
In the 70s, your modern granny
used my grandpa.
Don't attack my family.
Let me make one thing very clear,
Rocky.
Neither of us used each other.
Whatever happened between us
was consensual.
Can you repeat?
Consensual means we did it willingly.
You were willing, so was I.
Grandma was right.
"Never be too sweet
or you'll be eaten up."
- Stop it, Rocky.
- Ya, let's stop it.
Yes, let's stop our story.
I'm breaking off.
Rocky, you're overreacting.
Rocky, stop!
Let's talk. Where you going?
To learn the names of our presidents.
Is this love or a college exam?
Like a fool I've had this ring
in my pocket for days.
I wear the latest fashion, Rani.
But my heart's old-fashioned.
I don't want just physical.
Mental, emotional, consexual.
All or nothing.
But you have nothing for me
in your heart.
OK.
Whatevs...
Rocky!
Rocky, say what you want.
Rani, listen.
Thakuma, it's too much.
I don't want to discuss this.
I shouldn't waste time with such a family,
nor should you. That's it.
Right. After all, it's just
a fling, just a thing. No?
Yeah.
It's just a fling.
Whenever I imagine you can't
do anything worse,
you break your own record.
Listen to his side.
- Papa-ji...
- Stop. Enough!
If I catch this Romeo and Juliet
together again,
you'll be walking over my dead body.
He blocked me.
Grandpa, you must forget Jamini.
These Chatterjee girls...
they are ditchers!
They are ditchers!
Give me a hug!
So, ready for the Kashmir work trip?
You know, Somen, I'm so ready.
And I'm so excited that I just
can't control myself.
- Somen.
- Hmm?
Can you hug me?
A hug? You know?
Here?
Then where?
Hug me, Somen!
Forget it.
- Let's try again. From this side?
- No!
It's fine... it's fine.
It's not fine.
Colourless were the days
Colourless were the nights
To my world
You brought colour
Bland were the moments
Lived till today
To my world
You brought life
Paths going nowhere
Now lead somewhere
You make all troubles disappear
You can be trouble too
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
My heart came to flower
With the coming of spring
Since the day we met
The pages of our life were blank
Without love in our lives
Heartaches run through lines
of verse
For those with love stories
There was a time when
we had no name
Now they call us the eternal lovers
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
My heart came to flower
With the coming of spring
Since the day we met
Get the proforma. Get the work done.
Come on, baby. Sit in my car
- Rocky.
- Go away!
Rocky, two minutes.
I want to talk to you.
Rocky!
Shut up!
Rocky and Rani
Rocky, stop!
Rocky and Rani's Love Story
Rocky, stop, please.
Their love is modern
But they fight conventionally
Rocky and Rani
Damn it!
Vot the bluddy hell! You're crazy.
I told you to stop the car.
I wrapped my car two weeks ago.
- Why did you block me?
- You sent hundreds of messages.
I didn't understand your English.
Be quiet. I want to talk.
You never let anyone speak.
Be quiet!
I'll do the talking. Shut up!
I graduated from LSR.
Did my post-grad in Columbia.
All my exes were high achievers.
Some in economics,
others in banking.
One is looking for the cure to cancer.
Seriously!
Then you landed up in my life,
with a protein shake in your hand
and a shirt wide open.
Limitless hotness and in strange English,
you said:
"Hi, Rani! How's you?
Rocky Randhawa this side."
My head said we had nothing
in common.
It's just a physical thing.
Just a fling, just a thing.
But, no...
I was wrong.
My heart got in the way.
Rocky Randhawa from Karol Bagh,
I'm in love with you.
I see you everywhere,
that kinda love.
I hear violins playing,
To hold your hand forever,
that kinda love.
Endless love,
Give our love story
another chance.
Rocky Randhawa this side.
Come to my side.
Please?
Please...
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
This is a story that has no end
No, not now. No, not now
No, no, no, no
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
Don't mind.
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
Don't go away, don't leave me now
My heart hasn't had its fill
of you
What will it be?
Dastination or Dhanlakshmi?
- What?
- Our wedding.
What is it now?
Roc -
Rani!
- So you want to get married?
- Yes.
Your groom is coming
on a white horse for you!
Hold your horses!
Tell me where will we live
after we get married?
- Randhawa Paradise. Where else?
- See! That's the problem!
What problem? After marrizz, the lady
moves to the husband's house.
After marriage, the wife moves
to her husband's!
Who wrote that rule? Is it
in the Constitution?
I dunno. I never read it.
Baby, it's not in the Constitution.
Everyone assumes the girl will live
at her husband's after marriage.
You move in and you'll see,
we'll adjust.
Adjust? When was the last time
you adjusted?
You never adjust. And eventually
I know what'll happen.
I'll end up doing all the adjusting,
and I'm not OK with that.
Don't get cross.
I'm not arguing. I agree with you.
Be gentle. Handle with care.
I'm a fragile.
My baby.
Once we get married, would you consider
living with my family?
- Don't split up my family.
- This is exactly what I'm saying.
Wouldn't my family be split up,
if I moved to Randhawa Paradise?
It must work both ways, no?
So let's have it your fancy way.
What do you want? Live-in?
I wish! Live-in won't change anything.
The problem is our families
are so different.
We may hold the steering wheel
in our hands,
but it's the family that does
the backseat driving. That's a fact.
Who drives from the backseat?
Nonsense, Rani.
I didn't mean it literally, Rocky.
- It's a metaphor.
- Metaphor, meanz?
- So our families are different.
- Our families are very different.
We have very different ideologies...
You want me to live with your family?
And you live with mine?
Are you suggesting you'll live
with my family and I... Oh my God!
Oh my God.
- Genius!
- Who?
You're a genius.
That's true!
What are you saying?
Ma, hear me out please.
It's outrageous.
Why are you experimenting
with your life?
In fact, if more people experimented
before marriage,
there'd be less divorces in the world.
Don't you think?
It's for only three months.
Think of him as a house guest.
House guest? A house pest!
Exactly. Exactly.
That Rambo... Randhawa...
- Rocky!
- Yes! Rocky.
You must understand Rocky...
Tomato allergy!
And I'm allergic to that boy.
Allergic is a bit overdramatic, Baba.
How can we possibly live with that madcap
for three months?
Plus that boy, he's got no class,
no standards.
Class and standards?
Father, you're so educated,
is this how you think?
No, no, one second.
I don't know about Rocky,
but I think you have double standards,
father.
Mind your manners.
- Did you hear what he said?
- What did I say?
Stop it!
Come here.
Ma, put some sense into her.
Tell me.
If neither of you can adjust
to each other's family, then what?
End of your relationship?
Thakuma, I know you ended your relationship
because of your family.
And I respect that.
But times have changed.
Rocky and I love each other very much.
We're going to make this work.
What's not working right now
are you guys.
You should support me.
Is that too much to ask?
Have you gone crazy? I'll give you
one slap.
Shut up! Don't butt in.
- How dare you?
- Tijori, one minute.
So, in three months, Rani will decide
if our family is worthy of her. Yes?
No, grandma. You're getting it all wrong.
What if we don't like Rani?
Will you do as I say?
Grandma, your word is final for me.
But for my sake,
give Rani a genuine chance?
I agree. I accept.
Go tell her.
- Mummy!
- I've said what I had to.
Now go!
I want to talk to Tijori alone.
Everyone, go.
The whole world is for me
Mummy, what are you doing?
You agreed?
Do you want to lose your only son?
Hmm?
Have you seen his eyes?
He's in love.
That love will turn to rebellion.
He'll turn his back on us and leave.
Who'll inherit our empire?
Who will be your heir?
Let the girl come.
Three months?
She won't last a week.
If I don't put an end
to their love story,
my name is not Dhanlakshmi.
Understand?
I see you near me, yeah
Take care of my heart, yeah
Why the distance between us?
I can see you
Without you the world is poison
No one can take you from me
I fought so much for you, yeah
I can't handle the heat,
you're fire
I'll make you mine,
that's my desire
I can't handle the heat,
you're fire
I'll make you mine
Baby, I'm your lover
[Chanting]
Sorry, my bags...
'Prasad' is first offered to guests.
Right hand.
- I wanted...
- Give some...
Give some to everyone in the house.
I'd like to say something.
I know that our culture,
our backgrounds, even our thinking
is very different.
- But we have something in common...
- We have nothing in common.
We do.
Our love for Rocky.
Since when have you known Rocky?
7 months, 17 days.
You have a good memory.
You hardly know him, and we've known him
all his life.
Ironically enough though,
sometimes a few moments give you
enough love for a lifetime.
Sometimes a lifetime together
doesn't give you love.
You have a way with words.
Your style must work on
your TV channel.
But our home is guided
by certain principles.
This is the first time we've broken
the rules.
We believe no decent girl
should be living in a stranger's house
without being married.
I have only one request.
Treat me as a family member,
not as a guest.
I'm sure we could try.
We are trying, that's why you're here.
Dinner will be served at 9.
You can't find the way.
Don't go round in circles.
Why don't you make use of the magnificence
of the global positioning system?
In English, please.
GPS is English.
Why do you always have to use
such big, huge words?
Hallo.
Hallo and valcome.
Rocky Randhawa!
All I wish to say, coming here today
I'm so heppy, so heppy.
I'm so full of heppiness
that I could burst!
Just too heppy to be here.
That calls for a team huddle.
No huddle? No cuddle?
- Rocky, come.
- Thakuma!
- Looking hot and sexy...
- Mother!
just like Sridevi in that song
about the endless night.
You crazy boy!
- Come!
- No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
No touching. Overfamiliarity
breeds contempt!
But why? I'm double vax.
Soshal distancing is over.
Who said it.
- Who?
- Who.
- Who, who?
- WHO.
World Health Organisation!
World Haalth Organisation!
Your general knowledge is weak.
Next time I'll give four option answers.
- Where going? Where going?
- Outside.
- I know you aalso want!
- I don't want it at all.
I don't want your cuddle.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Why are you allergic to a hug?
A hug is good for haalth!
A hug is important for being human.
A hug is like... a hug!
I get it! I get you and I get your hugs.
Hugging and dancing. He'll be dancing
the Bhangra all day.
Dancing 'Balle balle' is life.
It's a theory.
Good God! A coma would be more
pleasurable right now,
rather than this ridiculous diddly squat.
I do squat. 150 kilo.
New personal record!
- Huh?
- Yes.
Oh, ho, ho!
Respected grandfather!
That's Shree Rabindranath Tagore.
I know!
There was some filter on the picture,
so could not make out.
- What?
- Come on.
Let's go to your room.
Come on!
Grandpa?
Grandma sent this for you.
Another surprise.
Kanwal-ji. Red is your
favourite colour, right?
I knitted this muffler for you.
You must use it.
Isn't it amazing?
Our Rani is with you and your Rocky
is with us.
Looks like those unfulfilled
dreams of ours
are now the dreams of Rani and Rocky.
This time
they may just fulfill them.
Stay well. Your Jamini.
Pass me the 'bhindi'.
Rajma.
Paneer.
Just a little. Enough.
The phulka is cold.
I'll get you another.
Her phulka must be cold too.
Aunty, sit down. I'll get it.
No, Poonam, you go.
You're a guest. Sit down.
I insist, please.
Here you are.
Nice hot phulkas.
At home, we're used to fetching stuff
from the kitchen when we're eating.
We set the table together.
We serve one another.
And we clear the table together too.
That never happens here.
Here Mummy orgasms every day.
Organises... organises!
You're like the trader Harshad Mehta!
The stock market is strong.
Buy Tata.
- Gayatri?
- Bata!
I was ordering Bata shoes.
You want something?
No, I was going to the kitchen.
Need anything?
No, thanks. You carry on.
OK.
Yes, buy Ba... Tata.
You're still here?
Go. We need to get up early to pray
with grandma.
I'll do it. Go, good night.
If I found someone like you
Life would be easy
If I found someone like you--
I usually drink hot milk
with turmeric at night.
I'll heat up the milk for you.
Don't worry, aunty, I can do it.
You've already done enough today.
I enjoy making hot phulkas
for my husband.
My mother used to make
hot phulkas for my father.
So did my grandma.
That's our tradition.
Does that mean it's right?
Must you decide what's right
or wrong?
There's nothing wrong in serving
your husband.
I agree. In fact, there's nothing
nobler than serving others.
But if service is only one way,
it isn't service,
it's slavery.
Good night.
Alexa! Snooj.
Snooj.
What's with uncle?
- Is he possessed by the star Madhuri?
- Madhuri?
He's practicing his dance steps.
- Kathak.
- Gents' Kathak?
Sit down.
Very humid and sweaty!
Want some tea?
Let me.
Only 42% are voting, it's appalling.
Only 42%? Really?
Voting is our national duty
as citizens.
The voting lines must have closed
by now.
- Voting lines?
- I've stopped voting.
You stop voting too. Shamita
is out of the house.
- Shamita?
- Shamita.
Which constituency
does she represent?
Bigg Boss!
Son, will you have some tea?
No, grandma says drinking tea darkens
the skin.
So? What's wrong with being dark?
Of all the things, he's also
decidedly racist!
No, no, aunty. It's not like that
at all.
Black Lives Matter.
I have no personal problem with Black folk.
Beyonce and Rihanna are lovely.
When I cruise around at night,
it's hip-hop.
Drake, Kanye West...
My favourite song at weddings
that always make me dance...
"Black is beautiful"
"Black is beautiful,
like my dark skinned beloved"
"Keep the fair-skinned ones away"
Sing with me!
Very good, very good.
So do you want black coffee?
Go to the kitchen. Left of the stove,
on the second shelf, there's coffee
and sugar.
- If you need milk, it's in the fridge.
- No milk for me.
Go make it.
Self-service?
Like food court?
Go!
I can do whatever I want
Under the canopy of roses
Put this in the kitchen.
Do you need something?
No, I thought I'd spend
a little time with you.
You think a lot.
He doesn't even know how to turn
on a gas stove.
He thinks Tagore is your grandfather.
Hallos!
- Shobha.
- Somen.
- You here too?
- Bring it in!
- Rani, let's go!
- Nice to meet you.
It's Rani's break time.
You go ahead.
Disgusting!
What are you doing?
Someone will see us.
- Can't you even light a gas stove?
- Can't you eat without talking?
Without talking! Guts!
I was just trying to help your mother.
You're the baest girlfrand.
- How's my mom treating you?
- She dislikes me.
- And how's my mom?
Your home is on the other shore
O stranger from a distant land
I've seen you on autumn mornings
I've seen you on fragrant nights
I've seen you
I hear you in my heartbeat
O stranger from a distant land
Bravo!
Wow, Jamini! Outstanding!
You're great, Thakuma.
- Rocky!
- Bravo, Jamini!
It's amazing that you still
don't need reading glasses.
- And cheers to that!
- Cheers!
I agree! You don't need glasses.
Drink straight from the bottle.
Who's that?
Rocky. Our house guest.
Hallo! Hallo!
Rocky, this is our culture club.
Come, join us.
Ma, I don't think that's such
a great idea.
Rocky will get bored.
After all, this is a culture club thing.
Rocky, go to your room.
Do your exercises.
Or go and rest.
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
Yaa... recovery is important.
Hmm.
Won't you also sing?
I don't have my glasses today.
Rocky made a fool of himself
in front of
the very doyennes of high art
and culture during culture club.
How can you imagine marrying him?
Ma!
Think about it. He has no class,
no education,
no language, no culture-
Ma, he has a good heart!
So does my cardiologist.
- But I don't want you to marry him!
- I'm going now. I'll call you later.
Can't waste cake.
- It's sugar free.
- Fat free.
- Gluten free.
- And free.
- Milk and turmeric?
- No, no, I'll make it.
Don't worry.
Please carry on eating freely.
If I found someone like you
Life would be so easy
Aha, life would be so easy
If I found someone like you
A new life would be born
He would father a new life
Father a new life? Don't sing
your version in public!
A flower needs the spring...
And the spring...?
What about the spring?
A flower needs the spring,
the spring needs the garden
The heart needs a heart,
a body needs a body
Everyone longs to meet
their soulmate
Hope I find my soulmate too
Whoa! Go for it!
Life would be so easy
Follow me!
If I found someone like you
Life would be so easy
Wow, aunty! You sing brilliantly!
- Really?
- Yes.
I used to sing on the Prasar Bharati
radio station.
Everyone said I'd be the next
Asha Bhosle.
And then?
I got married.
So?
In our home, getting married
is a girl's greatest dream.
And your dream?
Compromising is better than dreaming.
At least you don't get disappointed.
Poonam! I'm fed up.
My husband will not eat,
or have his pills.
- Go to him.
- Yes.
Let me try.
- Hello, Aunty! Howr' you?
- How can I help you?
I was going to ask about my dirty
clothes. Londry?
Laundry? Go to your room, dial 9.
Somebody will be at your service.
OK.
Ah! I know you're playing a fun!
You are very jokey!
It's one of my strongest suits.
Actually, my cloths are dirty.
Tell me what to do and I'll do it.
Go to your bedroom,
remove your clothes. I'm coming.
What is it?
That's wrong, Aunty.
You're Rani's mother.
Goodness me, no, no!
Not these clothes, you silly boy!
Your dirty clothes.
Keep the whites separate.
I don't want any kind of fuss over
pettifogging details later mind you.
- I didn't got you.
- I didn't 'get' you.
- I aalso.
- Huh?
Aunty, I don't want to give you
any load.
In fact, you should give me yours.
Phone me if there's anything
I can do. At your service!
Just tell me if I can do
anything for you.
Frankly, there's nothing now.
I'm just about to embark
on a shopping expedition.
Shopping!
You're off to the market?
I'm coming too!
The thrill of going to a market
can never be felt online.
What will you do there? I'm going
shopping for lingerie.
That's OK.
I can carry the bags for you.
My workout for the day.
Whenever I go to a mall,
I cause a riot!
I'm an expert shopper.
My choice is...
Come along.
We'll max out our cards today!
Ma, 36B. Rani, 32B and I'm 34C.
Your seat number? You're going
to the pictures?
SRK's latest is playing.
Pictures?
I told you, I'm shopping
for bras.
Come on, there's a shop.
- What are you buying?
- A bra.
Wow! There's some lovely
new stock in here.
Oh Chintu, Chintu! How are you?
I'm like always happy Diwali, Aunty.
OK then, show me something
new and exquisite.
We have a buffet of items.
Show me a Balconette.
Something with lace.
A classy type.
Here's your balcony!
Yes, this is nice.
- Rocky?
- Nice.
But last time, there was a tad bit
of inconvenience with the hook.
It won't happen now. This stock is new.
I'll show you.
- I'll try it on.
- I don't think so.
Also, I don't think so.
Brother!
- Me?
- You!
Didn't you say you wanted
to help?
Come here. It won't take a minute.
Lift your arms up.
Now through the straps.
Go on...
Very good. Very nice. See?
You look smart.
Buy one for yourself.
Chintu!
Let me hook it up for you.
- It isn't working.
- No, no, it'll work.
It's not staying in place.
It's the hook.
Look! A perfect fit.
What the hell is going on?
What is all this?
Get it off me. I don't want to wear it.
This... this...
This, this, this!
This is a bra!
Short for brassiere!
I wear one, your mother wears one,
your sister too.
Your granny wears one. It doesn't
spread Covid. So what's the problem?
I'll tell you what the problem is.
Indian women, for centuries,
have washed their husbands' underwear.
Scrubbing and scrubbing away!
And you can't touch a bra?
But you can dance to the song
"What's behind my blouse?"
Dance your vulgar dance.
But actually saying what's behind
the blouse embarrasses you.
What's behind the blouse?
Actually, Aunty,
I don't touch it out of respect
for laddiz.
When you stop thinking they're unlike you
- some strange species -
and treat them as equals,
then you'll be respecting ladies.
- Show me something else.
- I'll unhook it.
Done, thank you.
Yes, Aunty, tell me.
Do you have the pink one?
Poonam?
- Yes, Mummy-ji?
- Has my husband had his breakfast?
He's had his breakfast
and his pills.
Hello. Yes.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen, please!
We have a crisis on our hands.
And it's goddamn serious.
Look, I'll be the first one to admit.
I knew this ad campaign
was a terrible idea.
- What?
- But what's done is done, ma'am.
Women are our greatest consumers.
Because of this ad,
'Boycott Dhanlakshmi'
is trending at number 1.
We must do damage control!
These female do-gooders
just want the chance to make trouble.
Sir, please.
The situation is serious.
I think we should withdraw the ad.
We have no other option.
And the loss of millions?
What are you saying, Tijori?
In the 80s, this same ad created
a storm.
- Everyone was crazy about it.
- Exactly.
Hope you're listening, Rocky?
Ma'am, that was the 80s.
We're now in 2023.
Our share price is down.
We must at least admit we made
a mistake.
Put out an apology.
Just a minute!
Is this a fish market?
Calm down. Let's see why the ad
has made everyone so angry.
Play it!
Show us!
Pushpa!
Jaya!
Roopa!
At dawn rises the traditional wife.
She asks her husband,
what he'll eat today.
What will you have?
For years the answer
has always been the same -
How could anyone forget
the taste of...
Dhanlakshmi laddoo!
For me and for you!
From our kitchen to your kitchen.
Dhanlakshmi Sweets.
Eating them makes you burst with joy.
For me and for you!
It's terrific!
Are you serious?
- Baby? What'r you doing here?
- I'm so sorry.
You didn't answer my call.
So I came up.
It's OK.
Come, there's no problem.
I'm really sorry.
- Miss Rani Chatterjee?
- Yes.
My staddy GF.
You not like this advertise?
No.
What's issue?
It's so outdated. I'm not surprised women
are boycotting the brand.
To be very honest, it is sexist,
it is regressive...
That's what you think.
Uncle, it's what your consumers
think too.
Excuse me. If I could ask Miss Chatterjee
to elaborate?
After all, she's the woman of today
- and represents our ideal consumer base.
- This guy...
If the board won't object...
- No, no. I really shouldn't.
- Why would we object?
We've seen the wind changing
many times.
But those winds cannot change
Dhanlakshmi.
Yes!
With all due respect, the wind
and the times have changed.
Perhaps it's time for Dhanlakshmi
to change.
What you meanz?
I mean making laddoos
or cooking a meal at home
is no longer only the woman's job,
then why must the ad say that?
That's right!
I mean...
So according to you,
what must this ad say?
What do you mean? According to me?
I'm no expert.
Tell us.
I'm just saying,
think of something new.
- Something new?
- Why only women?
Men can serve laddoos too.
It's almost like...
"New thinking, great old taste."
That's an excellent line.
That works!
"New thinking, great old taste."
Hashtag!
What do you say, Papa?
I come here on Sundays
so that I'm not disturbed.
Come.
I could help you.
These laddoos... press too hard
or too softly,
and they fall apart.
Like relationships.
When I was 7, I made a laddoo
for the first time with my grandma.
From that day on making laddoos
has made me happy.
What is it?
It's just so inspiring.
You're as passionate about
your work as ever. And ambitious.
In that sense, we're so alike.
Your idea for the ad was good.
Thank you.
No, please, don't thank me.
No, no. You deserve to be thanked.
You're our guest for just a few days,
yet you've been so helpful.
You deserve a thank you.
Pardon?
You and I are not alike.
Nor will we ever be.
For you, you come first.
For me, the family does.
You can make the ad or a laddoo,
you can't make ties
with this family.
Who told you family isn't important
to me?
Family and relationships are equally
important for a career woman.
Who knows that better than you?
Your empire is even named after you:
"Dhanlakshmi Sweets".
And about making lasting ties,
where hearts are one,
ties will be made too.
Because the heart heeds no one.
Game on!
Rani, Rani! I am Rani
The girl who knows it all
Argue and you'll look foolishly small
Do you think you can beat me?
Don't you know I'm the queen bee?
A tsunami of tweets.
The shares are up and up.
Number one viral trend all India!
And all thanks to you.
Without you, Dhanlakshmi Sweets
would've turned bitter.
Just see what the press is saying:
"Dhanlakshmi make a powerful and
progressive statement in new ad."
I understand what 'powerful' is.
But what is 'progressive'?
- You really are unique!
- Whatever I am, I'm yours.
Let's celebrate!
We're going to celebrate
at Vicky and Minty's sangeet.
Sister is getting married
Valcome, Chatterjees.
The original families are here.
Aunty, I know you miss me.
Hi, Rani.
- How I look? You like?
- Very good.
Let's say hallo to my family.
The Chatterjees are here.
Grandpa, the Chatterjees are here.
Namaste.
Kanwal-ji, how are you?
You came, Jamini.
I'll be right back.
Let me show them to their seats.
No problem. We're all family.
You'll sit near the cooler.
I'm sending over a waiter.
I'd gone away for 12 years,
when I came back I brought a car.
Let's start the party
Grandma Dhanlakshmi!
- Granny, please!
- Why are they after her?
Granny, dance with us!
Granny, Granny, Granny.
Look, I don't know how to dance.
I'm sorry.
But there's a great artist here today,
if he dances for us,
it will be our honour.
Calcutta's famous dancer,
Mr. Chandon Chatterjee.
Come!
Sir, please come to the stage.
One second.
Papa, this isn't right.
Come, please come onto the stage.
A big round of applause
to welcome on stage, Chandon-ji!
Long live our Chandon uncle!
Wonderful!
Dhanlakshmi-ji, I'd like to thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
What an opportunity!
What a great audience.
Nothing could please an artist more.
Come on.
What music can you play to dance
the Kathak?
The Kathak? You're a Bengali,
so a 'Devdas' song is a must.
- DJ, play a song from 'Devdas'.
- So typical.
Another big round of applause
for Chandon-ji!
Two and a half evenings have stopped,
have stopped, have stopped
and you playfully kissed me
You playfully kissed me,
you playfully kissed me
My scarf slipped away from my head,
went away, went away
sliding, sliding, sliding
Why do you tease and provoke me,
making my heart dance
Why do you tease and provoke me
What kind of dance is this?
Uncle...
I... wanted to say sorry.
It's OK.
I'm used to it.
The first time
I told my father
I wanted to learn Kathak,
he made fun of me too.
When I insisted, he got furious.
He even hit...
When I joined Kathak classes,
I was the only male student there.
All my friends became engineers
and doctors.
I told everyone I was going to be
a professional Kathak dancer.
They made so much fun of me
behind my back, saying
"That bloody loser."
I won't lie.
It makes a difference.
I'm a human being...
it's hurtful.
But I never ever thought
of giving up dancing.
Know why?
Because my mother
always stood by me.
She said:
"Son, talent has no gender."
And I live by that.
I've messed up so badly.
I stand here before you,
if I'm to blame for anything else,
tell me.
Why use swear words that insult women?
What misogyny!
So I can't swear now?
Aunty, I'm from Delhi.
How can I not swear?
What times we live in!
Can't call fat people 'fat.'
Can't call Black people 'black.'
Can't call the old, 'old.'
Scared to open my mouth.
Can I call Chinese food
'Chinese'?
What if I'm ordering Chinese,
what do I say?
Should I say? "Yes, sir. The place
right of Himanchal.
"Our neighbour! The Corona guys.
"Yes, I want a Crispy Chicken."
Now you'll say, I can't say
'Corona guys'.
Since I was a small boy,
my grandma said:
"Drinking tea darkens the skin."
Now I realise this is racist.
No one told me some swear words
are missaaginy.
They didn't tell me calling my sister
'Golu' was fat-shaming.
Talking like that felt normal.
Never thought it was wrong.
Never knew I'd be hurting someone
if I used such words.
Tell me.
What would you call the words
you've used to describe me?
Rocky doesn't know how to turn on
the gas stove. Whattey shame!
Rocky doesn't know men can also
go bra shopping. Whattey shame!
Rocky doesn't know men can dance
Kathak. Whattey shame!
And what's the biggest shame?
Rocky doesn't know English.
Whattebad! Whatteworst!
All confirmed, he's cancelled.
I'm no one to talk. But I will say,
if we keep cancelling each other,
we'll never learn anything in life.
I thought if I came here, I could win
your hearts. But what's with you all?
No one will hug me,
or touch me.
You laugh at the way I speak.
You're ashamed to introduce me
to your friends.
You think I'm blind to your attitude?
That I can't feel? That it doesn't
hurt?
How can you shame me? I'm so ashamed
of myself anyway.
And especially today.
Uncle,
by God, I'm touched by the things
you said.
Did you know dancing makes me
happy too?
But I don't have the guts
to dance in front of my family.
My father has a problem
with me dancing.
I could never challenge him.
I have never fought for
my own happiness. I'm a big loser.
I respect you deeply, uncle.
I'm sorry.
You gave me a place in your home.
Thanks a lot.
God bless.
Rocky.
Won't you give me a hug?
Cuddle?
Baba! You OK?
I've been calling you for hours.
Baba,
I think I should come home.
I don't think this is working.
No, Rani. You must stay there.
Baba, how?
They were making fun of you.
Forget that. Rocky was too.
That's not OK, Baba.
Didn't we laugh at Rocky?
Didn't you?
He isn't perfect, neither are we.
You think love is perfect, Rani?
Well?
From this body of mine
Veiling the soul and spirit
A punishment? Or a blessing?
Are these stories of love
OK, students! Ready?
- To show respect we bow mid-way.
- But respect must be all the way.
O crazy one!
- O crazy one! O naïve heart of mine
- Come on, let's start.
O crazy one!
O crazy one! O naïve heart of mine
You lose yourself in love
Never to be found again
I'm learning how to make
an Americano from YouTube.
You chose a cage over the open sky
Refusing the chance to break free
Why are you so obsessed
with crypto?
You'll make a profit...
I'll call you back...
How long will you trade
in secret, Gayatri?
You're so good. Do it professionally.
- Professionally?
- Yes.
Impossible.
Gayatri, it's time you gain confidence.
And if you need any help,
I'm here. OK?
Go, fall in love if you must.
Be stubborn if you must
O crazy one!
In love you will find
you'll be left with nothing
Here it comes.
One more...
Enough, Rani.
He remembers your name?
He uses it sometimes.
- He hasn't called my name in years.
- Will you feed him?
Ignoring yourself, you heed the other
Is this love? Or a blunder?
If this is a blessing,
then why the punishment?
A moment's attachment
Will make you sleepless forever
Heed the words of the selfish
Who find the goal they seek
The easy way was never your way
If the world curses, let it curse
Never count your suffering
So have your way
O crazy one! O naïve heart of mine
Straight from the heart!
If they do not heed your call,
walk alone
Walk alone, walk alone
If they do not heed your call,
walk alone
Rani has become so close to Papa-ji.
He listens only to her now.
I am a stranger to him.
You weren't permitted to show him
that you cared for him.
O crazy one
O crazy one!
O naïve heart of mine
Go, fall in love if you must.
Be stubborn if you must
O crazy one
In love you will find
you'll be left with nothing
O crazy one
Go, fall in love if you must.
Be stubborn if you must
O crazy one
In love you will find
you'll be left with nothing
O crazy one
- Talent Contest, wild card entry!
- What?
I took a chance and videoed you
the other day. You've been selected!
Your audition is on Saturday at 7.
See?
What's wrong?
How dare you?
- I thought you'd be happy.
- Happy?
You can be a rebel.
But do you want me hung?
What do you want?
I don't want anything, I...
Actually, that's a lie.
I want you to show yourself
the love and respect you show others.
Give yourself a chance
to be happy.
Don't be a symbol of weakness
but strength for Gayatri.
That's what I want.
Ma, the Rana Mart owners are coming
to see me on Saturday.
Grandma says they've approved
my full length photographs.
And what did you say?
This is called a spine.
You can't buy one. You must use
the one you have.
Ah, here's the tea.
And so is Golu.
Come, child.
Yashpal Rana's younger brother,
Gopal Rana. Rana and Rana.
Some tea?
We're not here to drink tea.
We've come to see the girl.
Well, my little Rana! You like her?
Like her?
He's shy.
We like your daughter.
Congrats!
We wanted a plumpy girl like her.
Why keep it from you?
Yashpal's first wife was Miss Noida.
The whole neighbourhood eyed her up,
and she eyed them back.
Divorced in two months.
That's why we like your girl.
So we don't make the same mistake twice.
Well, child?
Any hobbies?
Cooking, cleaning, embroidery,
painting...?
Answer the question, Golu.
- Yes, singing.
- Singing?
Since when?
If you don't mind, can I sing for you?
Sing! Join in the rhythm!
Yes.
Why do you cover your face
with that long veil?
Girl, did you bring shame on us?
My brother-in-law was sleeping
on the roof terrace
I thought it was you
and lay down beside him
Mr. Rana, forgive me
I made a little mistake
Gupchup. Gupchup. Gupchup.
You insolent girl!
You're behind what happened today. You!
It wasn't Golu, it was her.
- It was me.
- Golu...
My name is not Golu.
My name is Gayatri. Gayatri!
I put on 20 kilos,
and you made me lose
all my self-respect.
Did you ever wonder why my words
come out wrong?
Why I can't speak properly?
Why call me "Golu"?
Why "Golu?" Ever thought about it?
All this is because of you.
You think I'm round like a
Dhanlakshmi ladoo, ready to sell.
It's enough. More than enough!
I'm going to work
at India Now Network.
And I'll marry, if and when
I feel like it.
Given my legacy, marriage
seems impossible, to be honest.
My respects.
Seven o'clock!
It's seven!
What's going on?
Aunty. Aunty, one second.
All the best!
Poonam, I'm getting late.
- Listen, please.
- Yes?
Rani's family organises a grand
Durga Prayer every year...
- We are not going.
- They've invited us.
I said we are not going.
If not for our sake,
then for the Goddess?
Hail Ma Durga!
Season's greetings to you all.
And welcome to CCAD.
Chittoronjon Cultural
Association Durgotsav.
As you know, every Maha Astami
we perform a dance here.
But not this year.
Today we'll deviate a little
from our traditional format.
Breaking our anti-Bollywood
stance,
we bring you a unique performance.
Go, Baba!
Let us dance, let us sway.
All eyes are on me.
Let lightning strike
Lightning, lightning.
All eyes are on me.
Let lightning strike
I will tie my dancing bells
to my ankles
And I will dance, I will rejoice
Let us dance, let us sway.
[Chanting]
Breaking all barriers
Loving without reserve
The world can stop us,
if it so desires
There's no shame in loving
No greater duty than loving
No one can turn against us
No one can match us
when we dance together in step
Arm in arm, we'll dance
the night away
Hear the drums play
When hearts are entwined
nothing can separate them again
Hear the drums play
Counting the days,
counting the stars
The passionate ones
Counting the days,
counting the stars
The passionate ones
Fly on the wind if you choose
With wings of dreams
now pinned on you
Adorn yourself with every
colour of the rainbow
Whatever you may say,
luck is on your side today
Your face glows like the moon
Hear the drums play
When hearts are entwined
nothing can separate them again
Hear the drums play
[Chanting]
Papa-ji.
Papa-ji! You can't walk out
in the middle of the prayers.
Rocky, you don't belong to us anymore.
You've become their performing monkey.
You want to marry into that family?
Her father is a shameless dancer,
ready to entertain menfolk.
He can't control the women in his family.
Her mother drinks.
Her grandmother is a flirt.
Right?
Your girlfriend has no manners.
Her family is totally rotten.
You're right. We're immoral.
We don't believe women
are men's property.
Rocky, I won't speak to her.
We don't get our daughters
married against their will.
- We don't stifle dreams.
- Rocky, tell her!
We don't live in fear,
we love each other.
Only the lucky few are immoral
like us.
Rocky, shut her up!
But I'm talking.
You can say whatever you want,
but you should listen too.
How dare you raise your hand?
- I did not...
- Rani, you dare raise your hand?
I didn't do anything.
Didn't you hear what he just said?
He insulted my family.
He didn't. He was talking to me.
Just me.
You came in between us.
So? I heard him. Did you want me
to shut up?
- Like your women folk do?
- Don't drag them into this.
When he was dragging my family
into this, where were you?
One second. I have a problem
with my father too.
But I thought we shouldn't argue
on a festival day.
You told me to talk to him.
So let me handle it.
You can't even be upfront with him,
or look him in the eye.
I know his ways, but I ignore them,
because I respect my elders.
Keep your phony respect.
They're our elders, but they still
don't have the right to insult others.
Elders should be worthy of respect.
I can't bear you humiliating my father.
Likewise.
You should not have raised
your hand.
Your family must've taught you that.
And you're right.
We are very different.
No matter how much we try,
we'll always be different.
This difference won't end.
We're done now, Rocky.
You lied the other day.
Family doesn't come first for you.
Congrats!
In your house only one woman
can be happy.
You.
Dhanlakshmi, my respects.
Can't believe you.
I would not have said a word,
but they insulted you, father.
Whatever the provocation,
why raise your hand?
I didn't.
You were there. You saw what happened!
Yes, Rani, I saw. But your father
is right.
Just one second!
Of all people, you're taking
Rocky's side, Ma?
I have no qualms in admitting
that I was wrong about him.
Are you crazy?
After all, he is his father's son.
And his mother's.
- Aren't you being patriarchal now?
- Yes, he's his mother's son,
but he never stood by his mother.
As if he'd stand by me.
Thakuma, you understand me?
You said family does the backseat
driving in relationships.
I know his family does.
How will I survive? Tell me!
- Rocky isn't like that.
- How do you know?
Honestly, you shouldn't be giving us advice.
You cheated on grandpa.
Rani!
So I cheated!
I don't regret it for a minute.
But I do regret bottling it up
for all these years.
Your grandpa used to hit me.
He'd beat your father with a belt.
He was disgusted by his son
wanting to dance.
He hated him.
You want to judge Tijori?
So hear this.
On the surface, your grandfather
looked so gentle,
but inside, he was another Tijori.
Your father is unlike his father.
Just as Rocky is unlike his father.
The love I was showered with
in those brief seven days,
I never got in my long years
of marriage.
Love was not in my destiny, Rani.
But it is in yours.
Decide if you want to become
a 70-year-old Jamini,
someone who waited for love
all her life.
Tell me!
Did you hear what she said?
I knew she was pure trouble.
I'll never forget the way
I was humiliated today.
My humiliation was even greater.
Hey! Switch the TV off!
Tijori, you saw how my husband
was running after that Jamini.
And that Rani has spread poison
in this house.
I said, put the TV off!
Pulling my veil free
Breaking all barriers
No one can stop my heart
from flying
There it goes!
When did this happen?
She has shamed us.
No one can stop my heart
from flying
There it goes!
Today I want to live again
Today I want to die again
You wretched woman!
Rocky, are you in your right mind?
For the first time I am, Grandma.
You know what I learned
in their home?
The respect I felt for you both,
was not respect, but fear.
- I'm not scared anymore.
- Talk politely to your grandma.
First talk politely to my mother.
You fool! You dare answer
your father back?
Father?
A father who was not a loving son,
how could he be a loving father to me?
You know, Papa.
I can't explain how much I love Rani.
She didn't respect you,
or the elders of my family.
So I broke off with her.
I consider my mother like a goddess.
But you show her no respect.
So we must part ways.
I hope you enjoy your grand home,
your business,
your wealth, your arrogance, Tijori-ji.
I'm leaving home.
My son will not leave alone.
Absolutely not.
You can't be of our blood.
Wrong, Grandma.
Your blood does run in my veins,
but there's no trace of you
in my heart.
Who are you to me?
Blood ties and love ties
are not the same.
Love makes relationships.
Such a pity you could never love.
So now you're all alone.
Now live with yourself.
Tijori...
Papa-ji.
Papa-ji, you took my name?
Tijori.
My son.
Never break up the family.
Papa-ji!
- Rocky.
- Grandpa.
Check his pulse.
Get the car out! Papa-ji...
Grandpa's pulse is very weak.
Nurse!
Doctor!
Tijori!
Cry your heart out, Ranjha
Parted from your Heer
Cry your heart out
Cry your heart out, Mirza
Parted from your Sahiba
Cry your heart out
The heartless spider struck
Spreading its poison
Listen to our plea, O God!
Show pity on lovers
who are pulled apart
All happiness in life is nothing
without my beloved
No prayer, no balm can heal
this deep affliction
Swallow your youth
The two streams that flow
from your eyes
Tijori, tell her to leave.
Let me say a last goodbye.
It's Jamini.
Made of strong clay
Yet hearts are made of fragile glass
Those who are fated to break
do so at your gestures
Lovers not fated to live
as one
O Lord, never let them meet
Why take pleasure in their pain?
When it is nothing to you
It's all a twist of fate
Let lovers live
They don't know the ways of the world
He was my soulmate.
Cry your heart out, Ranjha
Parted from your Heer
Cry your heart out
Poonam.
I know I do not deserve
to be forgiven,
- but if you can...
- No.
It's too late.
You lost the right to say sorry.
You aren't worthy of respect,
nor is your mother.
She didn't respect women,
despite being a woman herself.
What could be worse than that?
In raising you as the man of the house,
she forgot you were not only
her son,
but also your father's son.
And a father to your children.
And you are my husband.
Now you're imprisoned by regret,
and I am free.
Be well in your confinement,
Mr. Tijori.
Disrespectful woman! Is that how you
talk to your husband?
First learn how to talk
to my wife.
Tijori.
You dare shout at your mother?
Is this how I raised you?
Raised me, Mummy?
You hardly did.
You made me an arrogant man.
That arrogance is hollow.
You were right, Poonam.
I'm unworthy of forgiveness.
But I'll try my best to earn
your forgiveness.
I have lost my father.
I don't want to lose
my wife and children.
I will not lose them.
Thakuma, I'm going out...
We came here to apologise.
I'm responsible for all the problems
that have come between us.
- Forgive me if you can.
- Uncle, please.
I was wrong to do
and say what I did.
I insulted our love by insulting you
the other day.
Rocky may never forgive me,
but you must, uncle. I'm really very sorry.
No, my dear.
We really want Rocky
to marry into your family.
If you all agree...
...and you agree too.
A heartbroken lover
waits for you outside.
How long will you be cross with me?
I'll hold you close
so you won't stay mad at me
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
Come, sit in my car, babe
Long drive, full speed,
stopping nowhere
Shut up!
Can't you see she is emotional?
Hi.
I am dyed in your colours now.
Everything is Rani Pink.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I'm really sorry.
In love, no sorry, no thank you!
This is Rocky and Rani's love story.
Can't be brushed off
like dandruff!
- You really are unique!
- Whatever I am, I'm yours.
- I love you!
- I love you from last life.
Will you kiss me?
Or do I hit you?
One second.
Give us happy vibes!
Paths going nowhere
Now lead somewhere
You make all troubles disappear
You can be trouble too
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
My heart came to flower
With the coming of spring
Since the day we met
At this age, my pride and self-respect
won't allow me to think
that perhaps I was wrong.
So I give you this peace offering:
the secret laddoo recipe
that my grandmother gave me.
I trust you will not make
the same mistakes that I have made.
Congratulations on your wedding, dear.
A long life to you.
There's the girl with stars
in her eyes
Here she comes, the lovely bride,
bringing spring with her
The wedding music plays,
tears well in every eye
There's the girl with stars
in her eyes
Here she comes, the lovely bride,
bringing spring with her
The wedding music plays,
tears well in every eye
Childhood passes so quickly
Like the months of spring
Now your new life begins
In your dear husband's home
Feels like home to you
Now your new life begins
May the evil eye never fall on you
Your parents' home is full
Adorned with marigolds
Your palanquin is ready
Those days of your childhood
No one can stop them pass by
Now your new life begins
There's the girl with stars
in her eyes
Here she comes, the lovely bride,
bringing spring with her
The wedding music plays,
tears well in every eye
When you bid farewell
to your parents
You will take their joy with you
Who does the birdsong awaken
at dawn?
Who has the sun come to meet
in the courtyard?
The feelings we kept silent
in our hearts
Are spoken today for all to hear
Tell your brother all about it
Just how much I really love you
Wedding bangles on your wrists
Your childhood toys all gone
Now your new life begins
Childhood passes so quickly
Like the months of spring
Now your new life begins
There's the girl with stars
in her eyes
Here she comes, the lovely bride,
bringing spring with her
The wedding music plays,
tears well in every eye
Colourless were the days
Colourless were the nights
To my world
You brought colour
Bland were the moments
Lived till today
To my world
You brought life
Paths going nowhere
Now lead somewhere
You make all troubles disappear
You can be trouble too
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
My heart came to flower
With the coming of spring
Since the day we met
The pages of our life were blank
Without love in our lives
Heartaches run through lines
of verse
For those with love stories
There was a time in the eyes
of the world
We had no name
Now they call us the
eternal lovers
Since the day we met
I'm no longer me
My heart came to flower
With the coming of spring
Since the day we met
O crazy one!
O naïve heart of mine
How deep is your love for her?
Have you ever asked yourself?
When selfishness has no hold
over you
Only then can you truly love
Heed my words
O crazy one!
O naïve heart of mine
In exchange of her smile
grant me a thousand tears
O crazy one!
True love demands this condition.
Why question it?
O crazy one!
Forget stubbornness.
Forget conditions
All is endured in love
That's the heartless learn to love
A little distance is not a bad thing
Love s fragrance spreads from away
Without you, my story is incomplete
Who says lovers are united forever
Where is this written?
When our worlds become one
Then your love will be complete
Come into his arms
O crazy one! O naïve heart of mine
O crazy one!
O naïve heart of mine
We always pray for what
we do not have
This is your fault
Why behave indifferently towards
those you love?
Why do such a thing? Tell me.
Your disregard worries me
You're either a character in your own life
or someone else's
Now you choose
O crazy one!
O naïve heart of mine
In exchange of her smile
grant me a thousand tears
O crazy one!
True love demands this condition.
Why question it?
O crazy one!