Until you have proven your innocence
you will be hand cuffed?
Even tribal men will not
have such rule like that
Throw your rule in fire, your law in
river. Such a foolish kingdom
DEVASENA, this kingdom is great...
If you say another word against...
Tall buildings and scriptures
alone does not make a kingdom great.
Having an open heart is better.
There is not one person with an
open heart & mind. What a shame...
Did you listen to that, my king?
She is so arrogant before you
See how she behaves
when you are not around
Baahubali...
>
What happened? Explain Sethupathy
Lots of people are around the temple
That time the Princess also arrived
Since it’s the time... for you to come
So I asked her to come on the other way..
Baahu, What is this?
Why are you making him panic?
I am making him spit the poison out..
You are crossing your limits, Baahubali
When you hand cuffed a pregnant women
This kingdom already crossed its limits
Pregnant women or old women
We investigate everyone the same way
Do you know what happened?
Tell me what happened, Devasena?
He asked all the women to come in one way
Then he touched all of them...
What you did is wrong... You should have
not cut his fingers.. but instead cut his head