Wow! SG bat! Is this yours, dad?
- Where's mom?
- She's coming.
Dad, where are you going?
Back in time.
Dad... Fast! Fast! Mom's coming, dad.
Make it fast, dad.
Nani, want some milk?
No...
I'll also come, dad.
Please! Please!
No. It'll go on till late at night.
You'll have to go to bed.
Please, dad! Let me come with you.
I've never seen you bat.
Please, dad. Please!
No!
Sarah, I'm going to watch
a movie with Rajesh.
A movie?! Let me join you, dad.
Please, dad!
- Take him along. Tomorrow's his day off.
- Please, dad. Please, dad. Please!
Please, dad. Please! Please!
Okay, let's go.
Yay!!!!
Who's that? Bastard!
What does bastard mean, dad?
It means All the best!'.
Oh.
Slowly...
There's a place me and
your dad often hang out.
Let me take you there. Let's go.
Yay! Let's go!
- Thank you, mom.
Good morning, birthday boy!
Happy birthday!
How's the toy?
Hey, listen. Brush your teeth.
Go and hurry up.
I'll put this there.
Wow!
Happy birthday!
Thank you, dad.
On our way home from the match,
let's buy that jersey from uncle's shop.
-Really?
-Hmm.
I made dal and curry.
Boil rice an hour before lunch. Okay?
All the best!
Thank you, sir.
Hey, Nani!
Guys
Stop. Stop. Bowl now.
Do it now.
Stop.
Let's go. Come on.
I heard we have a new player.
Stop. Stop.
Arjun... You don't know him, do you?
Nandu... The best batsman in our club.
Arjun. Ex-Ranji player.
You must've heard of him.
No, I didn't.
In that case, remember him.
He might soon be the
club's assistant coach.
Oh. Is he playing?
What is this, sir?
Where were you this whole time?
Were you waiting for Gavaskar to retire?
By the way, you mentioned something
about the assistant coach's post.
Your place is secure, I hope.
If he concentrates well,
forget about my job.
You'll lose your place. Watch out!
Stop it, guys. Leave now.
Stop it.
Go.
Nani, go sit with Rajesh.
- Okay.
- Come. Come.
It's a big match for
Hyderabad Cricket Association.
They're getting to play New Zealand
in this charity match for Hope Foundation.
Hey! It's John Spearman. Look!
So, Hyderabad vs. New Zealand
at LB stadium.
Let's head to the toss.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
This is tails and this is heads.
- Tails.
- That's tails.
- You won the toss.
- I think we'll have to bat.
Good luck!
The atmosphere today at the
stadium is unbelievable.
John Spearman,
Captain of the New Zealand team...
Presenting a cheque to the Chairman
of Hope Foundation.
Yay! John Spearman!
Money would be going to the underprivileged
children for their education.
Look at that! Beautiful as they walk out.
Spearman and Andrew are opening
the batting for New Zealand.
They would like to use this match to get
used to conditions of the Sub Continent.
Almost like a practice match for
the New Zealand this must be.
Hyderabad would like to give a tough fight,
this being their home ground.
John Spearman opening the batting and
Nivas ready to bowl the first ball now.
That is driven handsomely to the off side.
First boundary coming off the first ball.
New Zealand off the mark.
Hyderabad giving away runs.
That's a bold shot again.
Pulled brilliantly and that's a four.
A great start for New Zealand and
a good partnership for the opening batsmen.
Let's see if this fiery war continues.
Here he goes again. That's a six.
Wonderful! Really wonderful!
Brilliant!
This team's making it a practice match for
New Zealand before the big series to come.
Here he goes again.
Bang! Out of the ground.
Hyderabad doesn't look pleased at all.
They haven't had a single breakthrough yet.
Hey...
Put those drums aside and cover them
with a cloth.
We won't need them today.
Chakri introduced into the attack.
His first ball and he is punished as well.
New Zealand leaving no
room for the bowlers.
New Zealand's having a run party.
They are only dealing in boundaries.
Andrew going in for the big hits.
And that's a boundary too...
Which brings up the fifty for Andrew.
Ball! Ball!
What an innings this has been!
The coach is very happy.
Very well in finding the gap.
That's it.
Oh, yes!
That's brilliant timing.
But there's a man there.
Good throw, dad.
Arjun saves runs for Hyderabad.
Excellent piece of fielding.
One run away from his century.
John Spearman hit the ball,
gets a single easily.
What a magnificent
innings this has been!
He has been a lightening.
He hasn't timed that one.
Gone straight to Nandan Reddy.
For a second, It looked like he dropped it.
First wicket for Hyderabad.
New Zealand setting a big total here.
Nicely driven.
Swept away.
That's a grand total set by New Zealand
and more runs added to the total.
Hit straight for a six.
Hyderabad has a huge
task at their hands.
They need to hit 332 to win the match.
- Bro, want me to pull the drums out?
- Not yet. Wait for it.
Hi!
Pitch is quite bouncy.
They're literally smacking the ball.
So, boys... At least give them
a tough fight.
Don't go down so easily, okay?
We need 6.5 runs per over.
Nandu, do well.
Keep going. Keep going.
- Sir...
- Yes?
Arjun is a good player.
Shall we send him one down?
Oh. Do you want to get in after him?
Boys! Get going. Get going.
And I want all of you to play well.
It's okay.
Huge responsibility on the two opening
batsmen Nandan and Srikanth.
Hyderabad needs a good start.
They should make the most of the
field restrictions in the first 15 overs.
First ball. That crosses the boundary.
That's a great shot.
Good shot.
James Wheeler in for the attack.
Oh! That's hit the pad.
New Zealand appeals and up goes the finger.
Hyderabad loses its first wicket
quite early into the match.
Can we send Arjun in next?
Ugh, Mr. Murthy! Don't get started again.
Captain!
Required run rate rising and we have the
Captain of Hyderabad, Ravinder coming in.
That's timed sweetly.
The ball goes for a boundary.
Excellent shot! Fantastic!
That's wonderful!
The ball will go for a boundary.
Fifty runs partnership for
Nandan and Ravinder.
Nandan's two runs away from half century.
That's hit to the leg side.
Nandan Reddy completes his half century.
Brings much needed runs for Hyderabad.
Are you playing as well, sir?
Let me go get everyone then.
Oh, that is hit hard.
Fielder gets a finger on it but
that goes for a four.
That's a good shot.
Bro, want me to pull the drums out?
Wait on, man. I'll tell you when.
Hold it.
Goes again. The ball is in the air.
He should get it and that is caught.
Hyderabad loses
its second wicket and
Captain Ravinder walks
back to the pavilion.
Oh, damn.
Didn't I tell you?
Sir
-Sir
-Hmm?
If the next wicket falls...
If you keep bothering me,
I'll walk out of the ground.
Please!
New Zealand seems to be in control here
and that is bowled!
Can you believe that?
Hyderabad loses another wicket.
Sir...
Send him in.
Yes! Arjun, come on. Pad up.
Hyderabad in deep trouble now.
All the set batsmen have walked
back to the pavilion.
Sorry.
Wheeler has got 2 wickets
in the last two balls.
He is on a hat trick.
Let's see if he can do it.
Arjun is the new batsman at
number 5 for Hyderabad.
36 years old, ex Ranji player
facing the hat trick delivery.
Can he save Hyderabad from
an embarrassment?
Wheeler running to bowl,
will he get another wicket?
Oh, that is hit! What a stroke!
Denying the hat trick to Wheeler,
ball races to the boundary.
Good shot, dad!
That is as good as anything from
anybody at anytime.
Not an easy ball to play.
But he actually middles it.
Can Wheeler get a wicket this time?
Oh! He has hit is straight.
That is a good shot and the ball
is racing to the boundary.
Well played!
- Hit the next ball and show me, mate.
- What a start for this batsman!
This isn't going down well with Wheeler.
Wheeler is an experienced bowler.
It's not that easy to attack him.
I'm sure Wheeler is going
to answer back definitely.
Wheeler is considered as good as it
gets in this form of the game.
Last ball of this rollercoaster.
Wheeler over.
Front foot  full toss and
that's been hit high in the air.
We have no track of where the ball is.
Yes! There it is. It's out
of the ground. That's a huge hit!
If nothing, the crowd will get
their money's worth.
Bro! Pull the drums out now.
Come on, pull them out.
Wonderful! What a shot!
Brilliant!
And again well played.
It's going, going and gone.
Oh! What a performance this is already!
Thanks to this man Arjun.
Hyderabad seems to have got back
to this game already.
But it all depends on these
two players at the crease.
Chakri hits another shot.
Fifty runs partnership for Arjun-Chakri.
Bringing hope to the Hyderabad side.
Oh! He smashes through the covers.
Ball racing to the boundary.
And it's a four.
Hyderabad inching towards victory.
New Zealand disappointed.
Hyderabad needs just 45 runs in 30 balls.
That's a four again. Bowling change.
He goes on the front foot and misses.
That's out.
Chakravarthy walks back to the pavilion.
New batsman for Hyderabad.
New Zealand has that extra
fielder in the circle.
Don't want to give any run,
keeping Arjun on the non strikers end.
Bowled him. Austin Nash strikes.
The game now slipping
away from Hyderabad.
Oh, that's bowled again!
Hyderabad now in trouble.
8 wickets down! Vittal walks back.
Change of bowling.
Praveen, the new batsman...
Hits it in the air.
There is a man out there coming under it.
Will he be able to catch it?
And yes! He got the ball.
Hyderabad loses its 9th wicket.
Now this game is getting
interesting and really close.
Hyderabad needs 18 runs from just 9 balls.
Arjun on strike!
That's front foot. He hits it in the air.
Gone above the fielder into
the crowd for a six.
12 runs needed of 8 balls.
2 balls left of the over.
Here he goes again!
Ball in the air. Is it caught?
No! That's a six.
The match is again starting to
creep away from New Zealand.
They wouldn't want to lose it.
Looks like this man Arjun is going
to finish this match in this over.
Last ball of the over.
Oh, he goes again! Massive hit!
Is it going for a six?
Just short of the boundary. It's a four!
Hyderabad players are very happy.
Hyderabad just needs two runs.
This is nail biting.
It's a really tricky
situation for John Spearman.
He cannot afford to
give away a run now.
Fielder closing in the circle.
The first ball of the last over.
Short. Dot ball!
Wheeler getting all smiles here.
Will Hyderabad get a run now?
That's a bouncer and
he gets away with it.
2 runs needed from 4 balls.
Pressure building. Third ball.
Swing and miss.
Now only three deliveries remain.
Hyderabad's so close yet so far.
We've got 3 balls and
we only need 2 runs.
Rotate strike. Don't panic.
As the new batsman,
will he do it for Hyderabad?
Can he take a single this time
to get Arjun on strike?
Yes, he connects the ball.
Wanting the single. Arjun says no.
- Go, go back.
- Confusion here.
Sai going back. Will he be out?
And New Zealand misses a chance
to finish off the game.
No one's happy and that's
a terrible misunderstanding from Sai.